<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss">
  <channel>
    <title>We Work Remotely: DevOps and Sysadmin Jobs</title>
    <link>https://weworkremotely.com/categories/remote-devops-sysadmin-jobs.rss</link>
    <description>We Work Remotely: DevOps and Sysadmin Jobs</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0074/7619/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Clevertech: Senior DevOps Engineer </title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0074/7619/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; New York, NY
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://clevertech.biz"&gt;https://clevertech.biz&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Experience Remote done Right. Over 20 years of remote experience, all 500+ staff are 100% remote and we still grow vibrant relationships, provide exceptional opportunities for career growth while working with stellar clients on ambitious projects&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're working on:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Enterprise companies turn to us to help them launch innovative digital products that interact with hundreds of millions of customers, transactions and data points. The problems we solve every day are real and require creativity, grit and determination. We are building a culture that challenges norms while fostering experimentation and personal growth. In order to grasp the scale of problems we face, ideally, you have some exposure to Logistics, FinTech, Transportation, Insurance, Media or other complex multifactor industries&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7+ years of professional experience (A technical assessment will be required)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Senior-level experience with AWS (EC2, RDS, S3, ECS, ELB)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong background in Linux and Mongo Atlas administration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience deploying Kubernetes in a production environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with CI/CD in Jenkins or CircleCi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Infrastructure as code (we use Terraform)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with requirement gathering and presentation to executives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;English fluency, verbal and written&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional, empathic, team player&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Problem solver, proactive, go-getter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Straight from the Devs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Watch short snippets of actual developers (Real, not scripted) share why they joined &lt;a href="https://cleverte.ch/3"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YouTube Playlist&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Clevertech is an amazing place to work at&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;At Clevertech, you can expect that you will:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be 100% dedicated to one project at a time so that you can hone your skills, innovate and grow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a part of a team of talented and friendly senior-level developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on projects that allow you to use cutting edge tech. We believe in constantly evolving your mastery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;The result? We produce meaningful work and we are truly proud and excited to be creating waves in an industry under transformation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits of joining the Clevertech team&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We know that people do their best work when they’re taken care of. So we make sure to offer great benefits:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive Salaries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 Month Paid Time Off For You&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personal Development Fund&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tenure-Based Rewards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible Family Leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clevertech University&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clevertech Gives Back&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amazing Culture &amp;amp; Strong Community&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clevertech-senior-devops-engineer-11"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clevertech-senior-devops-engineer-11&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 13:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 13:53:59 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clevertech-senior-devops-engineer-11</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clevertech-senior-devops-engineer-11</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/9300/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Kitces.com: Senior Director of Platform &amp; Product</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/9300/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Virginia
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://kitces.com"&gt;https://kitces.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Director of Platform &amp;amp; Product&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The mission of &lt;em&gt;Kitces.com &lt;/em&gt;is to help real financial advisors be better and more successful, creating a 100X multiplier effect for our work and the number of consumers we can positively impact with the power of financial planning delivered by a Kitces-supported &lt;a href="https://www.kitces.com/financial-advicer-manifesto-values-difference-advisor-broker/"&gt;financial advicer&lt;/a&gt; to their clients. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To achieve this mission, &lt;em&gt;Kitces.com&lt;/em&gt; publishes the leading financial planning industry blog Nerd’s Eye View and the &lt;em&gt;Financial Advisor Success &lt;/em&gt;podcast, producing award-winning commentary on financial planning strategies and practice management trends for financial advisors &lt;a href="https://www.kitces.com/blog/celebrating-10-years-kitces-nerds-eye-view-hiring-career-opportunities/"&gt;ranked as the most Influential, Objective, Relevant, and Useful content amongst any online media publication for financial advisors&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Unlike traditional media sites, though, Kitces.com deliberately generates no revenue from advertising or sponsored content. Instead, we remain solely focused on creating value directly for our advisor readers in the form of one single deep-dive article each day, strengthening the awareness of and integrity of the Kitces brand through our quality and relevant content, and being compensated directly from our readers both on our site (for those who &lt;a href="https://www.kitces.com/become-member-for-imca-ce-and-cfp-ce-credits/"&gt;join our Members Section&lt;/a&gt;, hire us to &lt;a href="https://www.kitces.com/speaking/"&gt;speak and consult&lt;/a&gt;, or purchase our &lt;a href="https://www.kitces.com/kitces-online-ce-courses-for-financial-advisors/"&gt;Kitces Courses&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.kitces.com/kitces-financial-planning-value-summit-2022/"&gt;Summits&lt;/a&gt;), and through our &lt;a href="https://www.kitces.com/financial-planning-solutions-for-consumers/"&gt;co-owned financial services solutions for consumers&lt;/a&gt; (who may engage with our related financial advisory firms) as well as &lt;a href="https://www.kitces.com/practice-management-solutions-for-financial-advisors/"&gt;our business solutions for financial advisors themselves&lt;/a&gt; (for whom we have a number of businesses providing service and technology solutions for advisory firms). &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Kitces.com is hiring a Senior Director of Platform &amp;amp; Product &lt;/strong&gt;to lead the development of and serve as Product Owner for our digital media and online educational platform. In practice, this means learning how our Financial Advicer audience engages with our platform and its offerings, identifying and prioritizing improvements and new platform capabilities at the intersection of user demands and business strategy, lead our full-time developer team (and contractors, where appropriate) to build and implement the new features, and working cross-departmentally to deploy and launch. In addition, the Senior Director of Platform &amp;amp; Product should be able to strategize about the platform infrastructure and technical requirements to ensure stability and scalability as we grow, and have a strong focus on data-driven user experience, to help make UX improvements that strengthen the experience of, and bolster our Trusted-Source brand with, our Readers and Members. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;So if you can’t stand the negative reader experience of media websites that are filled with annoying slideshows and interstitial ads and want to work for a digital media platform that avoids advertising and cares about building a good platform experience, are constantly curious about what drives engagement behaviors and have always wanted the opportunity to work with an existing and loyal audience to build new digital experiences for them, and love turning product visions into reality by leading a developer team through a data-driven iterative process while building a great developer culture, … then this is the job for you! 😊 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Description/Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;This entirely virtually based staff position will report to Managing Director Rachel Zeller, and work directly with the Chief Financial Planning Nerd and lead visionary Michael Kitces, and serve as the Lead Engineer and Product Owner for the Kitces.com website and educational platform, including managing a growing team of contract and full-time employees in the Platform department. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Further description of annual responsibilities are indicated below. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Platform &amp;amp; Product Responsibilities&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Collaborate with leadership on and then be accountable for driving the execution of our overall platform strategy and roadmap, with responsibility for the entire product development process for new Kitces features and capabilities, including maintaining the product roadmap, prioritizing the backlog, gathering internal and external stakeholder input to determine requirements and user journeys, leading development and QA, deployment in coordination with other departments, and outcome tracking. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Responsible for managing the day-to-day and week-to-week developer team in their build process, mentoring and focusing the developers to optimize both their productivity and value of the developer team’s work output. (Currently we operate using a 2-week sprint cycle, though candidates will have the opportunity to set their own approach and cadence.) &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Accountable for the Platform experience of our readers and Members when they interact with the Kitces website, making iterative changes to improve on key Reader and Member metrics as they navigate to and engage with our offerings, and tracking and reporting on relevant metrics.  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Accountable for the management and maintenance of our (Wordpress) website, the Kitces Advicer Database (KAD), and other key integrated systems, as well as the identifying, vetting, and selection of potential new technology vendors and platform solutions to integrate with (or update or replace) existing systems, to ensure systems stability and scalability.  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Responsible for determining, tracking, and reporting relevant data metrics, regarding both utilization of the platform and product offerings, efficiency of the developer and building process, and outcomes of new features and capabilities. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Leadership of the Platform/developer team, including the training and development of team members (weekly L10s and 1:1s, quarterly check-ins, and annual performance reviews), and responsible for the expansion of the Platform team by mapping out future seats and being able to distinguish between the needs of full-time hires vs contractors. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Key Candidate Traits&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;The ideal candidate should be self-motivated enough to work in a virtual environment with limited supervision (autonomous), have an extremely strong inclination for continuous learning (self-development), an immaculate attention to detail (organized and efficient), a service mindset (seeks to collaborate and to help and support others), an ability to work in a changing environment (adaptability), and be highly effective at team communication in a virtual environment.  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Key domains of required expertise and experience include: &lt;br&gt;- Building within and around Wordpress website platforms (e.g., Wordpress, Javascript, etc.) &lt;br&gt;- Developing standalone web-based apps to integrate into existing products/platforms (e.g., Golang, Python, Ruby, etc.) &lt;br&gt;- Determining and managing server infrastructure for websites, web apps, and underlying user databases &lt;br&gt;- Product Owner leadership in executing the product development process &lt;br&gt;- Running DevOps and leading a team of developers through ongoing sprints &lt;br&gt;- Leadership of developers and building good developer culture &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Experience in digital media is strongly preferred but not required. Experience with EOS (Entrepreneurial Operating System) is preferred but not required. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Candidates must be U.S. Citizens and work primarily within the United States. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Compensation/Benefits&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;- Base salary $150,000 - $180,000/year based on experience &lt;br&gt;- Available bonus up to 12% of base salary, determined by meeting key Members Section and other business metrics &lt;br&gt;- $3,000 budget for additional training/skills education &lt;br&gt;- $4,000 conference budget &lt;br&gt;- $2,000 budget for technology hardware/software or related office materials &lt;br&gt;- Paid membership in a relevant membership association and for a relevant professional designation or certification &lt;br&gt;- 20 days of paid time off for combined vacation + sick, plus 6 national holidays &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;-Paid parental leave &lt;br&gt;-Participation in company health plan &lt;br&gt;- Participation in company 401(k) plan &lt;br&gt;-“No Meeting” Wednesdays &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;What it’s like working at Kitces.com&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are a team that lives by our values, our support of one another and our commitment to the community we serve. The successful candidate will share these Kitces Core Values: &lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do the Right Thing &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advisors First &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be the Trusted Source &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deposit More Than We Withdraw &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No A$$holes &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get Your Nerd On &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;At Kitces.com we have all but eradicated internal email. All internal communication is done via Slack or through Asana tasks.  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;When on Slack calls, video is expected as we believe hearing voices and seeing faces makes for stronger communication and connections. We lean on technology tools to get things done and protect our time. An example is our use of the delayed-send on Slack messages. While anyone might have a great idea pop up at any time, we are careful to make sure messages are only sent during regular business hours to respect the work/home boundaries of our work-from-home (or work-from-anywhere) team.  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a company we try to front load meetings to the beginning of the week so that the end of the week can be more focused on &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Deep-Work-Cal-Newport-audiobook/dp/B0189PVAWY/ref=sr_1_1?crid=3UPSKC83YLSAU&amp;amp;keywords=deep+work+cal+newport&amp;amp;qid=1666633794&amp;amp;qu=eyJxc2MiOiIyLjU1IiwicXNhIjoiMi40NSIsInFzcCI6IjIuNTYifQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;sprefix=Deep+Work%2Caps%2C172&amp;amp;sr=8-1"&gt;Deep Work&lt;/a&gt; to maximize our personal productivity. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;While, as a remote company, we tend to attract mostly hard-core introverts, we also recognize the value in creating work relationships, so we have a social committee that creatively offers a multitude of ways for people to connect in the ways they feel most comfortable. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To Apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;Interested candidates for the Senior Director of Platform &amp;amp; Product should complete the &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://airtable.com/shr9G3A3zW8lRIWNa"&gt;&lt;em&gt;pre-interview application https://airtable.com/shr9G3A3zW8lRIWNa&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Questions may be sent to &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:jobs@kitces.com"&gt;&lt;em&gt;jobs@kitces.com&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;===== &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/kitces-com-senior-director-of-platform-product"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/kitces-com-senior-director-of-platform-product&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 15:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 15:34:31 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/kitces-com-senior-director-of-platform-product</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/kitces-com-senior-director-of-platform-product</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/9143/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>University of Pennsylvania: DevOps Engineer (Remote Eligible)</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/9143/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Philadelphia, PA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.upenn.edu/"&gt;https://www.upenn.edu/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DevOps Engineer (Remote Eligible)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;University Overview&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The University of Pennsylvania, the largest private employer in Philadelphia, is a world-renowned leader in education, research, and innovation. This historic, Ivy League school consistently ranks among the top 10 universities in the annual U.S. News &amp;amp; World Report survey. Penn has 12 highly-regarded schools that provide opportunities for undergraduate, graduate and continuing education, all influenced by Penn's distinctive interdisciplinary approach to scholarship and learning. As an employer Penn has been ranked nationally on many occasions with the most recent award from Forbes who named Penn one of America's Best Employers By State in 2021.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Penn offers a unique working environment within the city of Philadelphia. The University is situated on a beautiful urban campus, with easy access to a range of educational, cultural, and recreational activities. With its historical significance and landmarks, lively cultural offerings, and wide variety of atmospheres, Philadelphia is the perfect place to call home for work and play.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The University offers a competitive benefits package that includes excellent healthcare and tuition benefits for employees and their families, generous retirement benefits, a wide variety of professional development opportunities, supportive work and family benefits, a wealth of health and wellness programs and resources, and much more.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;COVID-19 vaccination is a requirement for all positions at the University of Pennsylvania. New hires are expected to be fully vaccinated before beginning work at the University. For more information about Penn's vaccine requirements, visit the https://coronavirus.upenn.edu/ for the latest information.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Posted Job Title&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;DevOps Engineer (Remote Eligible)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Profile Title&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Application Developer C&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Description Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The DevOps engineer has responsibility for the planning, development, and support of a layer of infrastructure that allows the library to package, deploy, monitor, and maintain applications that are developed from scratch at the library or that are our local customizations of open-source software like Samvera and Blacklight. This work requires close collaboration with developers, digital projects staff, and sysadmins, because the DevOps Engineer will create systems and processes to deliver software prepared by developers to hardware managed by sysadmins, entailing responsibility for a distinct, emerging layer of technical infrastructure.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duties:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The DevOps Engineer will:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Collaborate with developers, the core services team, and an incumbent peer DevOps Engineer to organize and promote high-quality releases of library applications to production.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Research, plan, introduce, and maintain processes for continuous integration, automated builds, more frequent deployments, application monitoring, and other practices that will improve quality and efficiency.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Plan and implement robust development and production environments.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Test, troubleshoot, and upgrade systems and services to ensure high uptime/availability of library applications.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Serve as administrator and point of contact for cloud services on behalf of developers, digital projects staff, sysadmins, and stakeholders (currently primarily AWS S3 and Glacier storage, Digital Ocean).&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Participate in best practices such as integration testing, tracking QA process, and coordinating UA testing.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Bachelor's degree and a minimum of 1-2 years of experience, or an equivalent combination of education and experience, are required. Demonstrated experience developing, managing, and deploying Docker images is essential. Experience with Linux systems and a programming language like Bash, Python, or Ruby is required.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Experience with container orchestration tools (e.g. Docker Swarm, Kubernetes, etc.).&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Experience with configuration management and Infrastructure as Code (IaC) tools, such as Ansible and Terraform.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Proficient with continuous integration and continuous deployment frameworks, such as GitLab CI/CD, CircleCI, or GitHub Actions.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Experience with distributed version control systems, such as Git, for code management.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Understanding of system and/or microservices architectures.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Familiarity with software development life cycle processes.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Experience in a library or higher education environment preferred.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Application Requirement:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;A Resume/CV are required to be considered for this position. Please upload your Resume/CV; multiple documents are allowed.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Budgeted Pay Range:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;$70-80K commensurate with education and experience.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Location - City, State&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Philadelphia, Pennsylvania&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Remote Eligible&lt;/strong&gt; - This position is eligible for a fully remote schedule with all work performed remotely. (Note: Only salaried (i.e., exempt), non-temporary positions are eligible for remote work outside the tri-state area (Pennsylvania, New Jersey and Delaware.)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Department / School&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;University Library&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pay Range&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;$51,824.00 - $109,535.33&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Salary offers are made based on the candidate's qualifications, experience, skills, and education as they directly relate to the requirements of the position, as well as internal and market factors and grade profile.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Affirmative Action Statement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Penn adheres to a policy that prohibits discrimination on the basis of race, color, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, religion, creed, national or ethnic origin, citizenship status, age, disability, veteran status, or any other legally protected class.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Special Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Background check required after a conditional job offer is made. Consideration of the background check will be tailored to the requirements of the job.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;University Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• &lt;strong&gt;Health, Life, and Flexible Spending Accounts&lt;/strong&gt;: Penn offers comprehensive medical, prescription, behavioral health, dental, vision, and life insurance benefits to protect you and your family's health and welfare. You can also use flexible spending accounts to pay for eligible health care and dependent care expenses with pre-tax dollars.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• &lt;strong&gt;Tuition&lt;/strong&gt;: Take advantage of Penn's exceptional tuition benefits. You, your spouse, and your dependent children can get tuition assistance here at Penn. Your dependent children are also eligible for tuition assistance at other institutions.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• &lt;strong&gt;Retirement:&lt;/strong&gt; Penn offers generous retirement plans to help you save for your future. Penn's Basic, Matching, and Supplemental retirement plans allow you to save for retirement on a pre-tax or Roth basis. Choose from a wide variety of investment options through TIAA and Vanguard.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• &lt;strong&gt;Time Away from Work:&lt;/strong&gt; Penn provides you with a substantial amount of time away from work during the course of the year. This allows you to relax, take vacations, attend to personal affairs, recover from illness or injury, spend time with family—whatever your personal needs may be.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• &lt;strong&gt;Long-Term Care Insurance:&lt;/strong&gt; In partnership with Genworth Financial, Penn offers faculty and staff (and your eligible family members) long-term care insurance to help you cover some of the costs of long-term care services received at home, in the community or in a nursing facility. If you apply when you're newly hired, you won't have to provide proof of good health or be subject to underwriting requirements. Eligible family members must always provide proof of good health and are subject to underwriting.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• &lt;strong&gt;Wellness and Work-life Resources&lt;/strong&gt;: Penn is committed to supporting our faculty and staff as they balance the competing demands of work and personal life. That's why we offer a wide variety of programs and resources to help you care for your health, your family, and your work-life balance.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• &lt;strong&gt;Professional and Personal Development:&lt;/strong&gt; Penn provides an array of resources to help you advance yourself personally and professionally.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• &lt;strong&gt;University Resources:&lt;/strong&gt; As a member of the Penn community, you have access to a wide range of University resources as well as cultural and recreational activities. Take advantage of the University's libraries and athletic facilities, or visit our arboretum and art galleries. There's always something going on at Penn, whether it's a new exhibit at the Penn Museum, the latest music or theater presentation at the Annenberg Center, or the Penn Relays at Franklin Field to name just a few examples. As a member of the Penn community, you're right in the middle of the excitement—and you and your family can enjoy many of these activities for free.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• &lt;strong&gt;Discounts and Special Services&lt;/strong&gt;: From arts and entertainment to transportation and mortgages, you'll find great deals for University faculty and staff. Not only do Penn arts and cultural centers and museums offer free and discounted admission and memberships to faculty and staff. You can also enjoy substantial savings on other goods and services such as new cars from Ford and General Motors, cellular phone service plans, movie tickets, and admission to theme parks.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• &lt;strong&gt;Flexible Work Hours:&lt;/strong&gt; Flexible work options offer creative approaches for completing work while promoting balance between work and personal commitments. These approaches involve use of non-traditional work hours, locations, and/or job structures.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• &lt;strong&gt;Penn Home Ownership Services:&lt;/strong&gt; Penn offers a forgivable loan for eligible employees interested in buying a home or currently residing in West Philadelphia, which can be used for closing costs or home improvements.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• &lt;strong&gt;Adoption Assistance:&lt;/strong&gt; Penn will reimburse eligible employees on qualified expenses in connection with the legal adoption of an eligible child, such as travel or court fees, for up to two adoptions in your household.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;​&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To learn more, please visit: https://www.hr.upenn.edu/PennHR/benefits-pay&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply, visit https://apptrkr.com/3494283&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Copyright ©2022 Jobelephant.com Inc. All rights reserved.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;https://www.jobelephant.com/&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/university-of-pennsylvania-devops-engineer-remote-eligible"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/university-of-pennsylvania-devops-engineer-remote-eligible&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 16:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 16:53:54 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/university-of-pennsylvania-devops-engineer-remote-eligible</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/university-of-pennsylvania-devops-engineer-remote-eligible</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/9108/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Publitas.com: Site Reliability Engineer ( SaaS / Remote )</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/9108/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Amsterdam
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://publitas.com"&gt;https://publitas.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Increase product quality and grow with us.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We believe that business growth starts with a fantastic product that people want to use. And with Publitas, we aim to create an exceptional experience for browsing shoppers by publishing engaging content online. We are on a mission to inspire people from all over the world (60M today) through a more sustainable discovery experience. We guide our customers, leading retailers such as Mattel, IKEA, Home Depot, Lenovo, and Williams Sonoma, through the print transition and provide the personalized service they deserve, which has earned us their trust and loyalty. As a result, we have more than 1900 passionate customers and advocates worldwide.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our Operations Team is growing. We are expanding our team with multiple functionalities to ensure we follow the latest market trends, fulfill our highly positioned KPIs (availability, performance and security), and provide enough redundancy within the team to make sure we always have room for improvements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We embrace async work with fewer meetings and more focus time, but we are always happy to discuss new ideas of all team members so that we can elevate in the long run.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We do like state-of-the-art technology, although we understand that our customers' needs always have to be our first priority. We do everything in our power to provide quality service for them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will be responsible for ensuring that our infrastructure configurations and integrations are set according to our business needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will execute and optimize processes related to infrastructure and tools used for collaboration, development as well as for our production service.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will ensure security implementations are in place, maintained and documented according to our established standards (patch management, keeping the platform up to date, monitoring and adjusting configuration security).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will support the team to keep the documentation of our infrastructure, architecture, and processes intact and improve them continuously.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will deploy infrastructure components, applications, and upgrades in accordance with our release management process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will monitor the platform's health and performance proactively and will follow-up, mitigate and resolve incidents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will be implementing configurations and improvements of our monitoring components as well as introducing new components (functional and low-level monitoring).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will research and implement solutions for our product pipeline together with the Product Development Team which affects our infrastructure and operations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will scale our platform proactively to match the company's growth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can demonstrate Linux server administration knowledge (Debian/Ubuntu preferred) and background in internals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience working with a SaaS project before.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A solid understanding of core components (VPC, Security Groups, DNS, service discovery, etc.) of at least one IaaS (Infrastructure-as-a-Service) Platform (AWS, GCP, Azure).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with IaaC (infrastructure-as-a-code) and serverless environments (Cloudformation, Terraform, AWS Lambda, or similar).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with IaaS managed components such as RDS, managed Elastic(Search), message queues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have managed SaaS/Cloud tools such as or similar to (but not limited to) Google Workspace, Github, Slack, Zendesk, Geckoboard, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with scripting in Python and Bash.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with security implementations (packet filters, WAF, VPNs).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with writing basic SQL queries or willing to learn this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have configured and maintained CI/CD pipeline.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic but solid TCP/IP knowledge.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good at collaborating and multi-tasking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have up to date knowledge about the current (SaaS) cloud infrastructure industry standards and trends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have worked in an environment where ISO 27001 standard was implemented.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have been responsible for maintaining larger data sets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience in automated reporting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are familiar with Ruby.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you’ve been reading this far, chances are high you're a bit like us:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You desire to do things better and to improve the world around you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You believe that results and impact matter more than hours spent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re self-driven, and you love the fact that Publitas operates through &lt;a href="https://www.notion.so/publitas-ws/Publitas-Values-and-Habits-a97339a13a184d9db252e79f3c1da6d2"&gt;values &amp;amp; habits&lt;/a&gt; such as:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Honesty&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Respect&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generosity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Curiosity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What can you expect from us?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;€39,600 - €74,663 gross salary per year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;25 vacation days per year and your National Holidays off.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A contract of indefinite duration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work from anywhere you desire.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A monthly shared office space/co-working allowance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A one-time home office setup stipend.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A top-of-the-line MacBook.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monthly wellness allowance to stay healthy while working remotely.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Annual retreats in some of the greatest cities in the world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free books in Kindle and Audible store.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We'll challenge and support each other through &lt;a href="https://publitas-ws.notion.site/1-1-Sessions-2-1-c9aaa6c8442842d686c14538c5a983e4"&gt;1-1 sessions&lt;/a&gt; to get the most out of your and our potential.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;We promise to get rid of everything that stands in your way so you can create your best work. If this sounds like your kind of place, it’s time to get in touch.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Please feel free to contact our Recruitment Team at &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:careers@publitas.com"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;careers@publitas.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; if you have any questions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/publitas-com-site-reliability-engineer-saas-remote"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/publitas-com-site-reliability-engineer-saas-remote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 11:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 11:37:38 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/publitas-com-site-reliability-engineer-saas-remote</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/publitas-com-site-reliability-engineer-saas-remote</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0074/5180/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Paymentology: System and Infrastructure Engineer</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Contract</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0074/5180/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; London - Dubai - Johannesburg
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://paymentology.com"&gt;https://paymentology.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;As a driven and ambitious &lt;strong&gt;System and Infrastructure Engineer&lt;/strong&gt;, you will be joining a dynamic team of likeminded professionals and will deliver your expert knowledge and support to our Paymentology Infrastructure.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;The infrastructure of Paymentology is a globally diverse mix of Data Centres and Public Clouds and you have an amazing opportunity to get hands on with projects which will support the company and our mission of becoming the leading company within our market!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As the business grows and demands grows with it, we need an experienced mid-level Infrastructure Engineer to join our team and work closely with the wider infrastructure team to support the datacentres remotely.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU GET TO DO:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide technical and business-related knowledge to Paymentology teams to help resolve customer queries, including knowledge management &amp;amp; documentation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Detect possible service interruptions and share with partners and anticipate potential problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Root cause analysis (mature problem, configuration, change mgmt., process).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Escalate to appropriate group a detailed issue tracking (ticket) and status update to logger (requester.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Process automation capabilities &amp;amp; detect possible procedural improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take ownership by coordinating the feedback to the customer where analysis is required from other implementation and development departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attend change control meeting calls &amp;amp; follow problem/change management policies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Respond to alerts issued by Paymentology's monitoring system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Daily maintenance/administration of multiple Unix /Windows systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan for Monthly / Quarterly OS Patching (as per Audit Policy.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be involved in application deployments support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on new technologies and tools based on the requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on DevOps automation tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What it takes to succeed:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor's or master’s degree in Computer Science or Computer Engineering and/or equivalent working experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of Linux /Windows System Administrator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge of Linux, Solaris, Windows Servers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong background in OS administration, understanding of code and, script &amp;amp; work on job automations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Solaris Zone &amp;amp; LDOM.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands on experience with web servers like Nginx / Apache / IIS (knowledge in MTLS &amp;amp; SSL certificate is plus.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with virtualization VMWare / Oracle VM, SAN management and concepts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong technical problem-solving skills and experience in SSH, LDAP, SMTP, DNS, HTTP/S, SSL, GPG, Syslog logging facility, Openvpn.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced in different tools for monitoring health check-ups using Nagios, Cacti, Zabbix or wazuh.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Security Configuration on Windows /UNIX based servers hardening of the system (Any audit experience like PCI or ISMS is plus.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify and analyse the issues that hamper the performance of the system, and work in close collaboration with the Paymentology teams, recommending solutions to issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain proper documentation of all the procedures, configurations and programs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to use a wide variety of Azure / Aws / Oracle Cloud services.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to use a wide variety of open-source technologies &amp;amp; Patch Management Solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge on DevOps automation tools is a plus i.e., Puppet Jenkins, ELK, DataDog, Terraform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open-mindedness and willingness to learn.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU CAN LOOK FORWARD TO:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;At Paymentology we value making a difference to the lives of the people who work for us and who live in the communities where we operate. As values are important to us, you can look forward to working alongside fellow Paymentologists, who share these values. You’ll be part of a team that is passionate about making a difference on a global scale.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/paymentology-system-and-infrastructure-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/paymentology-system-and-infrastructure-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 12:49:14 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/paymentology-system-and-infrastructure-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/paymentology-system-and-infrastructure-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paymentology: Cloud Engineer</title>
      <region>EMEA Only</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Contract</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; London - Dubai - Johannesburg
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://paymentology.com"&gt;https://paymentology.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;As a &lt;strong&gt;Cloud Infrastructure Engineer &lt;/strong&gt;at &lt;strong&gt;Paymentology&lt;/strong&gt;, you'll be working closely with the entire technical team to build enterprise-level, highly scalable, highly secure financial processing systems that power tens of millions of transactions and tie them to web, mobile and API interfaces that make it easy for people to issue, redeem and reconcile prepaid cards all over the world. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This position requires in-depth knowledge of AWS,Azure and OCI services and cloud computing, and the ability to communicate architectural trade-offs &amp;amp; design options, so that &lt;strong&gt;Paymentology&lt;/strong&gt; can make informed decisions. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You will work closely with our product owners, application engineers, and security team to identify work that improves the stability, security, and self-service nature of our infrastructure, driving those ideas and projects from inception to completion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU GET TO DO:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Be part of improving our solutions -&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Position, architect and support the implementation of AWS, Azure and OCI cloud-based solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, build and migrate applications, software, and services on the AWS, Azure and OCI platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare and deliver technical presentations explaining products or services to clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide hands-on subject matter expertise and ensure that the tooling to deploy and manage our infrastructure is automated, secure, and easy for our developers to use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in the identification and evaluation of new technologies and development of new services.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support the core infrastructure for our existing test and production environments and participating in a 24x7 on-call rotation to assist other engineers in quickly debugging and resolving production-related issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify and collect metrics that allow the product development team to pinpoint areas for improvement and measure change.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What it takes to succeed:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have 6+ years of experience in cloud engineer &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with public cloud (Azure/AWS/GCP) services and infrastructure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with configuration management tools (Ansible, Puppet, Chef)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Automating Infrastructure deployment using IaaC tools such as terraform, Cloud formation, ARM templates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands on experience on DevOps Tools preferable on gitlab or any other tools such as github, jenkins etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Container image management experience using Docker&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in source control management with git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scripting experience such as bash, shell, powershell, python etc should be required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be passionate about identifying constraints or bottlenecks in engineering lifecycles and automating them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be accomplished with leveraging AWS &amp;amp; Azure Software Development Kit (SDK) with a grounded understanding of cloud services and best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and maintain system performance, scalability, manageability, and security requirements for mid-to-large scale programs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research, analyse, design, propose and support the delivery of solutions that are appropriate for Paymentology's business and technology strategies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with development and operations teams to develop practical automation solutions and custom modules. Troubleshoot automation issues and find practical solutions that move projects forward promptly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have excellent written and oral communication skills and the ability to interact and be involved with client negotiations and interfacing with management. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Agile methodologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be passionate about learning new things and solving problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organisational skills and the ability to independently execute work tasks in a rapidly changing, fast-paced environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bonus:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An eye for security - demonstrated understanding of how to operate pipelines at scale while maintaining the security and integrity of sensitive data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience deploying computational workloads on Kubernetes or other workload managers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU CAN LOOK FORWARD TO:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;At &lt;strong&gt;Paymentology&lt;/strong&gt; we value making a difference to the lives of the people who work for us and who live in the communities where we operate. As values are important to us, you can look forward to working alongside fellow Paymentologists, who share these values. You’ll be part of a team that is passionate about making a difference on a global scale.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/paymentology-cloud-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/paymentology-cloud-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 12:44:43 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/paymentology-cloud-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/paymentology-cloud-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/8740/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Unlimited Tech Solutions: Digital Project Manager &amp; HubSpot Specialist</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/8740/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Florida, USA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.unlimitedtechsolutions.com"&gt;http://www.unlimitedtechsolutions.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Role:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re looking for a Digital Project Manager &amp;amp; HubSpot Specialist who will work directly with clients and be their main point of contact and communicate with assertiveness and care both internally and with our clients. Manage projects by working with various departments to achieve results, and go above and beyond for our clients. Expand your HubSpot knowledge and practice by performing certain actions in HubSpot on behalf of our clients.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on “behind-the-scenes” client tasks like building emails, workflows, blogs, etc. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with internal teams as needed (for example, project managers to ensure projects stay on track, content team for writing email workflows, or our back-end engineers for data migrations or complex integrations).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan, coordinate, and oversee projects with a wide variety of tasks, work with cross-functional teams and ensure all targets and requirements are met and completed on schedule and within budget. Managing scope creep is your responsibility. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate regularly with the client regarding project scope and proactively yet kindly manage client expectations about what is included in the scope and what is not. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be our clients' primary point of contact and engage them in (8-10) live training sessions per week to ensure they get the most out of HubSpot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own multiple projects concurrently. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Projects you will be managing include website projects (from onboarding and goal setting to wireframing, copy, design, HubSpot implementation, QA, and launch), marketing campaigns (including graphic design, ads, SEO), complex integration work, and more. This means you will manage the internal resources and keep things on track, it doesn’t mean being an expert in all these fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively develop, implement, and monitor new and/or existing processes that improve cross-functional alignment, effectiveness, and decision-making.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create handbooks for our clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HubMasters Program: Play a major role in this program's function, communication with clients, running live group sessions, etc. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Results: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All projects in your care run smoothly and budgets are maintained carefully&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Results are communicated on a regular cadence through detailed and insightful reports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client satisfaction is high on all your projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our SOP &amp;amp; Process database grows with your assistance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Requirements:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of project management experience. Agency experience is a plus. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth HubSpot experience and the ability to train others on HubSpot’s many features and all Hubs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to manage multiple projects and consistently meet deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tech-savvy. Ability to quickly figure things out on your own when working with various tools. This is crucial for this position. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accountable, mature, responsible, organized and delivers on promises.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong client management skills with an assertive yet empathic presence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a fast-paced environment while being able to manage and prioritize changing deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess the passion for helping businesses succeed through a commitment to continuous improvement, critical thinking, reliance on facts (not just data), and rolling up your sleeves to get it done. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Available during EST mornings and afternoons.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Benefits and Perks:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are a remote-only company. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We offer full-time positions; we hire you as an employee, no matter where you are in the world. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generous compensation package.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid time off and holidays according to your country of residence. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rest week each December (we shut down entirely for a week so we can all disconnect)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with a team of high-achievers in a collaborative environment where everyone has a real chance to contribute. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with a highly supportive, accepting, and inclusive founding team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Our Hiring Process:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We value our team member’s time and nurture relationships with them. We promote our team members based on their results, not resumes. Expect this process to be unlike most others. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zoom conversation with our Director of Operations to discuss the position, our company, clients, and plan and hear about your experience and abilities, career growth plans, salary expectations, and why you’d like to work with us.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-2 more Zoom conversations with our CEO and/or CTO to get to know one another. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We’ll ask you to complete a short and fair exercise to demonstrate your skills and passion for working with us. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If we’re a good fit, we’ll send you an offer. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reference check - we’ll check references only after sending out an offer letter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once your references come in, we’ll send you a contract and get you onboarded.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We aim to have an intense yet quick hiring cycle. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/unlimited-tech-solutions-digital-project-manager-hubspot-specialist"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/unlimited-tech-solutions-digital-project-manager-hubspot-specialist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 11:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 11:32:31 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/unlimited-tech-solutions-digital-project-manager-hubspot-specialist</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/unlimited-tech-solutions-digital-project-manager-hubspot-specialist</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/8738/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Unlimited Tech Solutions: Technical Project Manager</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/8738/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Florida, USA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.unlimitedtechsolutions.com"&gt;http://www.unlimitedtechsolutions.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Role:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re looking for a Technical Project Manager who will work directly with clients and be their main point of contact and communicate with assertiveness and care, both internally and with our clients. The person in this role will manage projects by working with various departments to achieve results and go above and beyond for our clients. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define project scope, deliverables, milestones, roles, and responsibilities in collaboration with key stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage projects with top-down oversight throughout their duration and ensure their successful completion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Projects you will be managing include website projects, complex integration work, and more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor project progress continuously and create weekly, detailed reports on measurable items, such as milestones and deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and plan projects. This includes, but is not limited to, identifying milestones, ensuring the team is not over capacity, assigning tasks to the correct people, etc.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A fundamental understanding of UML and BPMN 2.0 is desirable, and the ability to document requirements in detail and produce data flow diagrams is required. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write detailed, meticulous briefs for contractors, freelancers, and/or employees for technical work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan, coordinate, and oversee projects with a wide variety of tasks, work with cross-functional teams and ensure all targets and requirements are met and completed on schedule and within budget. Managing scope creep is your responsibility. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate regularly with the client regarding project scope and proactively yet kindly manage client expectations about what is included in the scope and what is not. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be our clients' primary point of contact and engage them in (8-10) live training sessions per week to ensure they get the most out of HubSpot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own multiple projects concurrently. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively develop, implement, and monitor new and/or existing processes that improve cross-functional alignment, effectiveness, and decision-making.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document our processes regularly (create SOPs and handbooks for our team and clients).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Train additional members as required. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Results: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All projects in your care run smoothly and budgets are maintained carefully.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Results are communicated on a regular cadence through detailed and insightful reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Client satisfaction is high on all your projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively participate in creating efficiencies in project delivery, documenting internal processes, and recommending improvements when needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Requirements:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of project management experience is desirable. Agency experience is a plus. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A degree in information technology, business management, or a related field is desirable, but proven work experience is valued above all.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience working with HubSpot is desirable. Prior experience working in any CRM, ERP, or Service management software is required and the ability to clearly communicate how and why the systems were used is beneficial.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possesses fundamental understanding in the areas of web development, process management, contact management systems, APIs, databases, and system design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to manage multiple projects and consistently meet deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tech-savvy. Ability to quickly figure things out on your own when working with various tools. This is crucial for this position. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accountable, mature, responsible, organized and delivers on promises.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong client management skills with an assertive yet empathic presence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a fast-paced environment while being able to manage and prioritize changing deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess the passion for helping businesses succeed through a commitment to continuous improvement, critical thinking, reliance on facts (not just data), and rolling up your sleeves to get it done. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communication skills and the ability to interact professionally with a diverse group. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/unlimited-tech-solutions-technical-project-manager"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/unlimited-tech-solutions-technical-project-manager&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 11:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 11:22:48 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/unlimited-tech-solutions-technical-project-manager</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/unlimited-tech-solutions-technical-project-manager</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/8350/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Solar Monkey: Senior DevOps Engineer</title>
      <region>Europe Only</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/8350/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; The Hague
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://solarmonkey.nl"&gt;https://solarmonkey.nl&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;We are looking for someone who likes creating stability and efficiency in a cloud environment. Someone who is versatile at the shell to debug weird network issues, but who hates snowflakes. Someone who likes developing tools that are used by other developers, and makes their lives easier. Someone who masters our cloud.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whilst it is possible to run completely “server less” these days, that isn’t always practical for all applications. Thus we still run a moderate cloud stack on the Google Cloud Platform. As you can see in the description of &lt;a href="https://engineering.solarmonkey.nl/jobs/#our-stack"&gt;our stack&lt;/a&gt;, we use Hashicorp’s tools for deployment. That means a Consul + Vault cluster, and Nomad to schedule (container) jobs. That actually runs stable without too much maintenance. Most of the work is in improving the experience of other developers, and making it easier for them to do the things they need to do on the operations side.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For example, we use Terraform to control and set up our resources. However that doesn’t mean that it is clear for everyone what to use and how to tie that together. Modularizing and documenting is key here. Also, we want to enable continuous integration, so everyone can see what the effect would be of their changes, without giving everyone the proverbial keys to the kingdom.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The rest of the team will look at you for advice on how to deploy their service, how to keep sight on its metrics and errors. Note that you are probably the one with the most knowledge, we do rotate on-call duties with the whole team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Compensation&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The envisioned salary range for this position is €55-80k per year (excluding 8% holiday pay), depending on experience. Besides that we offer Stock Appreciation Rights and a 4% learning budget. You’ll get an Apple Macbook Pro (M1 or M2!) to work on.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience managing a cloud platform (GCP/AWS/OpenStack) from code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are proficient in Python (or another server-side language like Go or Ruby, and willing to learn Python).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can design a “stack” for a new service so it is scalable and trustworthy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience with container based deployment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are able to work with a diverse group of people. You’re not a rock star or code-ninja, you’re a human, of some form 🙂.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can clearly outline your thoughts about a technical solution in written form (and diagrams are always a bonus!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You actively engage with others to optimize processes and reduce bottlenecks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are able to pick up new things quickly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You want to work 32 to 40 hours a week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wishlist&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience with Hashicorp’s Consul, Vault &amp;amp; Nomad.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience with Terraform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/solar-monkey-senior-devops-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/solar-monkey-senior-devops-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 11:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 11:08:46 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/solar-monkey-senior-devops-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/solar-monkey-senior-devops-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/8346/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Onko Health: DevOps Engineer</title>
      <region>UK Only</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/8346/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; London (Paddington)
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://onkohealth.co.uk/"&gt;https://onkohealth.co.uk/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Onko Health is hiring a remote DevOps engineer for our cancer support application engineering team, shaping and evolving our methods, tooling and automation.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re a healthtech scaleup company. Our cancer health journey mobile apps blend remote support and coaching from expert oncology practitioners with self-help approaches, backed by a data handling platform.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We serve a number of UK healthcare providers and NHS trusts, delivering improved outcomes for patient health and care giving. We're bringing development in-house, growing a new engineering team to deliver upon our ambitious international growth plans. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You will become integral to our Agile approaches, owning engineering automation, shaping the build and deploy pipelines, participating in software development process discussions and enabling engineers to fully embrace the DevOps mindset.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your role includes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing the AWS infrastructure (Elastic Beanstalk, RDS, S3, VPC, CloudFront etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing developer access to the AWS infrastructure (IAM)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Setting up and maintaining CI/CD pipelines and empowering developers to release to production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attending Agile ceremonies, articulating the needs and considerations for nimble and harmonious DevOps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with developers on the build process for our four code bases, written with Angular and TypeScript, Node.js, iOS and Android&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We're looking for&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the AWS platform (certification is a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competence with AWS CodePipeline with CodeCommit (Git)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competence with observability, performance and health monitoring (preferably AWS CloudWatch)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A solid understanding of effective DevOps for web and mobile application engineering&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good competence with Linux&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a progressive Agile environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You may also bring - or like to gain - skills or interests around any of&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Monitoring application performance | observability, auditing | exploring DevOps tools/methods&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary and benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;£60,000 - £80,000 - reviewed at six months - we're keeping an open mind&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share scheme for formative team members (once proven value to the business)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;25 days holiday (plus bank holidays) and five days unpaid leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible working practices - tell us what you need - e.g. optional four day week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personal development plan that you can shape, with budget for related training/certifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/onko-health-devops-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/onko-health-devops-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 09:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 09:39:39 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/onko-health-devops-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/onko-health-devops-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clevertech: Senior DevOps Engineer</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; New York, NY
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://clevertech.biz"&gt;https://clevertech.biz&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Experience Remote done Right. Over 20 years of remote experience, all 500+ staff are 100% remote and we still grow vibrant relationships, provide exceptional opportunities for career growth while working with stellar clients on ambitious projects&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're working on:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Enterprise companies turn to us to help them launch innovative digital products that interact with hundreds of millions of customers, transactions and data points. The problems we solve every day are real and require creativity, grit and determination. We are building a culture that challenges norms while fostering experimentation and personal growth. In order to grasp the scale of problems we face, ideally, you have some exposure to Logistics, FinTech, Transportation, Insurance, Media or other complex multifactor industries&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7+ years of professional experience (A technical assessment will be required)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Senior-level experience with AWS (EC2, RDS, S3, ECS, ELB)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong background in Linux and Mongo Atlas administration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience deploying Kubernetes in a production environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with CI/CD in Jenkins or CircleCi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Infrastructure as code (we use Terraform)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with requirement gathering and presentation to executives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;English fluency, verbal and written&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional, empathic, team player&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Problem solver, proactive, go-getter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Straight from the Devs&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Watch short snippets of actual developers (Real, not scripted) share why they joined &lt;a href="https://cleverte.ch/3"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YouTube Playlist&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Clevertech is an amazing place to work at&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;At Clevertech, you can expect that you will:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be 100% dedicated to one project at a time so that you can hone your skills, innovate and grow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a part of a team of talented and friendly senior-level developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on projects that allow you to use cutting edge tech. We believe in constantly evolving your mastery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;The result? We produce meaningful work and we are truly proud and excited to be creating waves in an industry under transformation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clevertech-senior-devops-engineer-10"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clevertech-senior-devops-engineer-10&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 18:18:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 18:18:47 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clevertech-senior-devops-engineer-10</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clevertech-senior-devops-engineer-10</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/8296/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Equinix: Software Engineer, Systems Engineering</title>
      <region>UK Only</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/8296/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Redwood City, California
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.equinix.com/"&gt;https://www.equinix.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;About Equinix&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Equinix is the world’s digital infrastructure company, operating 210 data centers across the globe and providing interconnections to all the key clouds and networks. Businesses need one place to simplify and bring together fragmented, complex infrastructure that spans private and public cloud environments. With Equinix Metal, customers can rapidly deploy automated single-tenant infrastructure and interact with 1,800+ networks and 2,900+ cloud and service providers. Our global platform allows customers to place infrastructure wherever they need it and connect it to everything they need to succeed.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Equinix, we help the world’s digital leaders scale with agility, speed the launch of digital services, deliver world-class experiences, and transform people’s lives. Our culture is based on collaboration and the growth and development of our teams. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We hire hardworking people who thrive on solving challenging problems and give them opportunities to hone new skills, and try new approaches, as we grow our product portfolio with new software and network architecture solutions. We embrace diversity in thought and contribution and are committed to providing an equitable work environment that is foundational to our core values as a company and is vital to our success.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Equinix Metal, a leading bare metal cloud provider, is looking to grow our software engineering team! If you are an experienced software engineer and looking to help build out services that will affect how the next generation of infrastructure and hardware is delivered to the world, join our team!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This role can be remote or based in one of our office locations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;In this position, you will be an individual contributor of a small, focused team building and testing images for customers, ensuring processes are automated and repeatable, and introducing new hardware to the fleet safely and efficiently (read as automatedly as possible). You should have a passion for solving hard problems and a deep understanding of operating systems and debugging problems all the way down to the interaction with firmware and hardware. You’ll also:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Live and breath the developer experience with the platform we are responsible for caring and feeding for - our customers are Equinix Metal engineers, and they deserve the best&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deal with ambiguity and drive to the heart of problems - when developing / managing an internal platform, sometimes you participate in the “what” just as much as the “how”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Seek out weaknesses, identify problems and solutions, approach every day with a self-starter attitude and a focus on resolving problems while not getting bogged down in a changing landscape&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Validate new hardware configurations, firmware configurations / versions, and overall creating a healthy intersection of known-good configurations while tailoring our automation, processes, etc., to take full advantage of our available platforms and tools&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaboratively write RFC’s / blueprints that establish our go-forward patterns, architecture, or that otherwise create a picture of where we want to go&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help drive software design and improve our system architecture, making sure components are built in a way that is conducive for rapid development and deployment onto our platform&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with external vendors, internal stakeholders, to help align on the best procurement and logistics around our hardware lifecycle&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in on call rotation to support this product team's software in production&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deeply care about technology, your craft and about the success of your teammates and the company. Have strong intrinsic motivators to help drive self-improvement&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate clearly with all stakeholders&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team player, ability to work with a team to deliver complex software&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 4-6 years experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor's in Computer Science or Computer Engineering is a nice to have, but not required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Linux, with experience troubleshooting both hardware and kernel issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to debug issues with hardware and firmware / root cause analysis (or strong desire to learn)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with at least one programming language; preference given to candidates with Golang experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the git workflow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ideal candidates have some modern CI experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ideal candidates have some experience with data center technologies or have worked with bare metal servers before. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A desire to learn!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Desirable experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of operating systems a plus: Ubuntu, Debian, RHEL, CentOS, Rocky Linux, AlmaLinux, Windows, VMware, Talos, NixOS, Flatcar, etc. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous exposure to end to end bare metal provisioning lifecycle, and associated technologies used in the ecosystem, e.g. QEMU/KVM, PXE, grub, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of VMWare ESXi and Windows&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Awareness and desire to learn about data center networking related to bare metal provisioning; DHCP, BGP, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous exposure to a containerized environment with Docker and Kubernetes&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;Equinix is an equal opportunity employer. All applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, religion, colour, national origin, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, age, status as a protected veteran, or status as a qualified individual with disability.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/equinix-software-engineer-systems-engineering"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/equinix-software-engineer-systems-engineering&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 09:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 09:00:27 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/equinix-software-engineer-systems-engineering</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/equinix-software-engineer-systems-engineering</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0076/4314/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>TestGorilla: Senior System Engineer - Cloud</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0076/4314/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Amsterdam
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://testgorilla.com"&gt;https://testgorilla.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Hi,&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;I’m Ariel, Engineering Manager at TestGorilla. We’re a fast-growing HR tech startup that helps teams make better hiring decisions faster and bias-free.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Over the past year, we’ve experienced tremendous growth. More than 7,500 companies have replaced CVs with our assessments to screen candidates in an unbiased and data-driven way.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;As we scale our efforts in 2022 and beyond, we’re looking for a &lt;strong&gt;Senior System Engineer - Cloud&lt;/strong&gt;, to help us accelerate the development of our product. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The proposition&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping shape a fast-growing HR tech startup as an early employee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully remote position with bright, motivated, and friendly colleagues around the world &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary + Share Appreciation Rights (SARs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible hours and vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid parental leave &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote working budget: €1,000 per year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning and development budget: 3.5% of base salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The job in a nutshell&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are looking for a &lt;strong&gt;Senior System (Tech Ops) Engineer&lt;/strong&gt; to join our engineering department and help us bring our product to Enterprise level maturity. Your work will directly impact hundreds of thousands of users around the world.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a senior member of the engineering team, you will develop and own best-practice methodologies for provisioning, configuration management, and monitoring of our distributed systems. Your primary goal is to make sure these systems run reliably in a secure cloud environment.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As our company is experiencing high growth, you’ll also be responsible for the scalability of our cloud infrastructure and performing robust capacity planning. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’ll spend time on the following&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will design, deploy, and continuously improve our cloud infrastructure with a focus on reliability, scalability, and security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will provide input into long-range platform requirements and operational guidelines, with a focus on automation and continuous improvement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will perform incident management duties to investigate and follow up on incidents and deliver structural fixes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will raise the standard of our engineering excellence by implementing best practices for coding, testing, and deployment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will provide organisation-wide IT support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will guide other teams and departments in implementing security standards across the company and conduct risk management activities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will help implement compliance policies and procedures including security patch management for our complete IT assets inventory and our business continuity plan (e.g., backups, disaster recovery)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will act as a mentor for less-experienced team members through both your technical knowledge and leadership&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here’s what we’re looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are inspired by our mission to put &lt;em&gt;one billion people in dream jobs&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are fully aligned with our &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/careers/"&gt;values &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a deep understanding of deployment and monitoring strategies for reliable, highly scalable, and robust cloud infrastructure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are an expert on cloud and containerization technologies such as &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/test-library/role-specific-skills-tests/aws-test/"&gt;AWS&lt;/a&gt; and Docker&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have strong knowledge of automation and infrastructure as code technologies such as Terraform, Ansible, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience working with complex CI/CD pipelines for production releases in a microservices-based architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are an organised self-starter with an ability to follow through on tasks under minimal supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are comfortable in an ambiguous, ever-changing startup environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are passionate about improving skills and learning new technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You enjoy influencing others and always advocate for technical excellence while being open to change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re resilient in ambiguous situations and can approach challenges from multiple perspectivesYou have strong written and verbal communication skills. You can validate your decisions and communicate them clearly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We typically expect candidates with &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;at least 7 years of experience in system engineering, DevOps, SRE&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, or similar positions to have the skills mentioned above.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Bonus points if …&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience working in a SaaS company and a fast-growing startup &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have knowledge of SQL, data modelling, ETL, and data warehousing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience in at least one modern programming language such as Python, Java, Javascript, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interested?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;Here at TestGorilla, we eat our own dog food. We use our assessment platform to make sure we make the best hiring decisions faster and bias-free. I took one too and I enjoyed it!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;So if this role sounds like a good fit for you, I’d like you to &lt;a href="https://assessment.testgorilla.com/testtaker/publicinvitation/4eb3bd6e-1bae-43bc-8c27-b2b3725a9269"&gt;take an assessment&lt;/a&gt; so we can get a better idea about whether you would fit the role. It’s also a great opportunity for you to get to know our product!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you’re hired, I’ll do everything I can to help you succeed at TestGorilla and throughout the rest of your career.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-system-engineer-cloud-3"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-system-engineer-cloud-3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 08:30:34 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-system-engineer-cloud-3</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-system-engineer-cloud-3</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TestGorilla: Senior IT Engineer</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Amsterdam, The Netherlands
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/"&gt;https://www.testgorilla.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Hi,&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;I’m Ariel, Engineering Manager at TestGorilla. We’re a fast-growing HR tech startup that helps teams make better hiring decisions faster and bias-free.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Over the past year, we’ve experienced tremendous growth. More than 7,500 companies have replaced CVs with our assessments to screen candidates in an unbiased and data-driven way.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As we scale our efforts in 2022 and beyond, we’re looking for a &lt;strong&gt;Senior IT Engineer&lt;/strong&gt;, to help us accelerate the development of our product. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s in it for you?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping shape a fast-growing HR tech startup as an early employee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully remote position with bright, motivated, and friendly colleagues around the world &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary + share appreciation rights (SARs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible hours and vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid parental leave &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote working budget: €1,000 per year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning and development budget: 3.5% of salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;The job in a nutshell&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are looking for a Senior IT (Tech Ops) Engineer to join our engineering department and help us bring our product to &lt;strong&gt;Enterprise level maturity&lt;/strong&gt;. Your work will directly impact hundreds of thousands of users around the world.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a senior member of the engineering team, you will develop and own best-practice methodologies for provisioning, configuration management, and monitoring of our distributed systems. Your primary goal is to make sure these systems run reliably in a secure &lt;strong&gt;cloud environment&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As our company is experiencing high growth, you’ll also be responsible for the scalability of our cloud infrastructure and performing robust capacity planning. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Furthermore, you will own and automate &lt;strong&gt;IT-related tasks&lt;/strong&gt; including granting/revoking access for on/offboarding team members, securely configuring and maintaining our tools, keeping the IT asset inventory up to date. You will also collaborate to comply with security and privacy standards such as SOC II, ISO 27001, and GDPR.&lt;br&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’ll spend time on the following:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will design, deploy, and continuously improve our cloud infrastructure with a focus on reliability, scalability, and security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will provide input into long-range platform requirements and operational guidelines, with a focus on automation and continuous improvement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will perform incident management duties to investigate and follow up on incidents and deliver structural fixes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will raise the standard of our engineering excellence by implementing best practices for coding, testing, and deployment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will provide organisation-wide IT support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will guide other teams and departments in implementing security standards across the company and conduct risk management activities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will help implement compliance policies and procedures including security patch management for our complete IT assets inventory and our business continuity plan (e.g., backups, disaster recovery)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will act as a mentor for less-experienced team members through both your technical knowledge and leadership&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here's what we are looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are inspired by our mission to put &lt;em&gt;one billion people in dream jobs&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are fully aligned with&lt;a href="http://www.testgorilla.com/careers"&gt; our values&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a deep understanding of deployment and monitoring strategies for reliable, highly scalable, and robust cloud infrastructure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are an expert on cloud and containerization technologies such as &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/test-library/role-specific-skills-tests/aws-test/"&gt;AWS&lt;/a&gt; and Docker&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have strong knowledge of automation and infrastructure as code technologies such as Terraform, Ansible, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience working with complex CI/CD pipelines for production releases in a microservices-based architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are an organised self-starter with an ability to follow through on tasks under minimal supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are comfortable in an ambiguous, ever-changing startup environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are passionate about improving skills and learning new technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You enjoy influencing others and always advocate for technical excellence while being open to change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re resilient in ambiguous situations and can approach challenges from multiple perspectivesYou have strong written and verbal communication skills. You can validate your decisions and communicate them clearly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We typically expect candidates with &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;at least 7 years of experience in system engineering, DevOps, SRE&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, or similar positions to have the skills mentioned above.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus points if…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience working in a SaaS company and a fast-growing startup &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have knowledge of SQL, data modelling, ETL, and data warehousing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience in at least one modern programming language such as Python, Java, Javascript, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interested?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;We don’t offer rainbow glitter unicorns or dog-friendly offices (we literally don’t have an office), but we do offer real people, solid core values, and a product meant to give everyone a fair, unbiased chance at their dream jobs.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Here at TestGorilla, we eat our own dog food. We use our assessment platform to make sure we make the best hiring decisions faster and bias-free. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;So if this role sounds like a good fit for you, I’d like you to take an assessment so we can get a better idea about whether you would fit the role. It’s also a great opportunity for you to get to know our product!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;If you’re hired, I’ll do everything I can to help you succeed at TestGorilla and throughout the rest of your career.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-it-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-it-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 08:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 08:28:16 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-it-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-it-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0064/7639/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>OpSourced: DevOps Engineer</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0064/7639/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Savannah, Georgia
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://opsourced.com"&gt;https://opsourced.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;We cultivate teams of skilled and devoted DevOps Engineers capable of providing a fanatical level of support for our wide range of customers and a variety of tech stacks.  Then we set that team loose to build and support highly available, scalable, and reliable infrastructures and automation that our customers can use to iterate as often and with as little friction as possible.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You'll work directly with other engineers on our teams, and alongside those customers day to day to build, automate, and manage their infrastructures so they can focus on their applications!   If you're looking for an opportunity to work at a scale few ever get to, this could be the right place for you!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Qualifications :&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;•  Experience maintaining production Linux environments&lt;br&gt;•  Experience working with tools like Terraform / Ansible / CloudFormation&lt;br&gt;•  Experienced and comfortable working in Git&lt;br&gt;•  Strong Customer Service Mindset&lt;br&gt;•  Strong Troubleshooting abilities&lt;br&gt;•  Attention to detail&lt;br&gt;•  Self motivated and diligent&lt;br&gt;•  Ability to participate in an on-call pager rotation.&lt;br&gt;•  Must be eligible to work in the U.S. (or as a contractor if located in timezones 0 through +3)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred Qualifications :&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;•  Strong Terraform, Ansible, or CloudFormation experience&lt;br&gt;•  Experience with AWS, GCP, Azure or prior certifications&lt;br&gt;•  Experience with Kubernetes, EKS, GKE, AKS&lt;br&gt;•  Experience building and maintaining CI / CD pipelines&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Email hiring@opsourced.com or visit https://opsourced.com/hiring/ to apply!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/opsourced-devops-engineer-2"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/opsourced-devops-engineer-2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 20:22:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 20:22:01 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/opsourced-devops-engineer-2</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/opsourced-devops-engineer-2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/8024/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Big Cartel: Senior Site Reliability Engineer</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/8024/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Salt Lake City, UT
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.bigcartel.com"&gt;https://www.bigcartel.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;We are looking for an experienced Senior Systems Reliability Engineer to join our DevOps team. In this role, you’d work alongside our development teams to ensure the availability of the Big Cartel systems. You would be on call and available to troubleshoot and restore services when needed. Experience with managing physical hardware and server systems a plus.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The "ideal" candidate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: We’d still love to hear from you even if some of the below attributes don’t describe you, so long as you’re excited about Big Cartel and eager to contribute.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wants to build tools that make an impact on the lives of artists and creators&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can work alone or as part of a small team to build and launch ambitious projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has knowledge and experience automating systems with &lt;strong&gt;Ansible&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Chef &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with operating high throughput &lt;strong&gt;Rails&lt;/strong&gt; applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of &lt;strong&gt;Linux&lt;/strong&gt; operating systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Built &lt;strong&gt;Docker&lt;/strong&gt; images for production use cases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Setup and operated &lt;strong&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/strong&gt; clusters and authoring of Helm charts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Installation and configuration of monitoring tools such as &lt;strong&gt;Prometheus&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Nagios&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of web metrics and tracking down performance issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Big Cartel has a fixed salary structure per role based on data from industry research. This ensures pay equality for employees doing the same job at the same level. Current salary range for a Senior level Application Developer is &lt;strong&gt;$130,000 - $160,000.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hiring timeline&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Application closing date: &lt;strong&gt;October 31, 2022&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;We hope to fill this position by the end of November 2022.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/big-cartel-senior-site-reliability-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/big-cartel-senior-site-reliability-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 17:24:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 17:24:39 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/big-cartel-senior-site-reliability-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/big-cartel-senior-site-reliability-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/6802/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>BRYTER: Cloud Infrastructure Engineer</title>
      <region>Europe Only</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/6802/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Frankfurt
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://bryter.com"&gt;https://bryter.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What you will do&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🚀 This opening is for the infrastructure team which has the mission to build and maintain the multi-cloud, multi-region infrastructure for our product. As a member of this strategically important team you will be part of defining and shaping how we leverage cloud infrastructure and operations within the BRYTER organization.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🗄️ Our work starts with contributing to the product roadmap, helping with product growth at BRYTER.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🔨 We are building and maintaining the cloud infrastructure that hosts the BRYTER ecosystem.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;👩‍👩‍👧‍👧 As part of our highly collaborative ways of working, you will work closely with other engineers within the company, providing expertise and guidance on various topics such as running highly available services, deployment to multiple datacentres, building optimal CI/CD configuration, and so much more.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Where we hire&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;While we are a remote first company, we are currently eligible to hire FTE in the following countries: Germany, UK, US, Ireland, Italy, Netherlands, Poland, Portugal, Serbia and Spain. We do intend on expanding this list to the new territories, as our company scales in the future, so please do keep in touch with us, even if you are not based in those countries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What we are looking for&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;💻 For this role, we are looking for someone who has extensive practical experience with building and maintaining systems with Amazon Web Services (AWS), ideally with services such as Elastic Compute Cloud, Virtual Private Cloud, and Aurora.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;⚙️ Our infrastructure stack is based on Terraform and Kubernetes. This role requires you to have extensive professional experience in these technologies, ideally having built and maintained a multi-region cloud infrastructure setup&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;💜 You care about the people you work with and you are willing to grow together. You also care about the wider team and you want to work on a service that adds value for others.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🔄 We work together very closely and with short feedback cycles, both within our team and towards our peers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🙌 You proactively seek to support and collaborate with others, not just when you’re stuck, but also whenever you can lend a hand. We are largely self-organized, so we require you as our teammate to proactively come forward and take the lead at times without being explicitly told to do so.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The icing on the cake&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🍰 You have experience in (or always wanted to learn about) some of the other tools and technologies we employ such as Azure Cloud, Gitlab, Packer, Ansible, Postgres to only name a few.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About BRYTER&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;BRYTER is an all-remote organization, that started in Germany, but is now spread all over Europe and right now expanding into the US.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We enable business experts to build and distribute powerful applications. Our software is intuitive and simple enough for non-IT experts to understand within minutes, yet powerful enough and enterprise-ready for industries with complex reasoning and demanding use cases. We especially cater to experts in law, finance, tax and compliance by helping them automate and standardize decision making.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Want to know more about what working at BRYTER looks like? Take a peek at our &lt;a href="https://bryter.com/careers/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Careers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; page. 🚀&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/bryter-cloud-infrastructure-engineer-2"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/bryter-cloud-infrastructure-engineer-2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 09:28:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 09:28:39 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/bryter-cloud-infrastructure-engineer-2</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/bryter-cloud-infrastructure-engineer-2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/7853/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>AgencyAnalytics: Cloud Software Engineer (GCP)</title>
      <region>Canada Only</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/7853/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Toronto, Canada
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://agencyanalytics.com"&gt;https://agencyanalytics.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;We are a fully remote company based in Toronto with a small development team. Our very successful SaaS application is now 10 years old and has always used the latest technology and UI practices. We believe in making the highest quality product possible without worry about deadlines. All our developers are given a tremendous amount of trust and the full control to take a project from start to finish.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A good development team can be even better with a good DevOps team. We are seeking a Cloud Software engineer with experience using Google Cloud Console, Bash scripting and Kubernetes. You will be responsible for supporting the development team to remove bottlenecks in their process and execute deployments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This position is 100% remote and only eligible for those who are authorized to work in Canada.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build, support and automate all GCP infrastructure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimize CI/CD pipelines for various Environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform recurring Security Audits to ensure best practices are followed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimize and support log analysis/alerting using BigQuery and Grafana&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create bash scripts to automate various development, deployment and backup operations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clearly document all processes and tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job requirements&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of cloud-native operations, technologies, principles, and Infrastructure as a code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 years Google Cloud infrastructure support &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working for a software company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-3 years experience with Kubernetes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience writing bash scripts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with a Cloud Data Warehouse (BigQuery, RedShift, Snowflake)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Google Cloud IAM policies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profit-sharing, distributed quarterly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frequent promotions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 weeks vacation and paid sick days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Happy Hour once a month &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extended health benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continued education allowance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Annual fitness allowance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work from anywhere in the world&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Join a bootstrapped, product-focused, &amp;amp; customer-oriented team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/agencyanalytics-cloud-software-engineer-gcp-1"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/agencyanalytics-cloud-software-engineer-gcp-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 15:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 15:48:50 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/agencyanalytics-cloud-software-engineer-gcp-1</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/agencyanalytics-cloud-software-engineer-gcp-1</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proxify AB: Senior DevOps Engineer</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Sweden
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://career.proxify.io"&gt;http://career.proxify.io&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are searching for a Senior DevOps Engineer. You can be a perfect candidate if you are growth-oriented, you take pleasure in your work, and you enjoy working on new ideas to develop exciting products. By joining Proxify, you will get considerable opportunities to work with leading brands and amazing startups to build their next product and growth features. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we are looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have +4 years of solid development experience as a DevOps Engineer;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have +3 years of experience in Azure Cloud and Kubernetes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have good understanding of operating, monitoring, and documenting cloud solutions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible and able to work with minimal supervision;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upper-intermediate English level;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can communicate well with both technical and non-technical clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nice-to-have:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Timezone: CET (+/- 3 hours);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Azure certifications in Cloud development and architecture would be a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set up and maintain local development and test environments (based on containers and similar technologies);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set up CI/CD pipelines, including build processes for container images and delivery to container registries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Planning and setting up automated updates to AKS (Azure Kubernetes Service) and surrounding infrastructure components;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continued setup and improvement of Cloud infrastructure to support new cloud-native solutions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with the stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;What we offer:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;💻 &lt;strong&gt;100% remote work&lt;/strong&gt;: Work from anywhere.&lt;br&gt;👌🏻 &lt;strong&gt;Flexibility&lt;/strong&gt;: The ability to change the project to another one.&lt;br&gt;💵 &lt;strong&gt;Financial growth&lt;/strong&gt;: Competitive compensation and performance-based increases.&lt;br&gt;🧘🏻‍♂️ &lt;strong&gt;Freedom&lt;/strong&gt;: Very flexible working schedule&lt;br&gt;.🚀 &lt;strong&gt;360-degree growth&lt;/strong&gt;: Opportunities for professional development and personal growth.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your benefits with Proxify:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Be part of the Proxify community&lt;/strong&gt;: Network with like-minded and enthusiastic individuals to make a difference. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Make an impact&lt;/strong&gt;: You get the opportunity to work on projects that inspire you and add value to your career.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Transparency&lt;/strong&gt;: Contracts with transparency in earnings and working hours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Save your time&lt;/strong&gt;: Fast and efficient hiring process to match you with the project of your preference.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Ownership: &lt;/strong&gt;Take ownership of your work and enjoy more freedom in your career.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/proxify-ab-senior-devops-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/proxify-ab-senior-devops-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 13:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 13:39:30 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/proxify-ab-senior-devops-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/proxify-ab-senior-devops-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/7838/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>amazee.io: DevOps Engineer </title>
      <region>Oceania Only</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/7838/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Zurich, Switzerland 
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://amazee.io"&gt;https://amazee.io&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DevOps Engineer (APAC)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Description: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Grüezi, Howdy, and G’day! We're &lt;a href="http://amazee.io/"&gt;amazee.io&lt;/a&gt;, a ZeroOps application delivery hub for engineering teams to deploy applications more easily. Our developer-centric, open source platform makes developers’ lives and jobs easier, minimizing the stress of managing infrastructure or operations. amazee.io supports organizations across the globe to accelerate their cloud and container adoption, along with providing easily managed Kubernetes for developer teams. We run anywhere in the world, with 24/7/365 dedicated support. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re looking for a DevOps Engineer to join our remote team. As a DevOps Engineer with amazee.io you’ll be supporting our mission by engineering, managing and maintaining our hosting platform and infrastructure, allowing secure and scalable hosting. You’ll also be central to the future development of our services, looking for continuous improvement to the platform and supporting the roll out of new features and releases to keep us at the cutting edge of what we do. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you feel like this could be the role for you, then come and join a team of open source enthusiasts, committed to providing flexible hosting solutions in an open, transparent work environment, and having fun doing it.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be doing: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Onboarding and training clients on our platform, as well as providing them with post onboarding virtual support &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Guiding trouble free deployments of client projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specifying, implementing, documenting, and rolling out of features/updates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep diving into engineering and architecture topics, supporting the improvement and growth of our products and services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensuring the stability of our hosting environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implementing, practicing and advocating DevOps practices and methods &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicating via gifs and emojis&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Tech you’ll be using on the daily: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kubernetes, Docker, AWS, Terraform, PHP, MySQL, node.js&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll bring: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Production experience working with Kubernetes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfort working within Cloud environments (AWS, GCP, Azure)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands on experience designing and engineering microservices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience system engineering in/with Linux, Nginx, Varnish, MariaDB/MySQL and PHP, Docker &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfort communicating and documenting in English &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Work location&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Location is not important, although we have a preference for an Australia or New Zealand time zone for your working hours.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;amazee.io is dedicated to providing a work environment of trust, transparency, and inclusion for everyone. As a fully remote company we offer flexibility when it comes to working hours and location. Here’s some other things you can expect from us.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we’ll bring:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A fully distributed team of creative colleagues in a flat, open and transparent organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible working hours, and time off in lieu when you work more than you should&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote working &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 paid days off a year for conference attendance or education related commitments &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An annual education benefit of $2,200 or equivalent to dedicate to your professional development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An annual wellbeing benefit of $750 or equivalent to dedicate to your physical or mental health &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A connectivity benefit of $150 or equivalent a month, to help with internet/data costs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your own tech budget with the freedom to choose your setup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sweet, sweet Swag - Hoodies and other goodies &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;amazee.io Quest!&lt;/strong&gt; - After 3 years, you’ll get 3 weeks paid off work to undertake a profound personal goal, or undertake a bucket list type challenge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So what’s next?: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Apply! Send us your CV and cover letter showcasing who you are, your technical skills, and anything else you think we should know! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The amazee.io Team &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/amazee-io-devops-engineer-3"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/amazee-io-devops-engineer-3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 10:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 10:56:06 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/amazee-io-devops-engineer-3</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/amazee-io-devops-engineer-3</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0017/0933/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Tyler Technologies: Senior Infrastructure (DevOps) Engineer</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0017/0933/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Plano, TX
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.tylertech.com/"&gt;https://www.tylertech.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;At Tyler Technologies, our Data &amp;amp; Insights solutions are designed help government use data more strategically and effectively in the design and delivery of their programs and missions. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a &lt;strong&gt;Senior Infrastructure Engineer&lt;/strong&gt;, you will build and manage the infrastructure necessary to host our exacting worldwide clients. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Us?  &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We exist to inspire and empower every public servant to address society's pressing issues. We do that by enabling data-driven leadership through connected data and shared insights.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our data as a service platform and cloud-based solutions support the world’s most effective open and internal data sharing programs at every level of government. What we do matters. New York, Seattle, San Francisco and 230+ other cities, states, counties and federal agencies use us to connect citizens and their internal teams with information that matters to their day to day life.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why This Job Is Important &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You’ll help the company design, operate, monitor, and grow the platform that hosts our global client base. You will work side-by-side with the rest of the engineering team to ensure our new features and services meet our security and performance guidelines. You will build the infrastructure that makes other engineers even more productive. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Due to our work with several federal agencies,  candidates must reside in the U.S. for this position.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a Typical Day, You Might... &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute patches to open-source tools to better support our mission and operations. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in on-call rotation, which includes all engineering staff. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with security staff to implement advanced security and compliance requirements for our clients. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diagnose and fix systems and software failures and build additional automation to prevent the failure scenario from reoccurring. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage DNS and SSL configurations for customer domains.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build out a production environment. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upgrade our infrastructure. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform various AWS administration tasks. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AWS &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building out environments (Setting up VPC, configuring ACLs and security groups) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IAM user/key management &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CloudFormation &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with other services including: EC2, S3, RDS, ECR, EKS &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with other non-AWS infrastructure as a service platforms is also relevant. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Linux&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of Linux OS at a systems level. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Systems engineer experience is a plus &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ubuntu knowledge is a plus &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coding skills &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong familiarity with at least one dynamic language (Ruby or Python is a plus) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience writing configuration as code &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with objected oriented programming and data structures is a plus &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Configuration management &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with and proficient with at least one configuration management tool (e.g. Chef, Salt, Ansible, Puppet, etc.) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience specifically with Chef is a plus &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Containerization/Orchestration &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Docker&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Kubernetes &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Mesos and Marathon is a plus &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Networking skills are a plus &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are interested in working with engineers to help scale and optimize their services. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are calm in high-pressure situations and skilled at triaging situations.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ability to pass a federal background check required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;You belong here! Nobody checks every box and if your experience and interests match some of the above, we would love to hear from you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/tyler-technologies-senior-infrastructure-devops-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/tyler-technologies-senior-infrastructure-devops-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 23:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 23:23:47 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/tyler-technologies-senior-infrastructure-devops-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/tyler-technologies-senior-infrastructure-devops-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clevertech: Cloud Security Engineer</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; New York, NY
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://clevertech.biz"&gt;https://clevertech.biz&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Experience Remote done Right. Over 20 years of remote experience, all 500+ staff are 100% remote, and we still grow vibrant relationships and provide exceptional opportunities for career growth while working with stellar clients on ambitious projects.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're working on:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Enterprise companies turn to us to help them launch innovative digital products that interact with hundreds of millions of customers, transactions and data points. The problems we solve daily are real and require creativity, grit and determination. We are building a culture that challenges norms while fostering experimentation and personal growth. In order to grasp the scale of problems we face, ideally, you have some exposure to Logistics, FinTech, Transportation, Insurance, Media or other complex multifactor industries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7+ years of professional experience (A technical assessment will be required)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Senior-level experience with AWS (EC2, RDS, S3, ECS, ELB)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of experience in Cyber Security roles with a preference in engineering.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with industry-standard regulations and compliance frameworks (PCI-DSS, ISO, NIST, SANS, SOX, SOC II, HIPAA)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong background in Linux and Mongo Atlas administration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience deploying Kubernetes in a production environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with requirement gathering and presentation to executives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;English fluency, verbal and written&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional, empathic, team player&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Problem solver, proactive, go-getter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Straight from the Devs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Watch short snippets of actual developers (Real, not scripted) share why they joined &lt;a href="https://cleverte.ch/3"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YouTube Playlist&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Clevertech is an amazing place to work at&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;At Clevertech, you can expect that you will:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be 100% dedicated to one project at a time so that you can hone your skills, innovate and grow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a part of a team of talented and friendly senior-level developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on projects that allow you to use cutting-edge tech. We believe in constantly evolving your mastery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;The result? We produce meaningful work and we are truly proud and excited to be creating waves in an industry under transformation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clevertech-cloud-security-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clevertech-cloud-security-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 16:00:00 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clevertech-cloud-security-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clevertech-cloud-security-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/6781/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>TriumphPay: Senior DevOps Engineer</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/6781/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Dallas, TX
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.triumphpay.com"&gt;https://www.triumphpay.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Are you the kind of person who likes working on a variety of challenging projects? Would you enjoy helping a team work on log correlation this month and then move to tuning our OCR process next month? If so, being a TriumphPay Senior DevOps Engineer might be the thing for you. We are looking to join our three person DevOps team to help us solve our most challenging issues. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;At TriumphPay, you will join a team that:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has experience. The majority of our developers have more than 10 years of professional experience. One has published a book with the Pragmatic Programmers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has won the Chicago Innovation Award and Harvard Business School New Venture Contest.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is fully remote. We care about what you can accomplish, not where you choose to accomplish it from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Believes diversity is essential and strongly encourages applications from women and minority candidates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can articulate their values. You can read about our values at &lt;a href="https://engineering.hubtran.com/2017/06/01/welcome-to-the-new-hubtran-blog"&gt;on our blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pays well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Offers benefits including health insurance, 4 weeks of vacation, 401k, and more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;In order to succeed in this role you should be:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced. You have managed an entire environment, not just a single server.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Curious. You aren’t content with the status quo and know that we can always improve.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-directed. You can work on your own while prioritizing tasks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborative. You can work with others to improve a solution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Detail Oriented. Measure twice and cut once, only via code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Empathetic. You think about how your decisions will impact others on the team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong communicator. You will proactively communicate issues and trade-offs with team members to support alignment and fast decision making. You will also work closely with developers on issues and features before, during, and after deployment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Tech Stack&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Some of the technologies we use are:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AWS – we deploy on AWS, but are thoughtful about what services we use and how we deploy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kubernetes (K8S) – We deploy on Kubernetes for much of our infrastructure. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PostgresSQL/SQL Server&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Terraform, Helm, and to a lesser extent, ansible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prometheus/Grafana for metrics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Loki/Grafana/ELK for logs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We currently have a few different products, and each one is slightly different. We’ll be working to unify our tech stacks as much as possible over time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;Bonus points for:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Experience with Rails, SQL Server, DevSecOps, C#&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;About TriumphPay&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;TriumphPay is carrier payment platform that connects brokers, shippers and carriers through forward-thinking solutions that help each party successfully process, settle and manage carrier payments and drive growth. TriumphPay offers supply chain finance to brokers, allowing them to pay their carriers faster and drive carrier loyalty. TriumphPay provides tools and services to increase automation, mitigate fraud, create back-office efficiency and improve the payment experience. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;TriumphPay is a division of TBK Bank, SSB, Member of FDIC and Equal Housing Lender, and a member of the Triumph Bancorp, Inc. (Nasdaq: TBK) group. Triumph Bancorp is a financial holding company with a diversified line of community banking, national lending, and commercial finance products.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/triumphpay-senior-devops-engineer-2"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/triumphpay-senior-devops-engineer-2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 13:33:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 13:33:58 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/triumphpay-senior-devops-engineer-2</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/triumphpay-senior-devops-engineer-2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0071/3241/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Follow Up Boss: Senior Infrastructure Engineer</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0071/3241/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Remote
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.followupboss.com"&gt;https://www.followupboss.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;About the job&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a Senior Infrastructure Engineer at Follow Up Boss, you'll help us deliver the most reliable and performant experience for our customers and keep our existing infrastructure stable. You'll work on every single piece of our infrastructure and touch every single one of our applications with the support of our existing infrastructure team. As we continue to grow, you will help our infrastructure scale in a steady, reliable way that is rarely about the hottest, newest technologies, but often the mature, boring ones that keep pagers quiet and are easy to reason about.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Why would you want to work here?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re a bootstrapped, profitable company started back in April of 2011. We're a young, ambitious company who only answers to our customers and we don’t just claim to be customer-centric - &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/followupboss/reviews"&gt;we live it&lt;/a&gt;. We're fully remote and have been since day 1. Here's a few more reason's we think you'll love working here - and be sure to check out &lt;a href="https://www.followupboss.com/about/"&gt;our video on how we work&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunity to have a big impact on our growth and your career&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No red tape or pointless meetings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive base salary - top 10% in US; for this position &lt;strong&gt;the range is $166K - $180K&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong benefit package including a 401k with 6% match, fully paid health/dental/vision insurance for you and your family, funding for continuing education, paid parental leave, kindle + unlimited books, home office setup stipend, company meetups, and 20 PTO + 10 sick days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solve challenging technical problems and put your skills to the test every day. We've processed over a billion emails. Each month we send nearly 3 million text messages and handle 700k+ minutes of call time for tens of thousands of active customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;See a direct impact of your work and value you created for customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide direct input on technical and non-technical decisions. Your opinion matters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;This role is for you if...&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You would describe yourself as patient, empathetic and having a good sense of humor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re independent, self-motivated and can stay efficient and productive without someone looking over your shoulder all day long&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have superb written and verbal skills (with a professional yet fun demeanor)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are based in the United States (or similar time zone)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are happy to have direct communication with customers (we are customer driven).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Your qualifications include:&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Self-motivated&lt;/strong&gt; and proactive mindset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Remote work&lt;/strong&gt; experience is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Based in the USA&lt;/strong&gt;, with a quiet home office with fast internet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of experience in infrastructure pertaining to web applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience with configuration and infrastructure automation using tools like Ansible, Vagrant, Packer, and Terraform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well-versed in using and managing various Amazon Web Services offerings. We use services such as RDS, EC2, Route 53, S3, ElastiCache, and more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience with monitoring and alerting systems (we use Datadog, StatsD, PagerDuty, Pingdom)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of scripting languages (Bash, PHP, Python)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of relational databases (we use Aurora MySQL and PostgreSQL)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of CI/CD environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of UNIX and networking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of being security conscious.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to understand application code base for troubleshooting and partnering with software engineers to improve the measurability of code performance and reliability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional time management skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Attention to detail and commitment to quality.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pragmatic decision-making regarding human and financial costs associated with infrastructure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Your responsibilities will include:&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under the guidance of existing Infrastructure staff, take shared ownership and responsibility for the infrastructure, reliability, scalability, and performance of our applications and services.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn the current state of our infrastructure from other engineers and existing documentation, and improve that documentation to capture your findings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify and propose concrete steps to best improve existing infrastructure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in determining top infrastructure priorities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in ensuring company security practices are being applied for all staff members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively measure and monitor systems and react to anomalies as part of an on-call rotation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively troubleshoot issues with the infrastructure and services.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Press us forward with more automation and tooling to support our customer growth and engineering team effectiveness.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentor other team members.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;About the work&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;Here are some things we’ve worked on recently that might give you a better sense of what you’ll be doing day to day:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement and deploy ProxySQL for our database servers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform Capacity Planning for various services and infrastructure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Modify and extend Ansible/Packer configurations for managing AWS instances&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Handle on-call responsibilities across Follow Up Boss services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication and debugging DDL latency on a particular database server&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adjust existing and new metrics, monitoring, and alerts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;30 Day Targets&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Become familiar with our product and infrastructure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pair with fellow engineers to gain knowledge about the system and how we work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve the new hire onboarding process, by being a part of it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;60 Day Targets&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist with security updates for Infrastructure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve tooling for developer docker environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve gaps we have in metrics and monitoring.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;90 Day Targets&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Join on-call rotation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help with database scaling of a newer service.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help address key infrastructure performance-related items.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Core Engineering Values&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Teamwork&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code Quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Focus and Prioritization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Customer Driven&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leadership Qualities &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Why Follow up Boss? &lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;❤️ &lt;a href="https://followupboss-1.wistia.com/medias/s5nobr10pw"&gt;This is us  &lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🏝 Work remotely: Live and work wherever you like!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;💰 Competitive salary: Our career framework pays in the top 10% no matter where you live.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;👩🏾‍⚕️ Insurance: Company-paid health, dental &amp;amp; vision insurance for all of our team members and their families.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🍼 Family leave: generous family leave - fully paid!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;💻 Home office setup: Get a Macbook Pro + $1000 to set up your home office.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;👩🏻‍🏫 Personal development stipend: $1000 per year to focus on bettering yourself.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🤑 401(k): With 6% company match!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;✈️ Retreats: Join us for company get-togethers every year!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;☕️ Co-working stipend: Get some extra cash for a co-working space or a coffee shop work.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;📚 Free books and Kindle: Get a free Kindle and all the free books - digital and audio - you like, anytime.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;💪 Gym: Monthly stipend to keep you active and feeling good.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;☕️ Money each month to spend on caffeine.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Apply for the job&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;Do you want to join our team as our new Senior Infrastructure Engineer? Then we'd love to hear from you!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/follow-up-boss-senior-infrastructure-engineer-2"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/follow-up-boss-senior-infrastructure-engineer-2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 14:54:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 14:54:05 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/follow-up-boss-senior-infrastructure-engineer-2</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/follow-up-boss-senior-infrastructure-engineer-2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0016/1650/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Springboard: Mentor - Cyber Security Career Track (Part-time/Remote)</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Contract</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0016/1650/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; San Francisco, CA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://springboard.com"&gt;https://springboard.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Company &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;At Springboard, we’re on a mission to bridge the world’s skills gap, offering transformative online education in data science, UI/UX design, machine learning, and coding. Our courses may be tech-enabled, but we're ultimately human-centric: each student taps into a vast community throughout their time with us, engaging with fellow students, industry-expert mentors, student advisors, and career coaches, the goal of which is to successfully transition students into their dream job. Through this hybrid approach, we’ve helped thousands of learners revamp their careers and, by extension, their lives, with hundreds of top-notch job offers received every year and a near-perfect placement rate for our program graduates.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Opportunity&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Springboard runs an online, self-paced Cyber Security Career Track in which participants learn with the help of a curated curriculum and 1-1 guidance from an expert mentor. Our mentor community - the biggest strength of our programs - comprises some of the best cybersecurity experts in the field.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you are as passionate about mentoring as you are about cybersecurity, and can give a few hours per week in return for an honorarium, we would love to hear from you.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Please reach out to us with any questions at mentors@springboard.com&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Program:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Completely online and self-paced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Students become proficient in cybersecurity with the help of a curated online curriculum and project-based deliverables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coursework is made up of a 360 hour expert-curated curriculum in partnership with InfoSec Learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On average, students finish in 6 months; spending 15-20 per week on the course&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Students are working professionals from all over the world, dedicated to switching careers into cybersecurity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Students have a weekly 30-minute check-in with their mentor to discuss questions, projects, and career advice!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Students may communicate with mentors outside of calls on an as-needed basis to support learning and career objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In addition to the mentors, students have a strong support network including full-time TAs, career coaches, unlimited mentors, a student advisor and a technical community manager&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are as passionate about explaining principles of cybersecurity as about cybersecurity itself&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in the topics covered in our curriculum and are an expert on incident response, network scanning tools, vulnerability assessments, Kali Linux, and pCAP and log analysis, as well as basic Python and Powershell scripting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with cybersecurity related tools/technologies that we use including WireShark, Nessus, Nmap/Kali Linux, Splunk, Snort, Pfense, Aircrack, Cain and Abel, Virtual Box, Hashcat, Webgoat and Linux&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have at least 3+ years of relevant work experience &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold current CISSP certificate; additional industry certifications from Cisco, Microsoft, CompTIA Security+, EC-Council, SANS are preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are available for weekly, 30-minute video check-ins for each student to help them set and achieve learning goals, provide feedback, and help them move towards getting a job&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to spend up to an additional 30-minutes per call to review student submissions before the weekly call and prepare feedback to share with each student during the call&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have experience critiquing work, in particular giving meaningful feedback on cybersecurity related work, and are able to think on your feet quickly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are empathetic, patient, have excellent communication skills, and can hold other accountable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cybersecurity mentors are paid an honorarium between $16.50-$30.00 per 30 minute call with students&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Membership in a rich community of expert mentors from companies like Apple, Microsoft, and Google&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Change the lives of students in our program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help revolutionize online education and inspire the next generation of cybersecurity professionals!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work at your convenience: set your own working hours and workload&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are an equal opportunity employer and value diversity at our company. We welcome applications from all backgrounds, and do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/springboard-mentor-cyber-security-career-track-part-time-remote-2"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/springboard-mentor-cyber-security-career-track-part-time-remote-2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 18:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 18:56:05 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/springboard-mentor-cyber-security-career-track-part-time-remote-2</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/springboard-mentor-cyber-security-career-track-part-time-remote-2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toggl: QA Architect</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Tallinn, Estonia
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://toggl.com/jobs/"&gt;https://toggl.com/jobs/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We’re looking for a QA expert willing to lead efforts to enable improved speed and quality of delivery of the Toggl Track teams. We’re looking for someone to identify problem areas and implement innovative processes, tools and methods in a way that scales well with the growth of our company for years to come.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; looking to build a QA team of testers that manually test software, but rather focus on automation and processes for existing teams to improve their workflows. As such, this role will primarily focus on the planning, strategising and mentoring aspects.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Gross annual compensation for the role is €73,000 and we are committed to increasing salaries every year based on company and individual performance. In addition to that, we also have awesome benefits, which you can check out below.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You can work from anywhere in the world. However, since our team meetings typically happen between 11:00 and 15:00 UTC, you need to be willing and available to attend these meetings when they happen.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;About the Team&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are a global team of 100+ awesome people working from over 40 countries around the globe. We hire globally, you work locally—in the heart of London, a beach outside of São Paulo, or a quiet village near Florence, the choice is yours. Every few months we travel to meet up somewhere in the world and spend some quality time together. We place a huge amount of trust in our people, and we measure the outcomes rather than the work itself. Our values fuel our results.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Our Engineering Department consists of 3 platform teams, 5 product development teams and 4 app teams. The product teams are cross-functional teams that work on product features, while the platform teams specialise in building up the building blocks for the other teams.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;About the Role&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The responsibilities of this role:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively work with engineering teams, leaders and product managers to identify risks and other quality problems and discover ways of addressing them;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with engineering leaders to develop a quality strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish strong QA processes across multiple engineering teams;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overseeing the implementation and integration of automated test solutions in the development process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish and monitor metrics to measure effectiveness of QA;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensuring sustainable stability of a continuously evolving product;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentor developers to improve their QA practices and to build product quality awareness;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help in finding and enabling an effective combination of quality and speed of development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish work processes to ensure proper product quality without a significant decrease in the lead time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Here are some of the technologies we work with:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Go, PostgreSQL, Javascript/TypeScript and React, Android (Kotlin), iOS/macOS (Swift), Windows (C#) and some remains of Ruby&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google Cloud, Google Pub/Sub, Nginx, Github, Github Actions, Bitrise, Grafana&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;About You&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;We’re looking for you if you have:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A proactive stance and show ownership;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent problem solving skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Forward-thinking and the ability to strategise about future scaling of the product and it’s platform;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eye for details;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant experience leading, managing or developing QA efforts;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of different QA strategies and when to employ them, based on teams’ specific situations and company goals;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in building reliable automated tests solutions for mobile, desktop, and web applications;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to communicate QA concepts effectively;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to coach and support other developers to adopt these QA concepts;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organisational and planning skills to coordinate work with stakeholders and across multiple teams;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of web technologies, server-client architectures and modern CI/CD pipelines with fast delivery cycles;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;You’ll score some extra points with us if you have experience with:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working in a SaaS-based company;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Toggl products;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;QA for multi-tiered backend systems, mobile, desktop and web application&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;24 days of paid time off a year, plus your local holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-person meetups for team-building (expenses covered)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-6 weeks paid sabbatical (depending on the tenure of the employee)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Laptop reimbursement up to €2,500 and a €2,000 budget to set up your home office&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reimbursement for co-working space membership or internet service at home&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;€4,000 contribution per year for training, workshops, and conferences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health (physical and mental) budget of €2,000 per year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support for buying tools you need for doing your best work (even eyeglasses if you need a new pair)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/toggl-qa-architect"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/toggl-qa-architect&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 14:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 14:27:53 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/toggl-qa-architect</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/toggl-qa-architect</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0074/2934/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Ebury: Senior Site Reliability Engineer - (Remote, South America)</title>
      <region>Latin America Only</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0074/2934/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Remote
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://ebury.com"&gt;https://ebury.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Are you ready to join us?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you are an SRE and you want to move forward with your professional career in an international and dynamic environment, this job is for you!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You will be joining our SRE team to focus on site reliability of our Finance and Foreign Exchange platform, specifically looking to further decouple our application deployment and infrastructure. We are mainly in AWS, and we are actively migrating to EKS and implementing Kafka. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Candidate required skills:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Several years of relevant industry experience building large scale distributed systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience operating web-scale deployments of containerised systems on Kubernetes and Amazon Container Services.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A deep understanding of programming languages and the systems you've worked on.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A passion for architecting large systems with elegant interfaces that can scale easily&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A hunger for tracking down root causes, no matter where it takes you and fixing them in systematic ways. Working with code owners to prevent repeats.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A love for writing code - we use Python; you don’t need to be an expert, but the experience is a plus and we will expect you to learn on the job.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and interpersonal communication skills and willingness to uphold Eburys values.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our operating language is English but a knowledge of Spanish or Portuguese is a bonus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;More reasons to join us?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being part of a remote-first distributed technology team that cares deeply about culture and best practices, and believes in agile principles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clear career progression framework with regular reviews.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continued personal development through training and certification.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to our technical design through our open and collaborative Request For Comments (RFC) process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in one of the most disruptive sectors in the tech industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are Open Source friendly, following Open Source principles in our internal projects and encouraging contributions to external projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possibility to participate in conferences for your own professional growth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;We believe in inclusion. We stand against discrimination in all forms and have no tolerance for the intolerance of differences that makes us a modern and successful organisation. At Ebury, you can be whoever you want to be and still feel a sense of belonging no matter your story because we want you and your uniqueness to help write our future.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/ebury-senior-site-reliability-engineer-remote-south-america"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/ebury-senior-site-reliability-engineer-remote-south-america&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 12:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 12:47:52 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/ebury-senior-site-reliability-engineer-remote-south-america</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/ebury-senior-site-reliability-engineer-remote-south-america</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0071/3345/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>The Scale Factory: AWS Consultant</title>
      <region>Europe Only</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0071/3345/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; London, UK
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://scalefactory.com/"&gt;https://scalefactory.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Find full details about this role, and The Scale Factory &lt;a href="https://scalefactory.com/about/careers/open-roles/aws-consultant/"&gt;on our website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every day, we help teams deliver business value on the AWS cloud. We work with customers across a number of sectors, including e-commerce, media, healthcare, and fintech. The infrastructures we work with support millions of pounds of transactions every month.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Working with other Scale Factory colleagues, you’ll help our B2B SaaS customers build and operate their cloud solutions, working with their engineers to put together a foundation of good DevOps &amp;amp; SRE practise, helping them move faster, maintain uptime, and keep their secrets safe and secure.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Most of our customers are currently based in the UK, but this role is open to international applicants from &lt;a href="https://scalefactory.com/about/careers/international/"&gt;selected other countries&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;In this role you will:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with customers, understanding their business requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build client relationships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review infrastructure and processes against AWS' frameworks and our own&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help to identify new sales opportunities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide recommendations and guidance on good infrastructure and DevOps practice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coach and teach customers' staff, and Scale Factory colleagues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get hands-on with implementation either solo or as part of a small delivery team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;This isn’t the role for you if you’re not interested in investing in communication skills, or if you want to hide away from other people, cutting Terraform code and tuning RDS parameters (although we still do plenty of that). But if you’re friendly, curious, and collaborative, you’ll do well here.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Here are some of the benefits of &lt;a href="https://scalefactory.com/about/careers/working-with-us/"&gt;working with us&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re friendly and inclusive, so if you have the skills and the experience, please apply no matter your age, gender, race, sexuality, religion, or physical ability.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/the-scale-factory-aws-consultant"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/the-scale-factory-aws-consultant&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 16:23:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 16:23:48 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/the-scale-factory-aws-consultant</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/the-scale-factory-aws-consultant</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0067/0059/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Swimlane: Site Reliability Engineer (SRE)</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0067/0059/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Louisville, CO
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.swimlane.com"&gt;https://www.swimlane.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Swimlane is a rapidly growing, innovative startup with a passionate team focused on improving the lives of IT security practitioners through security automation and orchestration. At Swimlane, we work with a cutting-edge technology stack to create and distribute products that empower Security Operations teams to automate time-consuming and repetitive tasks, allowing them to focus on the advanced security activities that are most important to their work. We’re headquartered in the Denver, CO metro area, but our employees span 23 states and 6 countries. We offer competitive salaries and benefits, along with a community-based culture of transparency and innovation. Become a Swimlaner today!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a &lt;strong&gt;Site Reliability Engineer&lt;/strong&gt; on our team, you will help design, build, maintain, and scale our new greenfield SaaS platform. As a believer of our DevOps practices, you will continue to automate all aspects of our software deployment and product delivery processes. You will report to our Infrastructure Manager and be fully remote.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Additionally, in this Site Reliability Engineer position, you will:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help design, manage, and support our new SaaS platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build and manage highly reliable, redundant, secure, and scalable customer-facing infrastructure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, manage, and maintain tools to automate operational processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use monitoring tools to find problems, resolve and/or escalate to development and ensure that we exceed our SLAs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with the development and QA team throughout the technology stack&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in a 24/7 on-call rotation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with other developers, testers, and system engineers to ensure quality product enhancements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimize like crazy; squeeze every bit of performance out of our servers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Automate everything!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WE OFFER&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;In order for you to take care of yourself both professionally and personally, we offer a total rewards package that includes a number of great benefits, including:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, dental and vision coverage paid by Company at 100% for employee &amp;amp; 50% for dependents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) plan participation with 3% Company safe harbor contribution &amp;amp; 100% immediate vesting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited PTO &amp;amp; 11 Company paid holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company paid short-term disability, long-term disability, basic life insurance, and AD&amp;amp;D&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health Savings Account (HSA) for eligible plan participants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company sponsored training &amp;amp; professional development opportunities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;Here at Swimlane, we strive to represent our five core values in all things we do:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Punch above our weight class - surprising people that we accomplished what we did with what we have&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be happy innovators - accomplishing hard things together in a fun, creative way and high five-ing at the end!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have honesty and integrity in all things - We make decisions with the best of intentions that are right for as many stakeholders as possible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always be leveling up - continuously improving, embracing change, and consuming information to solve those really hard problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Move at the speed of WOW - working with a sense of urgency that doesn’t compromise quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;Requirements&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our ideal Site Reliability Engineer will have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience supporting a SaaS platform as Infrastructure As Code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building and using blue/green or canary deployment strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A security-first mindset when building infrastructure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building and scaling Amazon EKS clusters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience deploying highly available applications with Kubernetes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with monitoring and alerting solutions such as Prometheus and Grafana&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Likes to code, seeking someone with development competency, ideally Python, Javascript, or C#&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of JIRA, Confluence, Docker, and Github&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communication, presentation and collaborative problem-solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good analytical and organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team player who has a strong desire to never do the same manual task twice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to think proactively and work independently to accomplish goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated and able to manage multiple tasks simultaneously&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To be considered for this Site Reliability Engineer role, you must have: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Information Science, Mathematics, or comparable or relevant work experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of work experience in an SRE or Infrastructure Engineer role, preferably in a fast-paced web application environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Smart, friendly, gets stuff done&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in supporting a SaaS infrastructure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and interest in hardware and systems; you like the nitty-gritty of web application delivery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of TCP/IP, HTTP, TLS, load balancing, DNS, and every step of how a web request gets from the server to the browser&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building critical production infrastructure with Infrastructure as Code tools such as terraform, pulumi, or CloudFormation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands-on experience with AWS, Google Cloud or MS Azure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong propensity for documentation and knowledge sharing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intensely driven and proactive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to learn quickly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great team and business communication skills; project management communication ability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/swimlane-site-reliability-engineer-sre"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/swimlane-site-reliability-engineer-sre&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 15:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 15:09:16 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/swimlane-site-reliability-engineer-sre</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/swimlane-site-reliability-engineer-sre</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doximity: Data Integration Engineer</title>
      <region>North America Only</region>
      <category>DevOps and Sysadmin</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; San Francisco, CA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.doximity.com"&gt;http://www.doximity.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Doximity is transforming the healthcare industry. Our mission is to help doctors save time so they can provide better care for patients. We value diversity — in backgrounds and experiences. Healthcare is a universal concern, and we need people from all backgrounds to help build the future of healthcare.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;One of Doximity's &lt;a href="https://work.doximity.com/"&gt;core values&lt;/a&gt; is stretching ourselves. Even if you don't check off all the boxes below we encourage you to apply. Doximity is full of exceptional people that don't fit a mold, join us!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Data engineers on our data integration team are responsible for many of our foundational datasets powering our user-facing products. They collaborate with a variety of teams across the organization to shepherd data products in the right direction. Ultimately, data engineers on the data integration team take great interest in understanding how our data impacts our products - to drive the team's data endeavors in directions that directly improve our products.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;This role can be filled in our San Francisco headquarters OR remotely in the U.S.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;How you’ll make an impact&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with product managers and data engineers to develop data pipelines with the goal of creating or improving products through the use of our data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gain an understanding of Doximity’s data and proactively identify places where unused data can be integrated to add value&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define how data should be structured to provide maximum value to downstream consumers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build, maintain, and scale data pipelines that empower Doximity’s products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish data architecture processes and practices that can be scheduled, automated, replicated and serve as standards for other teams to leverage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work alongside others in planning and carrying out the implementation of solutions that are focused on enhancing products, leading one or two projects at any given time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What we’re looking for&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have professional data engineering or operations experience with a focus on data pipelines and the data within those pipelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are fluent in Python and SQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;You have an interest in spending time understanding how our user-facing products operate to help find novel ways to create value from our date&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;You are no stranger to data warehousing (we use Snowflake) and designing data models&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are familiar with different types of data structures and what they mean for the data stored within them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are foremost an engineer, making you passionate about high code quality, automated testing, and engineering best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have the ability to self-manage, prioritize, and deliver functional solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You agree that concise and effective written and verbal communication is a must for a successful team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why you want to work here/Benefits/Perks&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;“Doximity is proud to offer industry-leading benefits. Some of our offerings include: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, dental, vision offerings for you and your family&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401k with matching program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stock Incentives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Family building support, Childcare FSA, and parental leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Life, AD&amp;amp;D, and Disability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generous time off, holidays and paid company trips&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plus many more!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;More About Doximity…&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Founded in 2010, Doximity is the leading digital platform for medical professionals. The company’s network members include over 80% of physicians across all specialties and practice areas.  Doximity provides its verified members with digital tools built for medicine, enabling them to collaborate with colleagues, stay up-to-date with the latest medical news and research, manage their careers and conduct virtual patient visits. Doximity’s mission is to help doctors be more productive so they can provide better healthcare for their patients.  For more information, please visit &lt;a href="http://www.doximity.com/"&gt;Doximity.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Joining Doximity means being part of an incredibly talented and humble team. We’re driven by the goal of improving inefficiencies in our $3.5 trillion U.S. healthcare system and love creating technology that has a real, meaningful impact on people’s lives. To learn more about our team, culture, and users, check out our &lt;a href="https://workat.doximity.com/"&gt;careers page&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://blog.doximity.com/"&gt;company blog&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://engineering.doximity.com/"&gt;engineering blog&lt;/a&gt;. We’re growing fast, and there’s plenty of opportunity for you to make an impact—join us!"&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doximity is proud to be an equal opportunity employer, and committed to providing employment opportunities regardless of race, religious creed, color, national origin, ancestry, physical disability, mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, marital status, sex, gender, gender identity, gender expression, pregnancy, childbirth and breastfeeding, age, sexual orientation, military or veteran status, or any other protected classification. We also consider qualified applicants with criminal histories, consistent with applicable federal, state and local law.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/doximity-data-integration-engineer-1"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/doximity-data-integration-engineer-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 19:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 19:06:33 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/doximity-data-integration-engineer-1</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/doximity-data-integration-engineer-1</link>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
