<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss">
  <channel>
    <title>We Work Remotely: Remote jobs in design, programming, marketing and more</title>
    <link>https://weworkremotely.com/categories/remote-programming-jobs.rss</link>
    <description>We Work Remotely: Remote jobs in design, programming, marketing and more</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/8163/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Madeo: Web Developer (Drupal or Wordpress)</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Full-Stack Programming</category>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/8163/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Brooklyn, NY
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://madeostudio.com/"&gt;https://madeostudio.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Web Developer&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Full Time&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Madeo is a digital creative agency with a focus on social impact. We are an inclusive and diverse team of strategists, designers, and engineers. We value mission-driven work that relies on empathy, analytical thinking, and collaboration.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of our clients include Innocence Project, the Equal Justice Initiative, STOP Tobacco, Echoing Green, AFSC, and Girls Leadership.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience developing websites in Drupal or WordPress.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience with version control Git and REST API integrations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong written and verbal communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest in working directly with clients via zoom, Email, and slack to plan, scope, investigate issues and address questions on behalf of more engineers on the team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strong plus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with developing websites in both WordPress (Gutenberg) and Drupal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with configuring and deploying websites in Amazon AWS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Salesforce API integration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest in technical research and advancement of the field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your role &amp;amp; responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are a remote-first collaborative team that invests heavily in learning, career development, and supporting one another. Depending on your level of expertise, you may support or lead some of these responsibilities in collaboration with other Madeo engineers, designers, strategists, and project managers:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with 6+ engineers and other team members on researching and scoping client requirements for new website projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Investigate and test content migration from the client’s existing CMS to the new website’s decided CMS and version&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with other team members on defining CMS features for a client website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and integrate static (front-end) pages and features with the CMS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrate defined third-party API tools with the website (e.g. Mailchimp, Salesforce, Formstack..etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Carry out initial Quality Assurance testing for your own work and others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to CMS and technical documentation for client teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help deploy the new website within the client hosting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take the lead on post-launch support requests, working with other engineers on resolving reported issues, carrying out updates and improvements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in team-wide side projects, research initiatives, and learning opportunities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A work culture that supports collaboration, learning, and growth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% remote work supported with office available only as a resource&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible and generous vacation and personal days in addition to national holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discretionary annual bonuses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please see the application for additional salary and benefit information &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/madeo-web-developer-drupal-or-wordpress"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/madeo-web-developer-drupal-or-wordpress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 18:10:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/madeo-web-developer-drupal-or-wordpress</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/madeo-web-developer-drupal-or-wordpress</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fleetio: Senior Ruby on Rails Engineer</title>
      <region>North America Only</region>
      <category>Full-Stack Programming</category>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Birmingham, Alabama
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://fleetio.com"&gt;https://fleetio.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;We are looking for a product-minded and team-oriented Senior Software Engineer with passion and experience in solving business problems with good design, delightful UX, and scalable architecture.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is a remote opportunity and is open to candidates in the United States, Canada, or Mexico. If you reside in Mexico, please check out our job description &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://apply.workable.com/fleetio/j/5C825BBCF0/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;here.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;About us&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Fleetio is a modern software platform that helps thousands of organizations around the world manage their fleets. You can learn more about our platform &lt;a href="https://www.fleetio.com/features/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Transportation technology is a hot market and we’re leading the charge, with raving fans and new customers signing up every day. We raised a $21M Series B in late 2020 and are on an exciting trajectory as a company.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More about Fleetio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fleetio overview video: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IlvIbwZT3oU"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IlvIbwZT3oU&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fleetio Go overview video: &lt;a href="https://www.fleetio.com/go"&gt;https://www.fleetio.com/go&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More about the Fleetio platform: &lt;a href="https://www.fleetio.com/features"&gt;https://www.fleetio.com/features&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;API docs: &lt;a href="https://developer.fleetio.com/"&gt;developer.fleetio.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Test drive Fleetio to get an even better feel for what we're building: &lt;a href="https://www.fleetio.com/register"&gt;https://www.fleetio.com/register&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;What you'll be doing&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You’ll work closely with Product Managers, Designers, and other engineers to plan, design, and implement features in the core areas of our platform. You will collaboratively design and architect features, refactor as necessary and write elegant and performant code. You’ll have a strong voice in the development and planning processes, so senior-level experience is key.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What's in it for you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a part of an incredible team of “A” players who go above and beyond to make Fleetio a successful company. You will build software used by people all around the world. So many different types of companies and organizations operate a fleet each day, and Fleetio is a good fit for most of them (it’s a huge market).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work remotely (within the United States, Canada, or Mexico), or at our Birmingham, AL HQ. Over 80% of our Engineering Team works remotely (including our CTO), and we have promoted a strong remote working culture since the beginning (2012).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We place great emphasis on work/life balance. We have families and hobbies and know you do, too.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Our team&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our Engineering and Product teams are structured as autonomous squads that execute within one focal area toward a defined product vision. We're hardcore believers in easy-to-use software, and our main goal as Product Engineers is to quickly and continuously deliver meaningful value to our customers. We've optimized our CI/CD tools and processes to easily get code into our production environments, resulting in an average of 40 deploys per week. See what our team has to say about how we work in their own words &lt;a href="https://www.fleetio.com/careers/engineering#video"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. You can also learn about the interview process &lt;a href="https://www.fleetio.com/careers/engineering#process"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience with Ruby on Rails&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience solving challenging architecture problems with good design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience scaling fast-growing software products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of object-oriented programming and relational databases, such as PostgreSQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with data modeling and optimizing query performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with modern JavaScript/ES6+&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with unit testing frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills (particularly written)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be sure to mention "coffee" in your application so we know you read this&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Considered a plus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience onboarding and coaching other engineers on a team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with ReactJS, TypeScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Tailwind or CSS-in-JS frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You know a thing or two about the Fleet management industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% health/dental coverage (50% coverage for family)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vision insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Incentive stock options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) match of 4%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PTO - 4 weeks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8 company holidays + 2 floating holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parental and bonding leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dependent care and medical FSA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Short and long term disability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Community service funds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional development funds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health and wellness initiatives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mac laptop + new hire equipment stipend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monthly catered lunches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully stocked kitchen with tons of drinks &amp;amp; snacks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote working friendly since 2012&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;For Non-U.S. based candidates, Fleetio offers a country-specific competitive benefits package. If you reside in Mexico, those benefits are called out &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://apply.workable.com/fleetio/j/E025910910/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://apply.workable.com/fleetio/j/774C8B5121/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Not quite what you were hoping for? Check out our other engineering roles &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.fleetio.com/careers/engineering#jobs"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/fleetio-senior-ruby-on-rails-engineer-1"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/fleetio-senior-ruby-on-rails-engineer-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 15:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/fleetio-senior-ruby-on-rails-engineer-1</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/fleetio-senior-ruby-on-rails-engineer-1</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kinsta: Senior JavaScript Developer</title>
      <region>Europe Only</region>
      <category>Back-End Programming</category>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; West Hollywood
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://kinsta.com/"&gt;https://kinsta.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;At Kinsta we aim to create truly effective solutions for our customers and internal teams. We believe the only way to maintain and scale our standards is to focus on quality code. We are looking for a seasoned senior JavaScript developer who wants to work with a 100% remote,  globally distributed company. We work with an ownership-embracing, highly skilled team in a relaxed environment where culture is as important as technical excellence. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As part of our JS Development Team, you will be working with some of the most exciting JavaScript tools on the market to build our client-facing and internal tools.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our Stack:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;TypeScript, React, Node.js, GraphQL, SQL, NoSQL, Webpack, Babel, SWC, Jest, Storybook, GitHub, Docker, Stripe&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities and Challenges:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will be tasked with contributing to and eventually leading a diverse set of projects that immediately impact our customers' experience, our internal teams' day-to-day, and thus our business as a whole.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We rely heavily on communication between all team members, regardless of team or department lines. As a Kinsta developer, you will be communicating with the Design, QA, Marketing, and Support teams to provide and solicit feedback.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We strive to implement a bottom-up approach, hand in hand with an ownership mentality. Our goal is to give each developer as much freedom as possible with the capacity, knowledge, and willingness to make decisions that matter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We implement a robust review process to ship quality code. All developers are expected to participate in code reviews to ensure accountability and stability, share knowledge, and learn from peers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;About You:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a minimum of 5 years of hands-on experience with JavaScript, including backend and frontend.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced with backend-focused JS (e.g., Node.js, Express).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced with React or other modern frontend frameworks (eg: Vue, Angular, Svelte).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced with modern JS/TS tools (Babel, SWC, esbuild, current ES standards).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced with statically typed languages or typing tools for JS (Typescript, Flow, Elm).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced with databases (SQL or NoSQL).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced with git and team collaboration via pull requests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced with JS testing frameworks (Jest, Mocha).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced with frontend build tools (Webpack, Rollup, Vite).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bonus points:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with web hosting, server infrastructure, or server management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Cloudflare and its API.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth experience with the Stripe API.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Benefits:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We have a fully remote culture with a globally distributed, international team. You can work anywhere with appropriate internet access.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To ensure that everyone has time to rest and recharge, we offer Flexible paid time off.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We offer flexibility with work hours. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote expense budget and personal career development budget.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Due to the ownership mentality, developers participate in projects from conception to deployment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Everyone has a voice in the development process, and we welcome ideas, thoughts, and constructive criticism.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We have an amazing product design (UX and UI) team, and tasks are thoroughly researched and designed before development begins.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/kinsta-senior-javascript-developer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/kinsta-senior-javascript-developer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 14:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/kinsta-senior-javascript-developer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/kinsta-senior-javascript-developer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SystemOne, LLC: Windows Forms (C#) Engineer (REMOTE)</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Full-Stack Programming</category>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Northampton, Massachusetts, USA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://systemone.id/"&gt;https://systemone.id/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;SystemOne is searching for a Windows Forms developer to build &amp;amp; maintain new and
&lt;br&gt;existing client applications targeting Windows 7 &amp;amp; Windows 10.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;As an Applicant You are Expected to Have:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br&gt;● At least two years of professional software development experience building, deploying, and maintaining Windows forms applications.
&lt;br&gt;● Proficiency with HTTP client libraries, TLS, SQLite, MS SQL Server.
&lt;br&gt;● Experience with error &amp;amp; crash reporting frameworks used by Windows client applications.
&lt;br&gt;● Experience with .NET data encryption libraries.
&lt;br&gt;● Ability to work &amp;amp; communicate with the team in English.
&lt;br&gt;● Experience building setup packages for Windows applications.
&lt;br&gt;● Experience in setting up the infrastructure required to publish over-the-air updates to Windows applications.
&lt;br&gt;● Experience using Git for source code control.
&lt;br&gt;● Experience writing unit tests in C#.
&lt;br&gt;● Familiar with debugging tools and methods.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br&gt;● Design small footprint client side applications that are targeted at PCs running Windows 7 &amp;amp; Windows 10.
&lt;br&gt;● Deploy updates and installation packages for Windows applications.
&lt;br&gt;● Troubleshoot installation and runtime issues that are reported from remote locations.
&lt;br&gt;● Optimise HTTPs requests made from Windows applications.
&lt;br&gt;● Build data upload workflows that are tolerant to partitions in the network.
&lt;br&gt;● Collect error and crash logs from a fleet of remote Windows PCs and monitor overall fleet health.
&lt;br&gt;● Make strategic technical decisions that cater for system flexibility through safe updates and configuration changes.
&lt;br&gt;● Write unit tests that integrate into deployment pipelines.
&lt;br&gt;● Collaborate with an excellent team of engineers to produce high quality, performant &amp;amp; secure information exchange back-ends for healthcare initiatives.
&lt;br&gt;● Document APIs and expected system behaviour.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/systemone-llc-windows-forms-c-engineer-remote"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/systemone-llc-windows-forms-c-engineer-remote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 11:32:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/systemone-llc-windows-forms-c-engineer-remote</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/systemone-llc-windows-forms-c-engineer-remote</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SystemOne, LLC: NodeJS and Python Software Engineer (REMOTE)</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Full-Stack Programming</category>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Northampton, Massachusetts, USA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://systemone.id/"&gt;https://systemone.id/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;SystemOne is searching for a software developer to build &amp;amp; maintain new and existing client &lt;br&gt;applications built using Python &amp;amp; Node.js targeting Raspberry Pi.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;As an Applicant You are Expected to Have:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;● At least two years of professional software development experience building, deploying, and maintaining Python applications. &lt;br&gt;● At least two years of professional software development experience building, deploying, and maintaining Node.js applications. &lt;br&gt;● Proficiency with HTTP client libraries, TLS &amp;amp; SQLite. &lt;br&gt;● Some experience working with serial comm devices from a linux platform . &lt;br&gt;● Ability to work &amp;amp; communicate with the team in English. &lt;br&gt;● Experience building deb packages for distribution &amp;amp; installation of software on remote linux computers. &lt;br&gt;● Experience in setting up the infrastructure required to publish over-the-air updates to debian applications. &lt;br&gt;● Experience using Git for source code control. &lt;br&gt;● Experience writing unit tests in JavaScript &amp;amp; Python. &lt;br&gt;● Familiar with debugging tools and methods.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;● Design client side applications that are targeted at Raspberry Pi devices. &lt;br&gt;● Deploy updates and installation packages for applications running on Raspberry Pi devices. &lt;br&gt;● Troubleshoot installation and runtime issues that are reported from remote locations. &lt;br&gt;● Optimise HTTPs requests made from Raspberry Pi applications. &lt;br&gt;● Build data upload workflows that are tolerant to partitions in the network. &lt;br&gt;● Collect error and crash logs from a fleet of remote devices and monitor overall fleet health. &lt;br&gt;● Make strategic technical decisions that cater for system flexibility through safe updates and configuration changes. &lt;br&gt;● Write unit tests that integrate into deployment pipelines. &lt;br&gt;● Collaborate with an excellent team of engineers to produce high quality, performant &amp;amp; secure information exchange back-ends for healthcare initiatives. &lt;br&gt;● Document APIs and expected system behaviour.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/systemone-llc-nodejs-and-python-software-engineer-remote"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/systemone-llc-nodejs-and-python-software-engineer-remote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 10:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/systemone-llc-nodejs-and-python-software-engineer-remote</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/systemone-llc-nodejs-and-python-software-engineer-remote</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0017/2428/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Optimile: Back End Developer E-Mobility (remote - EU)</title>
      <region>Europe Only</region>
      <category>Back-End Programming</category>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0017/2428/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Ghent, Belgium
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.optimile.eu/"&gt;https://www.optimile.eu/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are you interested in E-Mobility and are you also looking for a job in which your technical knowledge comes to its full advantage? Optimile is looking for a back-end software developer for our Charge Point Operator (CPO) &amp;amp; Mobility Service Provider (MSP) platform development.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Optimile is a software company offering Mobility as a Service (MaaS) and Charging as a Service (CaaS), by combining all the mobility solutions in one app. Optimile delivers scalable software platforms to professional customers worldwide.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Optimile creates an innovative product in a new market within an international context. Not only do we develop charging software (such as white label platforms &amp;amp; applications) for external parties, we also have our own brand ‘Mobiflow’.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;You'll work (remotely) on our system of networked mobility. Our platform creates a connection between different mobility services and users, and is responsible for managing various charging points for electric vehicles.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a thorough experience with Python, Django and Java.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have an understanding of React Native.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with pull requests, code reviews and unit testing are basics for you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are passionate about developing and expanding back-end systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working in a team doesn’t scare you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have the ability to take responsibility and work independently.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You speak fluently English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Living in Europe is a must.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What will you be doing?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You'll be contributing to the further development of our Charging as a Service platform (CPO/MSP) for electric vehicles and the integration of various mobility platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Setting up roaming connections with other 'Charging Station Operators'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Setting up interoperability integrations with 'Charging Stations Manufacturers'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Offering technical support in the backend system for charging stations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/optimile-back-end-developer-e-mobility-remote-eu"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/optimile-back-end-developer-e-mobility-remote-eu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 09:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/optimile-back-end-developer-e-mobility-remote-eu</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/optimile-back-end-developer-e-mobility-remote-eu</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0018/4201/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Aurora Solar: Senior Software Engineer, Backend (Remote)</title>
      <region>North America Only</region>
      <category>Back-End Programming</category>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0018/4201/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; San Francisco, CA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.aurorasolar.com"&gt;https://www.aurorasolar.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Aurora Solar is a fast-growing Series C company on a mission to create a future of solar energy for all. Aurora makes the software that is enabling society to transition to a world powered by solar power. It’s our goal to have every solar installation in the world pass through our software, which has already been used to design millions of solar projects. Named one of “The Best Places To Work in 2021” by &lt;a href="https://www.builtinsf.com/company/aurora-solar"&gt;BuiltInSF.com&lt;/a&gt; and awarded #1 Solar Software platform by Solar Power World, Aurora is disrupting the energy industry and changing the course of history.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are looking for senior backend engineers who are comfortable taking control of complex projects and working with other members of the team. Every engineer contributes to key feature rollouts and cutting-edge technology of the solar industry.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are a diverse team based in San Francisco, passionate about advancing the growth of solar energy. If you are looking for a stimulating and fulfilling role, come join us!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What you'll do:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build new functionality and features for our software platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scale Aurora's infrastructure by 10x over the next year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and extend our existing API&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build integrations with other players in the solar industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What we value:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A degree in Computer Science or related fields&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4+ years of experience as a software engineer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing backend web systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing databases (PostgreSQL preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience integrating with third-party APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with (or eagerness to learn) Ruby on Rails&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Git or other version control systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for renewable energy and sustainability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to perform and thrive in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Thank you for your interest in Aurora Solar. Currently our interview process is taking longer than usual as we navigate the new normal of COVID-19. We appreciate your patience and look forward to speaking with you soon.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Aurora is dedicated to building a diverse and inclusive workforce of people who believe in and are passionate about creating a future of solar energy for all. We are an equal opportunity employer, we welcome and consider qualified applicants regardless of gender identity, sexual orientation, race, religion, age, national origin, citizenship, pregnancy status, veteran status, or any other differences. We encourage you to apply even if you feel that you do not meet all of the above criteria!&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aurora-solar-senior-software-engineer-backend-remote-2"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aurora-solar-senior-software-engineer-backend-remote-2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 20:29:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aurora-solar-senior-software-engineer-backend-remote-2</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aurora-solar-senior-software-engineer-backend-remote-2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0018/4200/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Aurora Solar: Software Engineer, Frontend (Remote)</title>
      <region>North America Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0018/4200/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; San Francisco, CA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.aurorasolar.com"&gt;https://www.aurorasolar.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Aurora Solar is a fast-growing Series C company on a mission to create a future of solar energy for all. Aurora makes the software that is enabling society to transition to a world powered by solar power. It’s our goal to have every solar installation in the world pass through our software, which has already been used to design millions of solar projects. Named one of “The Best Places To Work in 2021” by &lt;a href="https://www.builtinsf.com/company/aurora-solar"&gt;BuiltInSF.com&lt;/a&gt; and awarded #1 Solar Software platform by Solar Power World, Aurora is disrupting the energy industry and changing the course of history. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are looking for a frontend software engineer who will help take our cloud-based solar design software, which is used by thousands of solar companies worldwide, to the next level of functionality and interactivity. If you are interested in bringing cutting-edge design methods to a fast-growing solar industry and want to help society transition to a more sustainable future, we would love to hear from you!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are a diverse team based in San Francisco, passionate about advancing the growth of solar energy. If you are looking for a stimulating and fulfilling role, come join us!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What you'll do:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build new functionality for our industry-leading solar design platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spearhead the development of new greenfield products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write high quality, well-tested code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement, guide, and influence Aurora Solar’s front-end engineering practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What we value:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of experience building maintainable, clean, and well-tested user-facing code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Love writing Javascript or TypeScript (React, Redux, Styled Components experience a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great engineering skills and strong computer science fundamentals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent teamwork and communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thoughtful balance between shipping code quickly and adhering to best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to perform and thrive in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with full-stack development is a bonus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Thank you for your interest in Aurora Solar. Currently, our interview process is taking longer than usual as we navigate the new normal of COVID-19. We appreciate your patience and look forward to speaking with you soon.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Aurora is dedicated to building a diverse and inclusive workforce of people who believe in and are passionate about creating a future of solar energy for all. We are an equal opportunity employer, we welcome and consider qualified applicants regardless of gender identity, sexual orientation, race, religion, age, national origin, citizenship, pregnancy status, veteran status, or any other differences. We encourage you to apply even if you feel that you do not meet all of the above criteria!&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aurora-solar-software-engineer-frontend-remote-2"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aurora-solar-software-engineer-frontend-remote-2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 20:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aurora-solar-software-engineer-frontend-remote-2</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aurora-solar-software-engineer-frontend-remote-2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Follow Up Boss: Full Stack Engineer</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Full-Stack Programming</category>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Remote
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://careers.followupboss.com"&gt;https://careers.followupboss.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;About the job&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a Full Stack Engineer at Follow Up Boss, you'll build fully-fledged platforms using a range of different technologies. You'll be involved in the entire product development lifecycle including the design, development, deployment and maintenance of new and existing features. You'll write clean and functional code on the front- and back-end. You'll collaborate closely with our engineering team to ensure system consistency and to create a great user experience. You'll write reusable and maintainable code that is secure and scales well. You'll help ensure code quality with automated and functional testing along with peer review. Ultimately, your work will have direct impact on the stability and user experience of our products.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Why would you want to work here?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re a bootstrapped, profitable company started back in April of 2011.  We're a young, ambitious company who only answers to our customers and we don’t just claim to be customer-centric - &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/followupboss/reviews"&gt;we live it&lt;/a&gt;.  We're fully remote and have been since day 1.  Here's a few more reason's we think you'll love working here - and be sure to check out &lt;a href="https://www.followupboss.com/about/"&gt;our video on how we work&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunity to have a big impact on our growth and your career&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No red tape or pointless meetings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive base salary - top 10% in US; for this position &lt;strong&gt;the range is $130K - $146K&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong benefit package including a 401k with 6% match, health/dental/vision insurance for you and our family, funding for continuing education, paid parental leave, kindle + unlimited books, home office setup, company meetups, and 20 PTO + 10 sick days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solve challenging technical problems and put your skills to the test every day. We've processed over billions of emails; per month we send nearly 3 million text messages and handle 700k+ minutes of call time for tens of thousands of active customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;See a direct impact of your work and value you created for customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide direct input on technical and non-technical decisions. Your opinion matters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;This role is for you if...&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You would describe yourself as patient, empathetic and having a good sense of humor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re independent, self-motivated and can stay efficient and productive without someone looking over your shoulder all day long&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have superb written and verbal skills (with a professional yet fun demeanor)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are based in the United States (or similar time zone) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are happy to have direct communication with customers (we are customer driven).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Your qualifications include:&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Self motivated&lt;/strong&gt; and proactive mindset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Remote work&lt;/strong&gt; experience is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Based in the USA&lt;/strong&gt;, with a quiet home office with fast internet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-5 years of experience in web development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in front end technologies, we use React, JavaScript, CSS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in back end technologies, we use PHP, Aurora MySQL, Postgres, Redis, to name a few.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of RDBMS and SQL. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient understanding of Linux.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional time management skills. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Attention to detail and commitment to quality&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Security conscious. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pragmatic decision making.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Your responsibilities will include:&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and improve our application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help fix issues with the application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn and grow as an engineer to bring value to the team and our customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;30 Day Targets&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Become familiar with our product and codebase. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pair with fellow engineers to gain knowledge about the system and how we work. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve the new hire onboarding process, by being a part of it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;60 Day Targets&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement improvements for new and existing third party integrations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement new product features and improvements that deliver value to our customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve how our product supports customers with larger teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;90 Day Targets&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement improvements to the security of our app and customer's data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in architecture improvements of critical product features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in performance improvements to our API.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Core Engineering Values&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Teamwork&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code Quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Focus and Prioritization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Customer Driven&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leadership Qualities &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Our Employment Package Includes&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;🏝 Work remotely: Live and work wherever you like!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;💰 Competitive salary: Our career framework pays in the top 10% no matter where you live.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;👩🏾‍⚕️ Insurance: Company paid health, dental &amp;amp; vision insurance for all of our team members and their families.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🍼 Family leave: generous family leave - fully paid!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;💻 Home office setup: Get a Macbook Pro + $1000 to set up your home office.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;👩🏻‍🏫 Personal development stipend: $1000 per year to focus on bettering yourself.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🤑 401(k): With 6% company match!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;✈️ Retreats: Join us for company get-togethers every year!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;☕️ Co-working stipend: Get some extra cash for a co-working space or a coffee shop work.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;📚 Free books and Kindle: Get a free Kindle and all the free books - digital and audio - you like, anytime.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;💪 Gym: Monthly stipend to keep you active and feeling good.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;☕️ Money each month to spend on caffeine.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Apply for the job&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;Do you want to join our team as our new Full Stack Engineer? Then we'd love to hear about you!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/follow-up-boss-full-stack-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/follow-up-boss-full-stack-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 18:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/follow-up-boss-full-stack-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/follow-up-boss-full-stack-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0077/5011/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Power Auctions LLC: Ruby on Rails API Engineer</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Back-End Programming</category>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0077/5011/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Washington DC
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.powerauctions.com"&gt;https://www.powerauctions.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;The Power Auctions software team works closely with the world's leading experts on auction design, implementing innovative ideas from an academic environment in real-world applications of high economic and social impact. For example, we are currently helping the government of Botswana to sell diamonds mined in the country directly to diamond dealers, for a market price determined in a fair, transparent, and efficient auction. Our team built and successfully deployed the highest revenue auction ever, an $81 billion FCC spectrum auction.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are currently looking for software developers with Ruby on Rails experience to join our team. We value true Rubyists who understand the language and know how to use it in an object-oriented manner.  All of our code is test-driven because our solutions have to be correct.  We believe in principles such as Single Responsibility, Law of Demeter, and Dependency Injection. Given the nature of our project deliveries, we are able to stay current with the latest versions of our languages and tools.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You will be collaborating with our Project Management &amp;amp; QA teams to develop new software for different auction designs and customers. You may be required to implement a set of mathematical equations or design a complex workflow.  You may also be required to interface directly with our customers to understand their requirements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Power Auctions is an Equal Opportunity Employer. We encourage candidates from underrepresented minorities to submit resumes for consideration. &lt;strong&gt;Please note&lt;/strong&gt; that this position &lt;strong&gt;does&lt;/strong&gt; require U.S. Citizenship or Permanent Residency.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4+ years of experience using Ruby on Rails and TDD&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with a Unix command line interface&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable with relational databases and SQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid oral and written English communication skills and ability to express complex ideas clearly and succinctly in writing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enthusiasm to work in a fast-paced and dynamically changing environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to multi-task&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work autonomously with minimal supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability and patience to pay attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;US Citizen or Permanent Resident&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Desired Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A degree in computer science, mathematics, science, economics, or any related mathematical field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4+ years of web development experience (HTML/CSS/JS/backend)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with rspec, minitest, and/or capybara&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with any Javascript framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Elixir&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Object-oriented design skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Database and data modeling skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with AWS and Docker&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building complex systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has or can obtain a security clearance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;What we offer&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We offer competitive salaries with annual bonus, three weeks vacation, 10 paid holidays, 401(k), medical benefits, and flexible hours. If there is something specific that helps you personally, we can usually work something out!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/power-auctions-llc-ruby-on-rails-api-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/power-auctions-llc-ruby-on-rails-api-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 18:36:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/power-auctions-llc-ruby-on-rails-api-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/power-auctions-llc-ruby-on-rails-api-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0076/4287/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Stimulus: Software engineer</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Full-Stack Programming</category>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0076/4287/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Amsterdam, NY
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.stimulus.com/"&gt;https://www.stimulus.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Stimulus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.stimulus.com/jobs/Stimulus.com"&gt;Stimulus&lt;/a&gt; is a social platform started by Sticker Mule to show what's possible if your mission is to increase human happiness.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We offer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;1. Remote work with flexible schedules&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;2. A privately owned, low-stress culture.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;3. A fun "no bullshit" work environment&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We like you to know&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;1. Docker&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;2. NextJS&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;3. React&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;4. NodeJS&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;5. GraphQL&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;6. Redis&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compensation and benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;1. Salary: $120k+ based on experience&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;2. $20,000 signing bonus&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;3. 4 weeks vacation + holidays based on your country of residence&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/stimulus-software-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/stimulus-software-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 13:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/stimulus-software-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/stimulus-software-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/6914/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Proxify AB: Senior Front-end Developer: Long-term job - 100% Remote</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/6914/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Sweden
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://career.proxify.io"&gt;http://career.proxify.io&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are searching for a Senior Front-End Developer (Angular.js/React.js). You can be a perfect candidate if you are growth-oriented, you take pleasure in your work, and you enjoy working on new ideas to develop exciting products. By joining Proxify, you will get considerable opportunities to work with leading brands and amazing startups to build their next product and growth features. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we are looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have +3 years experience with React.js/Angular.js;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You follow best practices and conventions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant experience in CI/CD and related tools;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible and able to work with minimal supervision;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upper-intermediate English level;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can communicate well with both technical and non-technical clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nice-to-have:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Timezone: CET (+/- 3 hours);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic back-end knowledge for minor back-end jobs where necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build reusable code and libraries for future use;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure the technical feasibility of UI/UX designs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transform visual designs and wireframes into working products;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accurate planning of the feature delivery;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with other team members and stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;What we offer:&lt;/strong&gt;💻 &lt;strong&gt;100% remote work&lt;/strong&gt;: Work from anywhere.👌🏻 &lt;strong&gt;Flexibility&lt;/strong&gt;: The ability to change the project to another one.💵 &lt;strong&gt;Financial growth&lt;/strong&gt;: Competitive compensation and performance-based increases.🧘🏻‍♂️ &lt;strong&gt;Freedom&lt;/strong&gt;: Very flexible working schedule.🚀 &lt;strong&gt;360 degree growth&lt;/strong&gt;: Opportunities for professional development and personal growth.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your benefits with Proxify:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Be part of Proxify community&lt;/strong&gt;: Network with like-minded and enthusiastic individuals to make a difference. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Make an impact&lt;/strong&gt;: You get the opportunity to work on the projects that inspire you and add value to your career.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Transparency&lt;/strong&gt;: Contracts with transparency in earnings and working hours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Save your time&lt;/strong&gt;: Fast and efficient hiring process to match you with the project of your preference.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Ownership: &lt;/strong&gt;Take ownership of your work and enjoy more freedom in your career.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/proxify-ab-senior-front-end-developer-long-term-job-100-remote"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/proxify-ab-senior-front-end-developer-long-term-job-100-remote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 12:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/proxify-ab-senior-front-end-developer-long-term-job-100-remote</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/proxify-ab-senior-front-end-developer-long-term-job-100-remote</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0077/5406/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Aldrin: Senior React Native Mobile Developer Web3 (Remote)</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0077/5406/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; London
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://aldrin.com"&gt;https://aldrin.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;The Role&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are looking for a Senior React Native Mobile Developer with extensive experience in designing, building, and deploying highly secure, scalable, and maintainable client-facing UI systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You will be one of the senior developers of the mobile app working closely with our designers, product owners, and backend engineers to develop and maintain high-quality mobile applications for a global audience in an extremely fast-growing industry. We work with a modern tech-stack. We use Typescript, hooks, eslint, reanimated, automated CI and deployments, etc. We work with a design system and an updated figma design.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you are extremely passionate about mobile platforms and translating code into user-friendly apps, we would like to meet you. Ultimately, you should be able to help design and build the next generation of our mobile applications that will impact and shape the financial lives of a growing audience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You will:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute code to our iOS &amp;amp; Android React Native apps from the get-go&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on integrating and collaborating with other crypto products to enrich the user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement features with the aim to provide long term stability of a highly scalable application&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing clean and reusable react native components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively contributing new ideas and innovative UX/UI patterns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Play an active role in evolving our mobile engineering practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong expertise in React Native with 5+ years of professional experience building high-quality mobile apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High-level experience with TypeScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have experience with best-in-class client-side data design and management, whether that’s experience with GraphQL/ Apollo or other such tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a passion for good design and attention to detail. You’ll collaborate with designers but undoubtedly have the opportunity to express your own design sense if desired&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Verbal fluency in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice-to-Have Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable portfolio of released applications on the App Store or the Android&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passionate about crypto markets, blockchain technology, and decentralized applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge/experience working on mobile financial applications/cryptocurrencies/wallets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Solana Web3 frameworks and technologies, especially on mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with a large codebase and detox or appium testing tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with responsive UI and debugging skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing high-performance mobile app interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors or Masters degree, preferably in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or other technical (STEM) field or an equivalent of experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote work in a dynamic, fast-growth Web3 startup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible working hours&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunity to work with a diverse, global, and passionate team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaboration with leading projects and thought leaders in the crypto space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;At Aldrin Labs, we celebrate a truly diverse and inclusive company culture and are committed to equal employment opportunity regardless of race, color, ancestry, religion, sex, national origin, sexual orientation, age, citizenship, marital status, disability, or gender identity.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aldrin-senior-react-native-mobile-developer-web3-remote-2"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aldrin-senior-react-native-mobile-developer-web3-remote-2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 10:43:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aldrin-senior-react-native-mobile-developer-web3-remote-2</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aldrin-senior-react-native-mobile-developer-web3-remote-2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doximity: Senior Software Engineer, WebDev</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Full-Stack Programming</category>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; San Francisco, CA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.doximity.com"&gt;http://www.doximity.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Doximity is transforming the &lt;a href="https://www.bizjournals.com/sanfrancisco/news/2020/07/09/telemedicine-doximity-san-francisco-video-app.html"&gt;healthcare industry&lt;/a&gt;. Our mission is to help doctors be more productive, informed, and connected. As a software engineer, you'll work within cross-functional delivery teams alongside other engineers, designers, and product managers in building software to help improve healthcare.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our &lt;a href="https://www.doximity.com/about/company#theteam"&gt;team &lt;/a&gt;brings a diverse set of technical and cultural backgrounds and we like to think pragmatically in choosing the tools most appropriate for the job at hand. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;One of Doximity's &lt;a href="https://work.doximity.com/"&gt;core values&lt;/a&gt; is stretching ourselves. Even if you don't check off all the boxes below we encourage you to apply. Doximity is full of exceptional people that don't fit a mold, join us!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This role can be filled in our San Francisco headquarters OR remotely in the U.S.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About You&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You enjoy leading software engineering projects and prioritize the iterative delivery of high-quality solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are passionate about the intersection of Product and Engineering and can help guide your team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a deep understanding of object-oriented programming language like Ruby, a web framework like Rails and a modern JavaScript framework like Vue.js&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a passion for software engineering architecture and look forward to make high-quality contributions to modern, production web application&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are self-motivated and able to manage yourself&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You default to concise and effective written and verbal communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's How You Will Make an Impact&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead technical projects alongside your team to ensure rapid and reliable delivery of software products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advance our Telemedicine platform which connects doctors and patients millions of times per month&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help build distributed systems that put clinical knowledge, secure messaging, and professional connections at a doctor’s fingertips&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Secure, cache, and optimize software systems that can handle millions of operations per day&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Benefits &amp;amp; Perks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generous time off policy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive benefits including medical, vision, dental, generous paternity and maternity leave, Life/ADD, 401k, flex spending accounts, commuter benefits, equipment budget, and continuous education budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stock incentives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;.. and much more! For a full list, see our&lt;a href="https://work.doximity.com/"&gt;career page&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;About Us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Here are &lt;a href="https://drive.google.com/open?id=1qimYh0mG3i1nTJe6jDCDepJt2i4o8MEB"&gt;some of the ways we bring&lt;/a&gt; value to doctors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our web applications are built primarily using Ruby, Rails, Javascript (Vue.js), and a bit of Golang&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our data engineering stack run on Python, MySQL, Spark, and Airflow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our production application stack is hosted on AWS and we deploy to production on average 85 times per day&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We have over 500 private repositories in Github containing our applications, forks of gems, our own internal gems, and &lt;a href="https://github.com/doximity"&gt;open-source projects&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We have worked as a distributed team for a long time;&lt;a href="https://blog.brunomiranda.com/building-a-distributed-engineering-team-85d281b9b1c"&gt; we're currently about 75%+ distributed&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Find out more information on the &lt;a href="https://engineering.doximity.com/"&gt;Doximity technology blog&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our &lt;a href="https://work.doximity.com/"&gt;company core values&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our &lt;a href="https://engineering.doximity.com/articles/engineering-recruitment-process-doximity"&gt;recruiting process&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our &lt;a href="https://engineering.doximity.com/articles/mofo-driven-product-development"&gt;product development cycle&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our &lt;a href="https://engineering.doximity.com/articles/software-engineering-on-boarding-at-doximity"&gt;on-boarding &amp;amp; mentorship process&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;For the past decade, it’s been our mission to help every physician be more productive so they can provide better care for their patients. We believe that when doctors are connected, the healthcare system works better and patients benefit. Doximity enables our verified clinician members to collaborate with colleagues, stay up-to-date with the latest medical news and research, manage their careers, and conduct virtual patient visits. Today, Doximity is the leading digital platform for U.S. medical professionals, with over 80% of physicians, 50% of all nurse practitioners and physician assistants, and 90% of graduating medical students as members. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Joining Doximity means being part of an incredibly talented and humble team passionate about improving inefficiencies in our $4.3 trillion U.S. healthcare system. We are a team of doers who solve problems everyday by treating obstacles like an adventure, and we love creating technology that has a real, meaningful impact on people’s lives. Doxers are committed to working towards a more equitable world both within and beyond our office walls. This starts by fostering an inclusive and diverse work environment where differences are valued and all employees are encouraged to bring their full, authentic selves to work daily. To learn more about our team, culture, and users, check out our &lt;a href="https://workat.doximity.com/"&gt;careers page&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://blog.doximity.com/"&gt;company blog&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://engineering.doximity.com/"&gt;engineering blog&lt;/a&gt;. We’re growing fast, and there’s plenty of opportunity for you to make an impact—join us! For more information, visit&lt;a href="http://www.doximity.com/"&gt;Doximity.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;____________________________________________&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;EEOC Statement&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doximity is proud to be an equal opportunity employer, and committed to providing employment opportunities regardless of race, religious creed, color, national origin, ancestry, physical disability, mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, marital status, sex, gender, gender identity, gender expression, pregnancy, childbirth and breastfeeding, age, sexual orientation, military or veteran status, or any other protected classification. We also consider qualified applicants with criminal histories, consistent with applicable federal, state and local law.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/doximity-senior-software-engineer-webdev"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/doximity-senior-software-engineer-webdev&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 03:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/doximity-senior-software-engineer-webdev</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/doximity-senior-software-engineer-webdev</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/6904/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Cofense: Java Software Engineer, III</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Full-Stack Programming</category>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/6904/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Washington DC
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://cofense.com"&gt;https://cofense.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;This is an excellent opportunity to develop your career working for a fast growing Cyber Security Company that is disrupting the email security market with its Phishing Defense and Response (PDR) platform.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Java Software Engineer III is responsible for wearing multiple hats from viewing the architectural approach with a critical eye, making implementation decisions, and proactively communicating this with the team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essential Duties/Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding the approach and design decisions and creating an implementation that supports overall design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with other engineers on the team, particularly more junior engineers through pair programming, open communications, and collaboration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively participate in our Agile development lifecycle, including planning and grooming, stand-up, and retrospectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively perform code reviews, give feedback, and ask questions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively participate on one to two scrum teams including sprint and release related meetings such as planning, grooming, reviews and retros.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own (along with team) all aspect of the application, including quality, performance testing, and production support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with other members of the team in a proactive fashion, especially any junior programmers, mentoring as necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other duties as assigned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Knowledge, Skills and Abilities Required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full stack JAVA development experience, from backend systems to user interfaces as necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience using AWS services, such as EC2, RDS, and Fargate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience using Spring, Hibernate, jUnit, Mockito&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience using relational database systems especially PostgreSQL preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to comfortably develop code for and debug remote systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with others, capable of working constructively with a group of people that have different skill sets and interests&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to take ownership of and effectively communicate implementation decisions at various levels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently and take initiative as a member of a dynamic and fast-moving team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Been an active member of an Agile team (running Scrum and Kanban) preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Docker preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DevOps Chops preferred (Gitlab CI, Jenkins, Gradle, bash)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education and/or Experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with RESTful APIs with particular attention to security, scalability, availability, and performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and comfort developing large scale distributed applications in a microservices architecture using Java 11+ (Streams, Serialization, Multi-Threading, Annotations)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Microsoft Exchange / EWS a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;em&gt;The above statements are neither intended to be an all-inclusive list of the duties and responsibilities of the job described, nor are they intended to be a listing of all of the skills and abilities required to do the job. Rather, they are intended only to describe the general nature of the job. This job description is not a contract of employment, either express or implied. Employment with Cofense will be voluntarily entered into and your employment is considered at will. Cofense reserves the right to alter the job description at any time without notice&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Cofense is committed to equal employment opportunity. We will not discriminate against employees or applicants for employment on any legally recognized basis [protected class] including, but not limited to: veteran status, uniform service member status, race, color, religion, sex (including pregnancy), gender identity, sexual orientation, national origin, age, physical or mental disability, marital status, genetic information or any other status or characteristic protected by applicable national, federal, state or local laws and ordinances. We adhere to these commitments in all aspects of employment, including recruitment, hiring, training, compensation, promotion, benefits, and discipline.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/cofense-java-software-engineer-iii"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/cofense-java-software-engineer-iii&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 01:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/cofense-java-software-engineer-iii</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/cofense-java-software-engineer-iii</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0064/3769/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Follow Up Boss: Senior Security Engineer</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Full-Stack Programming</category>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0064/3769/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Remote
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://careers.followupboss.com"&gt;https://careers.followupboss.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the job&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a Senior Security Engineer at Follow Up Boss, you'll help product teams build secure software, review code, develop threat models, and lead security initiatives. You will help design and implement security-critical features in our PHP monolith. Ultimately, your work will have a direct impact on the security posture of our products and company.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why would you want to work here?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re a bootstrapped, profitable company that started back in April 2011.  We're a young, ambitious company that only answers to our customers and we don’t just claim to be customer-centric - &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/followupboss/reviews"&gt;we live it&lt;/a&gt;.  We're fully remote and have been since day 1.  Here are a few more reasons we think you'll love working here - and be sure to check out &lt;a href="https://www.followupboss.com/about/"&gt;our video on how we work&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunity to have a big impact on our growth and your career&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No red tape or pointless meetings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive base salary - top 10% in the US; for this position &lt;strong&gt;the range is $166K - $180K&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong benefits package including a 401k with 6% match, health/dental/vision insurance for you and our family, funding for continuing education, paid parental leave, kindle + unlimited books, home office setup, company meetups, and 20 PTO + 10 sick days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solve challenging problems and put your skills to the test every day. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;See the direct impact of your work and the value you created for customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide direct input on technical and non-technical decisions. Your opinion matters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This role is for you if...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You would describe yourself as a patient, empathetic, and having a good sense of humor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re independent, self-motivated, and can stay efficient and productive without someone looking over your shoulder all day long&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have superb written and verbal skills (with a professional yet fun demeanor)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are based in the United States (or a similar time zone) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are happy to have direct communication with customers (we are customer driven).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your qualifications include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Self-motivated&lt;/strong&gt; and proactive mindset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Remote work&lt;/strong&gt; experience is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Based in the USA&lt;/strong&gt;, with a quiet home office with fast internet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of experience in security, with a focus on web applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for security with strong expertise in security best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing large-scale software in PHP and are familiar with cloud computing environments (we use AWS).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient understanding of Linux.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional time management skills. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Attention to detail and commitment to quality&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pragmatic decision-making.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your responsibilities will include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing tools and services that make Follow Up Boss safer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build security-critical features along with other engineers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Researching security standards and new technologies from the industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review PRs for the team from a security perspective as needed. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Respond to security vulnerability reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in managing internal and external security audits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentor the team and organization regarding security best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead engineering and organization-wide security education initiatives. (veracode, riot, sonarqube, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform offensive penetration tests&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement automated security tools and monitoring.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;30 Day Targets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Become familiar with our product and codebase. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pair with fellow engineers to gain knowledge about the system and how we work. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve the new hire onboarding process, by being a part of it. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help address priority security issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in code reviews for the team, with a specific perspective of security.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;60 Day Targets&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement security improvements for new and existing product functionality. e.g. Option for customers to enforce SSO for Office 365 users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in prioritization of application security work. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;90 Day Targets&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ownership of various security education initiatives for developers and the organization. Assist in fleshing out these systems and processes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in security review of critical product features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Core Engineering Values&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Teamwork&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code Quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Focus and Prioritization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Customer Driven&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leadership Qualities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our Employment Package Includes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🏝 Work remotely: Live and work wherever you like!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;💰 Competitive salary: Our career framework pays in the top 10% no matter where you live.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;👩🏾‍⚕️ Insurance: Company-paid health, dental &amp;amp; vision insurance for all of our team members and their families.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🍼 Family leave: generous family leave - fully paid!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;💻 Home office setup: Get a Macbook Pro + $1000 to set up your home office.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;👩🏻‍🏫 Personal development stipend: $1000 per year to focus on bettering yourself.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🤑 401(k): With a 6% company match!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;✈️ Retreats: Join us for company get-togethers every year!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;☕️ Co-working stipend: Get some extra cash for a co-working space or a coffee shop work.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;📚 Free books and Kindle: Get a free Kindle and all the free books - digital and audio - you like, anytime.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;💪 Gym: Monthly stipend to keep you active and feeling good.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;☕️ Money each month to spend on caffeine.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apply for the job&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Do you want to join our team? Then we'd love to hear about you!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/follow-up-boss-senior-security-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/follow-up-boss-senior-security-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 16:23:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/follow-up-boss-senior-security-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/follow-up-boss-senior-security-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0006/6610/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Fitabase: Full Stack .NET Developer ASP.NET MVC / C#</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Full-Stack Programming</category>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0006/6610/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; San Diego, CA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://fitabase.com"&gt;https://fitabase.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Are you a talented .NET software developer looking to join a team where you can feel like a full-fledged member of the design and decisions? Do you want a job where you can take the time you need to build elegant solutions you can be proud of? This is the opportunity for you!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Hello. We’re Fitabase and we’re in need of a passionate full stack developer who can help code, design and lead key development areas of our cloud platform and wearable device tools and join us as we expand our product features and market reach. We’re looking for someone who can quickly become an integral part of the way we plan and design our health sensor data platform.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skills &amp;amp; Requirements&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Technologies we’d love you to have experience with:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;C# / .NET&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ASP.NET MVC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5 / Bootstrap&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Javascript&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;Tech you should be excited to get to learn more about while at Fitabase:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ASP.NET WebAPI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;.NET Core&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blazor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TypeScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Git / Github&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Azure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scalable, Distributed Microservices Systems Design&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Note: &lt;/strong&gt;We can only accept US based candidates. We can be flexible on exact schedules, but your working hours should be predictable and be within normal business hours in Pacific, Central, or Eastern time, Monday-Friday. Not open to short-term, agency, or contract positions.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why You’ll Love Working with Us&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We use all the bleeding edge technologies. For this role you'll use Visual Studio 2022 and code against the latest .NET Core stack combined with a modern framework including the brand new Blazor framework, and utilize many of the latest Azure services and offerings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will get exposure to exciting new cloud technologies like CosmosDB, SQL Azure, App Services, Azure Functions, Service Bus, API Management, and many other PaaS servings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We’re experienced software developers always looking to learn from one another, collaborating in a fast-paced small team environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Peer mentoring and a culture of prioritizing learning and professional development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No blame-game culture, where it's always a team approach to problem solving.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;True work/life balance and no expectations to work more than a normal work day’s hours. Really.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will contribute to software that improves how important health research is done. Our customers include some of the most prestigious academic universities, hospitals, and clinical care providers all over the world who are using technology in new ways not yet in science and literature, and you get to learn from them while helping us!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We’re remote friendly and have been for years!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your opinions will be valued and heard and you will contribute to the future direction of our product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will get a Fitbit of your choice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We'll provide you the latest and greatest developer hardware.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Corporate Benefits&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dental Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid Family Leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid Time Off&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid Sick&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Applying&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Please send 1) a resume and 2) a cover letter -- we’d love one that you wrote just for us that explains who you are and why YOU are right for this job.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/fitabase-full-stack-net-developer-asp-net-mvc-csharp"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/fitabase-full-stack-net-developer-asp-net-mvc-csharp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 00:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/fitabase-full-stack-net-developer-asp-net-mvc-csharp</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/fitabase-full-stack-net-developer-asp-net-mvc-csharp</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0016/3890/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Springboard: Mentor - Software Engineering Career Track (Part-time/Remote)</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Full-Stack Programming</category>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0016/3890/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; San Francisco, CA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.springboard.com/"&gt;https://www.springboard.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Opportunity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Springboard runs an online, self-paced Software Engineering Career Track in which participants learn with the help of a curated curriculum and 1-1 guidance from an expert mentor. Our mentor community - the biggest strength of our programs - comprises some of the best software engineering experts in the field.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you are as passionate about mentoring as you are about software engineering, and can give a few hours per week in return for an honorarium, we would love to hear from you.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Please reach out to us with any questions at mentorrecruiting@springboard.com &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Program&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Completely online and self-paced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Students become proficient in Software Engineering with the help of a curated online curriculum and project-based deliverables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coursework is made up of 800+ hour expert-curated curriculum in partnership with &lt;a href="https://www.rithmschool.com/"&gt;Rithm School&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On average, students finish in 9 months&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Students are working professionals from all over the world, dedicated to switching careers into Software Engineering&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Students have a weekly 30-minute checkin with their mentor to discuss questions, projects, and career advice!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;are as passionate about teaching coding as about software engineering itself&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;are proficient in the topics covered in our &lt;a href="https://ddf46429.springboard.com/uploads/resources/1572915743_Software_Engineering_Career_Track_-_Syllabus_2019.11.04.pdf"&gt;Software Engineering Career Track&lt;/a&gt; and are fluent in technologies such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Python, Flask, SQL, Data Structures and Algorithms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;have at least 3+ years of relevant work experience &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;are available for weekly, 30-minute video check-ins with students to help them set and achieve learning goals, answer subject matter questions, provide feedback on projects, and offer career advice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;have experience critiquing work, in particular giving meaningful feedback on web development, and are able to think on your feet quickly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;are empathetic and have excellent communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Software Engineering mentors are paid an honorarium between $17.50-$32.50 per 30 minute call with students&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Membership in a rich community of expert mentors from great companies like AirBnB, Uber, Google, and Pivotal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Change the lives of students in our program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help us revolutionize online education and inspire the next generation of software engineers!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work at your convenience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;We are an equal opportunity employer and value diversity at our company. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/springboard-mentor-software-engineering-career-track-part-time-remote-3"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/springboard-mentor-software-engineering-career-track-part-time-remote-3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 22:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/springboard-mentor-software-engineering-career-track-part-time-remote-3</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/springboard-mentor-software-engineering-career-track-part-time-remote-3</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0076/4921/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Rainforest QA: Senior Engineer (Frontend)</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0076/4921/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Remote
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.rainforestqa.com/"&gt;https://www.rainforestqa.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Rainforest&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Rainforest QA is a distributed company full of smart, capable people from around the world who enjoy working together to make our customers successful.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our mission is to make product quality accessible for every software company. The Rainforest QA solution combines no-code test automation and crowdsourced testing in a single, one-of-a-kind QA platform, allowing anyone to get the exact insights they need to release with quality, quickly.  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a Senior Engineer at Rainforest QA you'll be part of an experienced and diverse team with members all over the world.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We were built as a distributed team from the beginning and we've committed to implementing tools and processes that allow for and support continuous and effective communication across the world.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Role&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on the Rainforest QA dashboard, our single page application where users manage their test suite, configure test runs, review results and set up their account&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on our tester application, where our crowd of testers connect to our virtual machine infrastructure to conduct tests and submit their results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on internal tooling to improve the development experience of other engineers and ship faster and safer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with product managers and our customer facing teams to analyze customer problems and design high impact features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead projects to implement those features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help other team members to achieve their goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuously learn about new technologies and ways to solve problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with our customer facing teams to triage, troubleshoot, and fix bugs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write unit and integration tests (using our own product!) to ship high quality software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About You&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience in Javascript and be extremely knowledgeable of the language and associated ecosystem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience in React (or equivalent framework / libraries) and be extremely knowledgeable of the framework and associated ecosystem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in writing and maintaining CSS for large projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enthusiasm with building web applications using modern tools like ES7, React, Redux, CSS Modules, Flow, and Webpack - amongst others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience of working on a Ruby on Rails codebase&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Even though this position is mainly frontend focused, we expect you to have some grasp of the whole stack to be able to effectively communicate with engineers across the team, and can make backend or infrastructure changes when the situation calls for it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience in engineering SaaS products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience leading projects with teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An ownership mindset: you should look not only at what you’re asked to do, but ask why you’re doing it and how it impacts on the rest of the product, our customers, and whether it makes sense. We expect you to be responsible for your work and to resolve any bugs you might ship&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excitement to learn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills and able to give and receive constructive feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Happy to review code and have your code reviewed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can work effectively remotely with remote team members (we are a fully distributed company)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working in a large codebase with many stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How we’ll reward you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary plus equity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% company-paid medical, dental, and vision insurance coverage for employees, 75% for dependents (U.S., only).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited paid time-off (PTO).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A weekly allowance for lunches and a monthly allowance for remote office supplies or personal development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Semi-annual company off-sites in exciting destinations around the world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12 weeks of paid maternity leave and 8 weeks of paid leave for supporting parents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401k (U.S., only).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Note on Diversity and Inclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;At Rainforest we believe that diverse teams improve our business. We are an equal opportunity employer and do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, nationality, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Due to employment laws, we are unable to hire individuals internationally located in these following countries at this time: China, France, Iran, Egypt, Russia.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/rainforest-qa-senior-engineer-frontend"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/rainforest-qa-senior-engineer-frontend&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 17:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/rainforest-qa-senior-engineer-frontend</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/rainforest-qa-senior-engineer-frontend</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rainforest QA: Senior Engineer (Backend)</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Back-End Programming</category>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Remote
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.rainforestqa.com/"&gt;https://www.rainforestqa.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Rainforest&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Rainforest QA is a distributed company full of smart, capable people from around the world who enjoy working together to make our customers successful.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our mission is to make product quality accessible for every software company. The Rainforest QA solution combines no-code test automation and crowdsourced testing in a single, one-of-a-kind QA platform, allowing anyone to get the exact insights they need to release with quality, quickly.  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a Senior Engineer at Rainforest QA you'll be part of an experienced and diverse team with members all over the world.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We were built as a distributed team from the beginning and we've committed to implementing tools and processes that allow for and support continuous and effective communication across the world.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Role&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on our main app, which contains the majority of our business logic and is written in Ruby-on-Rails and backed by PostgreSQL and Redis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on numerous support services (including our work scheduler and VM management system - both of which manage hundreds of thousands of requests a day) written in a variety of languages (Elixir, Golang, Crystal, Node, Python) chosen because of their suitability to the problem the service is solving&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on internal tooling to improve the development experience of other engineers and ship faster and safer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with product managers and our customer facing teams to analyze customer problems and design high impact features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead projects to implement those features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help other team members to achieve their goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuously learn about new technologies and ways to solve problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with our customer facing teams to triage, troubleshoot, and fix bugs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write unit and integration tests (using our own product!) to ship high quality software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About You&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience in Ruby (or equivalent dynamic language) and be extremely knowledgeable of the language and associated ecosystem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience in Ruby on Rails (or equivalent framework) and be extremely knowledgeable of the framework and associated ecosystem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in writing and debugging SQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enthusiasm for building applications using tools like Ruby on Rails, Golang, Elixir, React, PostgreSQL, Redis, BigQuery, and Kubernetes - amongst others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience of working on a React codebase&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Even though this position is mainly backend focused, we expect you to have some grasp of the whole stack to be able to effectively communicate with engineers across the team, and can make frontend or infrastructure changes when the situation calls for it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience in engineering SaaS products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience leading projects with teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An ownership mindset: you should look not only at what you’re asked to do, but ask why you’re doing it and how it impacts on the rest of the product, our customers, and whether it makes sense. We expect you to be responsible for your work and to resolve any bugs you might ship&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excitement to learn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills and able to give and receive constructive feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Happy to review code and have your code reviewed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can work effectively remotely with remote team members (we are a fully distributed company)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working in a large codebase with many stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;How we’ll reward you&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary plus equity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% company-paid medical, dental, and vision insurance coverage for employees, 75% for dependents (U.S., only).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited paid time-off (PTO).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A weekly allowance for lunches and a monthly allowance for remote office supplies or personal development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Semi-annual company off-sites in exciting destinations around the world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12 weeks of paid maternity leave and 8 weeks of paid leave for supporting parents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401k (U.S., only).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Note on Diversity and Inclusion&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;At Rainforest we believe that diverse teams improve our business. We are an equal opportunity employer and do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, nationality, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Due to employment laws, we are unable to hire individuals internationally located in these following countries at this time: China, France, Iran, Egypt, Russia.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/rainforest-qa-senior-engineer-backend-2"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/rainforest-qa-senior-engineer-backend-2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 17:40:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/rainforest-qa-senior-engineer-backend-2</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/rainforest-qa-senior-engineer-backend-2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/5948/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Method, Inc.: Senior Software Engineer- Java</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Full-Stack Programming</category>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/5948/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Charlotte, NC
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.method.com/"&gt;https://www.method.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Method is a global design and engineering consultancy founded in 1999. We believe that innovation should be meaningful, beautiful and human. We craft practical, powerful digital experiences that improve lives and transform businesses. Our teams [based in New York, Charlotte, Atlanta, London, and remote] work with a wide range of organizations in many industries, including Healthcare, Financial Services, Retail, Automotive, Aviation, and Professional Services.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Method is seeking a seasoned Senior Software Engineer who has significant experience with DevOps, Cloud, and the development of RESTful services in an enterprise context.  Helping to facilitate application architecture and design are core, collaborative fundamentals of this role, as well as the ability to directly engineer business-critical applications.  Strong personal skills ordered towards client empathy and engagement are highly valued characteristics, and are central to our culture as a diverse and inclusive company.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;At Method, you will collaborate within high-performing, cross-functional teams to build innovative solutions for a variety of clients. You will have the opportunity to work with and learn a myriad of technologies, disciplines, and skills.  You will do so while working closely with engineers of every kind, data scientists, designers, and strategists who specialize in both product and business based solutions. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minimum Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will succeed in this role if you:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience working on large, enterprise development projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have built and launched RESTful Web APIs written in Java&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Java 8 or higher and Web Service Frameworks (Spring, Play, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using JPA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with ORMs such as Hibernate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with package/dependency management systems (Maven, Gradle, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understands Dependency Injection(DI) / Inversion of Control (IoC)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with unit testing frameworks (JUnit, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High level of OOP experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with cloud infrastructure environments (AWS, Azure)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are encouraging in teaching, communicating, and relating with others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a very high standard of written English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Love the journey as much as the destination&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Preferred Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oracle Service Bus experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Apache Kafka and Zookeeper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full stack development (SQL/NoSQL, Java, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with other JVM languages (Scala, Clojure, Kotlin, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why Method?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We look for individuals who are smart, kind and brave. Curious people with a natural ability to think on their feet, learn fast, and develop points-of-view for a constantly changing world find Method an exciting place to work. Our employees are excited to collaborate with dispersed and diverse teams that bring together the best in thinking and making. We champion the ability to listen, and believe that critique and dissonance lead to better outcomes. We believe everyone has the capacity to lead and look for proactive individuals who can take and give direction, lead by example, enjoy the making as much as they do the thinking, especially at senior and leadership levels.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We believe in work/life balance. Seriously. We offer a ton of competitive perks, including:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuing education opportunities &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible PTO and work-from-home policies &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401K matching&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health, Dental and Vision benefits, starting on day 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friday company lunches, company outings, along with a lot of snacks &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health and wellness programs &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other location specific perks (just ask!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Next Steps&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;If Method sounds like the place for you, please submit an application. Also, let us know if you have a presence online with a blog, Twitter, GitHub, Dribbble or other platform.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/method-inc-senior-software-engineer-java"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/method-inc-senior-software-engineer-java&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 15:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/method-inc-senior-software-engineer-java</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/method-inc-senior-software-engineer-java</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RemoteMore: Python Developer</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Full-Stack Programming</category>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Berlin/Chicago 
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://remotemore.com/candidates?utm_source=Jobpost&amp;amp;utm_medium=WWR&amp;amp;utm_campaign=PythonTrue"&gt;https://remotemore.com/candidates?utm_source=Jobpost&amp;amp;utm_medium=WWR&amp;amp;utm_campaign=PythonTrue&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;The position&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;RemoteMore is helping a large tech company with hiring Python developers for its European and US teams.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The company is one of the major tech companies and works across many internal product teams. Multiple Python Developers will be hired and matched to the teams that are best fit for their background/experience. All product teams are fully distributed. The company culture is to focus on work delivered and not hours worked.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Good work-life balance is encouraged: 4-week paid holiday per year is part of the benefits package.  You can work from home or any other place of your choice.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The position is full-time and remote.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Your profile&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Coming from a strong technical background, you are expected to have:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Required technologies: Python&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonus points: Python frameworks (Django, Flask etc), AWS/Azure/Firebase  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Top technical skills for your level of experience: Intermediate or Senior ( 2+  years of experience)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The soft skills to work remotely. Strong individual contributor, strong communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for remote work. You understand the pros and cons of working remotely.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good English language skills to work as part of an international team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Why should YOU apply?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work from anywhere you want.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive compensation based on your skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in a team with other top developers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Making a difference.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;To be considered for the position, please sign up to RemoteMore by following the apply button. &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/remotemore-python-developer-5"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/remotemore-python-developer-5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 09:50:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/remotemore-python-developer-5</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/remotemore-python-developer-5</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/7956/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>LeanTaaS: Senior Software Engineer, Java (US Remote)</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Back-End Programming</category>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/7956/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Santa Clara, CA 
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://leantaas.com"&gt;https://leantaas.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;We are a growth stage company that creates software solutions combining lean principles, predictive and prescriptive analytics, and machine learning to transform hospital and infusion center operations. More than 130 health systems and ~500 hospitals across 42 states rely on our award-winning products to increase patient access, decrease wait times, and reduce healthcare delivery costs. We have raised more than $300 million from top-tier investors such as Bain Capital, Insight Partners, and Goldman Sachs. We have been named among the top 100 AI companies in the world.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please note that while this role is listed as available for remote, we are currently employing in the following states: AK, AZ, CA, CO, FL, GA, IL, IN, MA, MD, MI, MO, NH, NC, OH, OR, PA, SC, TX, UT, VA, WA, WI.  If your state is not listed, we may not be able to proceed with your application. We have offices in Santa Clara, CA and Charlotte, NC for employees who prefer to work regularly or occasionally from an office.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our backend engineers work with small, close-knit, cross-functional teams to build backend APIs that power our products. They are product engineers - i.e, they work with PM, Design, Data Science, and Frontend engineers to understand customer needs and build simple and delightful user experiences to solve hard problems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHAT YOU’LL DO:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with PM, Design and Data Science to understand and solve customer problems with elegant solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own and drive complex initiatives to completion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan and scope new features, maintain and improve quality within the team, and set the direction for our future architecture.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evolve our backend services with new features, enhancements, and bug fixes to increase product value and improve reliability, security and scalability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive elegant systems design and produce clean, readable, performant code using best practices and guidelines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in design reviews, code reviews, on-call rotations, interviews, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHAT YOU’LL BRING&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree in Computer Science, Engineering or equivalent work experience. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years professional experience building production RESTful web services in Java in cloud environments (AWS preferred, GCP or Azure are also ok). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as a good generalist systems designer and coder who can come up with well thought out designs for scalable web services / systems and has an ability to build them neatly. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong command of Java and the ability to write and promote clear, easy to follow, performant and secure code. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A robust understanding of database driven RESTful web services and web architectures in general. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid experience with SQL and MySQL and an ability to write complex, performant, elegant queries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHAT YOU'LL GET&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intellectual and emotional satisfaction of solving tough operational problems in healthcare while improving patient access and saving lives!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive compensation package that includes base salary, annual bonus, and stock options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) Match&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive healthcare benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generous Paid Time Off and Parental Leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monthly reimbursement for Skill Building &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monthly reimbursement for Wellness, Transportation, and/or Home Office&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education Reimbursement for select courses/programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;#LI-Remote&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;LeanTaaS is an equal opportunity employer committed to promoting an inclusive work environment free of discrimination and harassment. We value diversity, inclusion, and aim to provide a sense of belonging for everyone. All qualified applicants for employment will be considered without regard to race, color, sex, gender identity, gender expression, religion, age, national origin or ancestry, citizenship, physical or mental disability, medical condition, family care status, marital status, domestic partner status, sexual orientation, genetic information, military or veteran status, or any other basis protected by federal, state or local laws. If you require assistance during the application process, please reach out to accommodations@leantaas.com. LeanTaaS will reasonably accommodate qualified individuals with disabilities to the extent required by applicable law.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Please note: LeanTaaS is not accepting agency resumes at this time, and we are not responsible for any fees related to unsolicited resumes. Thank you.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/leantaas-senior-software-engineer-java-us-remote"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/leantaas-senior-software-engineer-java-us-remote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 01:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/leantaas-senior-software-engineer-java-us-remote</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/leantaas-senior-software-engineer-java-us-remote</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Logical Engine: Full Stack Ruby on Rails Developer</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Full-Stack Programming</category>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; 222 Merrimac Street Newburyport, MA 01950
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.estimaterocket.com/"&gt;https://www.estimaterocket.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;We are looking for a RoR full Stack Developer to join our growing team! We are a remote-friendly company and encourage anyone in the United States to apply.  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a &lt;strong&gt;Full Stack Ruby on Rails Developer&lt;/strong&gt; at Estimate Rocket, you'll be joining a dynamic engineering team developing end-to-end features that help our customers grow their businesses by an average of 34% every year. Your primary focus will be the development of scalable, performant solutions to the practical challenges our customers face every day.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To be successful in this role, you should have extensive experience working in Ruby on Rails, jQuery and other javascript frameworks, Testing with Rspec or Minitest, and PostgresQL queries and views. You will have a desire to create clean, modular, and easy-to-read code, and enjoy collaborating with coworkers in design, marketing, and customer support to continue to provide exceptional service.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who We Are&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Logical Engine was founded in 2012 and is the creator of Estimate Rocket, a Mobile first SaaS application for service contractors that manages their projects from lead to paid and lets them get work done from anywhere. The project encompasses CRM, Estimating, Scheduling, Invoicing, Payment processing and much more. Our growth has created an opportunity to join our small, dynamic, and growing team.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You’ll Be Doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing, developing, and testing new features based on customer feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tracking down user reported issues and documenting and deploying solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing, developing, and testing responsive web UIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with customers to create integrations and perform data imports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing automated tests for new and existing functionality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with co-workers in small teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We Are Looking For&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4+ years experience building production Ruby on Rails applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent english communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Commitment to user experience and customer satisfaction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to be self motivated in a distributed working environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excited to learn new technologies and quickly jump into unfamiliar territory&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write high quality, well-structured code, tests, and commit messages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;History of shipping successfully released applications (please include names and links on your resume) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technologies We Use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ruby on Rails&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML/CSS/Slim&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Heroku&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zapier&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PostgreSQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Git and Github&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unix based operating systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Work With Us: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Life Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dental Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Short Term/Long Term Disability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;EyeMed Vision Care Plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PTO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid Holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid Sick Days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bereavement Leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An Exciting and Supportive Work Environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional development assistance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employee assistance program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;PLUS MORE PERKS: &lt;/strong&gt;On top of these benefits, we also offer exciting perks! Including, our charitable giving program, holiday gifts, a home office set up (for our remote staff), and an employee referral program.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our Core Values:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Blow Em Away&lt;/em&gt; - leave a great impression.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;em&gt;We've Got Your Back &lt;/em&gt;- We care about our customers, we care about our colleagues and we care about what we are creating.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Enjoy the Ride&lt;/em&gt; - Looking for the best in every situation will always yield a better outcome.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Clear is Kind&lt;/em&gt; - Unclear is Unkind. Don't be afraid of tough conversations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3 Easy Steps to Get Hired:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;1. Fill out the questionnaire. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;2. If you are qualified, you will be sent an assessment for you to complete and a link to schedule your initial screening.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;3. Once passed, you will be invited for a series of video or audio interviews with the hiring team.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Logical Engine is a proud Equal Opportunity Employer. All applicants will receive equal consideration regardless of race, sex, religion, national origin, disability, veteran status, or any other characteristic.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;All applicants must provide proof of identity and eligibility to work in the United States.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/logical-engine-full-stack-ruby-on-rails-developer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/logical-engine-full-stack-ruby-on-rails-developer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 19:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/logical-engine-full-stack-ruby-on-rails-developer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/logical-engine-full-stack-ruby-on-rails-developer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0076/4854/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>AssemblyAI (YC 17): Senior Software Engineer, Python</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Back-End Programming</category>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0076/4854/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; United States
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.assemblyai.com/"&gt;https://www.assemblyai.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;We're looking for a senior backend engineer with strong software and cloud engineering skills. You'll help us build highly scalable developer-centric APIs and backend systems powered by state-of-the-art ML models. Some of your responsibilities will include:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build new API features and endpoints&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build automated test suites and CI/CD pipelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build highly scalable event-driven and realtime systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Instrument systems with metrics, tracing, and logging &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Refactor applications to eliminate tech debt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshoot production issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You'll love this job if you....&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy solving complex technical problems, even when there is no perfect solution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy being in a fast-paced, customer-facing role.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thrive in small, cross-functional teams. We like to wear many hats here!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You're excited to tackle big technical challenges like building highly scalable architectures and achieving zero-downtime deploys.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6+ years of professional experience building backend applications using any popular language such as Python, Java, C#, JavaScript, Go, C/C++&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4+ years of working with SQL and NoSQL databases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of production support experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years working with common AWS services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years developing REST APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience working with Python&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ working with Python backend frameworks like Django, Flask, or Tornado&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience migrating systems to meet increasing traffic/scale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Startup or FAANG-type experience &lt;/strong&gt;- Has worked at a startup or high growth company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Deep AWS knowledge &lt;/strong&gt;- Has many years of experience solutioning within AWS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Strong Python coding abilities &lt;/strong&gt;- Can pass difficult programming challenges in a relatively short period of time. Can speak clearly about their thinking throughout these challenges. Can speak to O-notation of algorithms. Has excellent knowledge of common python idioms and libraries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;High scalability experience&lt;/strong&gt; - Has been a tech leader on scaling systems to hundreds of millions of requests/events per day. Has experience with hyper-observability, scaling algorithms, and using production data to drive system changes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Amazing system design chops &lt;/strong&gt;- When given a hard problem to solve with a new system, they can quickly shape an effective design and communicate its strengths, weaknesses, and tradeoffs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;High-octane thinking&lt;/strong&gt; - Engages deeply on subjects of expertise. Thinks ahead many steps and can see where decisions are likely to lead. Their brains compute at a very high level.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Extremely creative &lt;/strong&gt;- Can find both novel and effective solutions within highly constrained time and resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Fast learner&lt;/strong&gt; - Has shown they can ramp up on difficult topics very fast&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Exceptional gut instincts &lt;/strong&gt;- Can practically feel when something is right or wrong. Can use these instincts to quickly point themselves in the right direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Opinionated&lt;/strong&gt; - They have convictions in what they believe and can communicate their position clearly without drama.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to Have&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Machine learning experience - Has worked with machine learning models at scale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience integrating and deploying ML models into production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits (US)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive Salary + Bonus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401k&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% Remote team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited PTO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Premium Healthcare (100% Covered for you + dependents)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vision &amp;amp; Dental Care&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$1K budget for your home office setup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New Macbook Pro (or PC if you prefer)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2x/year company paid team retreat&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Salary Range (Global): $125,000 - $200,000&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/assemblyai-yc-17-senior-software-engineer-python"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/assemblyai-yc-17-senior-software-engineer-python&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 14:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/assemblyai-yc-17-senior-software-engineer-python</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/assemblyai-yc-17-senior-software-engineer-python</link>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
