<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss">
  <channel>
    <title>We Work Remotely: Design Jobs</title>
    <link>https://weworkremotely.com/categories/remote-design-jobs.rss</link>
    <description>We Work Remotely: Design Jobs</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0064/4850/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>TestGorilla: Web Designer</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0064/4850/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Amsterdam
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/"&gt;https://www.testgorilla.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Hi,&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;I’m Sharon, the Head of Marketing at TestGorilla. We’re a fast-growing HR tech startup that helps teams make better hiring decisions, faster and bias-free.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Over the past year, we’ve experienced tremendous growth. More than 7,500 companies have replaced CVs with our assessments to screen candidates in an unbiased and data-driven way.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As we scale our efforts in 2022 and beyond, we’re looking for a &lt;strong&gt;Web Designer &lt;/strong&gt;who’s passionate about creating and coding web pages and helping people land dream jobs.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s in it for you?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping shape a fast-growing HR tech startup as an early employee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully remote position with bright, motivated, and friendly colleagues around the world &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;€46,728 - €62,953 + share appreciation rights (SARs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible hours and vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid parental leave &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote working budget: €1,000 per year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning and development budget: 3.5% of salary per year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;The job in a nutshell&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;As the &lt;strong&gt;Web Designer&lt;/strong&gt;, you will create designs and work continuously to improve our site and make sure that we have the latest tools for optimum user experience. You will work closely with the Marketing team to bring our product to life and always keep the needs of current and potential customers in mind. You will play a pivotal role in web development, content management, and design optimization.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You are a goal-driven, detail-oriented self-starter. You are passionate about the internet and design, and are able to think analytically to solve problems.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are rebranding and we need your help to create a new website that is in keeping with our new brand. You will become a brand guardian for all designs on our website.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’ll spend time on the following:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will create innovative and responsive designs for our website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will update existing pages and design new ones&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will manage web development projects from start to finish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will collaborate with other team members to go over user experience features and potential website designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will review prototypes, code visual features, test color schemes, and help us to create a new website that embodies our new brand&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here's what we are looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are inspired by our mission to put &lt;em&gt;one billion people in dream jobs&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are fully aligned with our &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/careers/"&gt;values &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have good time-management skills and can adhere to deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are a good communicator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are proficient in HTML, CSS, and Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have an understanding of user testing, A/B testing, and collecting/reporting data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience using design software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have an understanding of UX/UI design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are comfortable with the ambiguity and pace of an early-stage startup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;We typically expect candidates&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; with at least 3 years of experience in Web Designing&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; to have the skills mentioned above.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus points if…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience working in a SaaS company and a fast-growing startup &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have knowledge of SEO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are motivated to improve web standards and practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interested?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;We don’t offer rainbow glitter unicorns or dog-friendly offices (we literally don’t have an office), but we do offer solid core values and a product meant to give everyone a fair, unbiased chance at their dream jobs.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Here at TestGorilla, we eat our own dog food. We use our assessment platform to make sure we make the best hiring decisions, faster and bias-free. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;So if this role sounds like a good fit for you, I’d like you &lt;a href="https://assessment.testgorilla.com/testtaker/publicinvitation/7fd893d6-00d9-47d7-984e-0a32f2a59f14"&gt;to take an assessment&lt;/a&gt; so we can get a better idea about whether you would fit the role. It’s also a great opportunity for you to get to know our product!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;If you’re hired, I’ll do everything I can to help you succeed at TestGorilla and throughout the rest of your career.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-web-designer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-web-designer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 13:23:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 13:23:53 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-web-designer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-web-designer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/9465/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>ShopExperts: Freelance Shopify UI/UX Designer</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Contract</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/9465/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Canada
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://shopexperts.com"&gt;https://shopexperts.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Shopexperts is looking for freelance UI/UX designers and Web layout designers to join our talent network. Our clients are eCommerce agencies and eCommerce tech startups building for Shopify, and DTC or B2B consumer eCommerce brands building on the Shopify platform. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vetted freelancers in our network are matched with companies in need of skilled design talent for ongoing/temporary contracts starting from 10 hours/week or for defined projects starting from 40 hours/week.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Set your own hourly/day rate - up to $85/hour, or up to $750/day&lt;br&gt;- Get matched with ambitious companies in the eCommerce space for defined large projects or ongoing contracts from 1-6 months, up to full-time permanent jobs. &lt;br&gt;- Be part of a growing and vibrant professional community &lt;br&gt;- Develop your career and craft with fewer, better contracts and companies&lt;br&gt;- Weekly or bi-weekly payouts&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Native or fluent English is required&lt;br&gt;- 4 years of professional experience as a web designer. The more experience you have as a Shopify developer, the better.&lt;br&gt;- Exposure to Shopify's Polaris design guidelines and eCommerce theme or PDP design experience a plus&lt;br&gt;- Must have a track record of high performing team member&lt;br&gt;- With or without team lead experience&lt;br&gt;- Available a minimum of 10 hours a week (up to 40)&lt;br&gt;- Priority and preference given to skilled freelancers in the UK, Spain, Portugal, Serbia, Romania, South Africa, Poland, Lithuania, Bulgaria, Argentina, Brazil. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://shopifygroup.typeform.com/to/sRuKEwy3"&gt;Apply to join our talent community&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/shopexperts-freelance-shopify-ui-ux-designer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/shopexperts-freelance-shopify-ui-ux-designer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 10:39:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 10:39:24 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/shopexperts-freelance-shopify-ui-ux-designer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/shopexperts-freelance-shopify-ui-ux-designer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0001/4290/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>PSPDFKit: Continuous Integration and Delivery Engineer</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0001/4290/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Vienna, Austria
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://pspdfkit.com"&gt;https://pspdfkit.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;As a Continuous Integration and Delivery (CI/CD) Engineer your objective is to make sure that the engineering team can continuously ship reliable and secure software.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maintain and evolve PSDPFKit’s CI infrastructure, which includes Linux, Mac and Windows machines&lt;br&gt;Maintain a set of core metrics about the CI infrastructure in order to facilitate data-driven decisions about technologies, vendors, and testing approaches&lt;br&gt;Collaborate with individual product engineering teams to facilitate optimal use of CI infrastructure&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;3 or more years of experience working on infrastructure tooling, with knowledge of one or more CI systems (e.g. Buildkite, Travis CI) - bonus points for experience with CI/CD systems based on AWS and Azure&lt;br&gt;3 or more years of experience operating *nix based infrastructure, with Linux as a main platform&lt;br&gt;Experience collaborating in a remote environment in close contact with application developers and devops engineers&lt;br&gt;Experience understanding and embracing the benefits of immutable infrastructure defined with domain-specific tools (e.g. Terraform)&lt;br&gt;Open to receiving and giving feedback - both positive and negative&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/pspdfkit-continuous-integration-and-delivery-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/pspdfkit-continuous-integration-and-delivery-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 13:09:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 13:09:32 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/pspdfkit-continuous-integration-and-delivery-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/pspdfkit-continuous-integration-and-delivery-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0074/6109/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>SugarCRM: UX Designer</title>
      <region>Europe Only</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0074/6109/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Cupertino
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://sugarcrm.com"&gt;https://sugarcrm.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;**Only candidates local to, and authorized to work in &lt;strong&gt;Serbia or Romania&lt;/strong&gt; are being considered at this time**&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Come be a part of a team of designers passionate about creating the very best product for our users. As a UX Designer, you will be involved in every aspect of the product development process, from brainstorming the next great product innovation to tweaking pixels right before launch. You will be expected to utilize your full range of designs, and you will own the experience for a wide area of the product. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Where do you fit: &lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are smart, talented, and aspire to be a master of your craft: You are able to distill complex problems and propose simple, elegant solutions. You are confident enough to deliver unconventional insights and designs. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You play well with others: You thrive in a collaborative environment. You are as good at soliciting feedback on your own work as you are at adding value to others. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are passionate about new technology: You follow the latest trends, download the newest apps, read the relevant design blogs. You have a keen eye for beautiful and useful products. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are even more passionate about people: You never lose sight of what matters most to our customers. You are a tireless advocate for our end users and unwavering in your desire to provide the best experience. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Impact you will make in the role: &lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design an easy-to-use, simple, beautiful product that also fulfills the high standards enterprise software must adhere to &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in all phases of the design process (brainstorm to making to QA). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work effectively in a collaborative environment to create top-performing interfaces &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct user research and usability testing, write up and present results &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work cross-functionally with product management, engineering and marketing &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Give and solicit feedback from other designers in order to continually raise our bar for quality &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Expertise you will bring in:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in building and shipping applications &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in URL featuring examples of interaction design work &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience with end-to-end (hybrid UX and UI) design &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work effectively in a collaborative environment to create top-performing interfaces ·Find creative ways to apply and enhance design system patterns &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of application design experience &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of interaction design experience &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong project management, communication, and presentation skills &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prototype out your ideas (Figma, Axure, Invision, etc…) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA/BS or MA/MS in interaction design, HCI, industrial design, or related field or equivalent experience &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bonus Expertise:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with the design of enterprise apps, tools design, mobile apps, productivity tools and user research &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;We understand that no candidate is perfectly qualified for any job. Experience comes in different forms; many skills are transferable; and passion goes a long way. Even more important than your resume is a clear demonstration of dedication, impact, and the ability to thrive in a fluid and collaborative environment. We want you to learn new things in this role, and we encourage you to apply if your experience is close to what we’re looking for. We also know that diversity of background and thought makes for better problem solving and more creative thinking, which is why we're dedicated to adding new perspectives to the team.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits and Perks:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Beyond a stellar work environment, friendly people, and inspiring work, we have some sweet benefits and perks:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Private medical and vision benefit coverage&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Health &amp;amp;Wellness Reimbursement Program&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Educational Resources - Career &amp;amp; Personal Development Program&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Attractive salary package&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Flexible work hours&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Meal tickets&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;-Football Team&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;-We are a merit-based company with many opportunities to learn, excel and grow your career!&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/sugarcrm-ux-designer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/sugarcrm-ux-designer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 20:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 20:58:25 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/sugarcrm-ux-designer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/sugarcrm-ux-designer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/8797/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>amazee.io: UX Product Designer - (80% - 100%)</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/8797/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Zurich, Switzerland 
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://amazee.io"&gt;https://amazee.io&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;UX Product Designer - (80% - 100%)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Hi! We're &lt;a href="http://amazee.io/"&gt;amazee.io&lt;/a&gt;, a ZeroOps application delivery hub for engineering teams to deploy applications more easily. Our developer-centric, open source platform makes developers’ lives and jobs easier, minimizing the stress of managing infrastructure or operations. amazee.io supports organizations across the globe to accelerate their cloud and container adoption, along with providing easily managed Kubernetes for developer teams. We run anywhere in the world, with 24/7/365 dedicated support. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re looking for a UX Designer to drive improvements to how we assess, develop, and improve user experience and interactions with our ZeroOps delivery platform Lagoon. From a largely internal tool, Lagoon has grown to be a core product in its own right. We are growing a design and development team around Lagoon, to drive it into becoming a world leading platform for application deployments, for both technical and non technical users. You'll work alongside a UI Designer, and a Front End Developer in a product development team. We’ve got some exciting new directions to take our interfaces and integrations, and in delivering a more complete experience for all our users. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you feel like this could be the role for you, then come and join a team of open source enthusiasts, committed to providing flexible web solutions in an open and transparent work environment, and having fun doing it.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be doing: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with our internal teams, external partners and users to identify opportunities to improve our Lagoon product suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conducting user research to uncover user’s pain points, needs and opportunities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing our user journey maps and personas &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working closely with developers to develop the look and feel of our products, and ensure a high level of quality and usability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Producing sketches and prototypes to test functionality and formalise design requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shaping a culture of design at amazee.io to help define the interactions users at all levels have with our products and tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll bring:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated work experience as a digital Product Designer or similar role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience designing technical products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in digital interface design for web/admin interfaces (and maybe even CLI!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with design programs (Inkscape, Illustrator and Sketch) and prototyping tools (Invision, Figma etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of how to conduct good UX research to obtain truly meaningful insights (quantitative and qualitative)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong focus on customer and user advocacy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An eye for aesthetic design and customer appeal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfort communicating design and technical topics in English, both verbal and written&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;amazee.io is dedicated to providing a work environment of trust, transparency, and inclusion for everyone. As a fully remote company we offer flexibility when it comes to working hours and location. Here’s some other things you can expect from us.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we’ll bring:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A fully distributed team of creative colleagues in a flat, open and transparent organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible working hours, and time off in lieu when you work overhours&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully Remote working &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 paid days off a year for conference attendance or education related commitments &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An annual education benefit of $1,500 or equivalent to dedicate to your professional development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An annual wellbeing benefit of $500 or equivalent to dedicate to your physical or mental health &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A monthly connectivity benefit of $100 or equivalent for you to expense internet costs as a remote worker &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your own annual tech budget, with full initial setup provided&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sweet, sweet Swag - Hoodies and other goodies &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;amazee.io Quest!&lt;/strong&gt; - After 3 years, you’ll get 3 weeks paid off work to undertake a profound personal goal, or undertake a bucket list type challenge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So what’s next?: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Apply! Send us your CV showcasing who you are, your experience, and anything else you think we should know!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The amazee.io Team &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/amazee-io-ux-product-designer-80-100"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/amazee-io-ux-product-designer-80-100&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 11:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 11:47:14 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/amazee-io-ux-product-designer-80-100</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/amazee-io-ux-product-designer-80-100</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/8736/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>TryHackMe: Lead UI/UX Designer</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/8736/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; London
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://tryhackme.com"&gt;http://tryhackme.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;Full-time Fully Remote&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;£70,000 to £90,000 (experience dependent) ~$81k to $100k&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What we do&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="https://tryhackme.com/"&gt;&lt;br&gt;TryHackMe&lt;/a&gt; is an online platform (with over a million users) that teaches cyber security through short, gamified real-world labs. We have content for both complete beginners and seasoned hackers, incorporation guides and challenges to cater for different learning styles.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;About the role&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The fundamentals of what you will be doing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate business needs, user needs and technology constraints into solution concepts that are meaningful, easy to use, and engaging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Combine UX thinking with design execution, to produce usable and intuitive user interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop UI mockups and prototypes that clearly illustrate how sites function and look like&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can innovate and develop out-of-the-box solutions to complex user interaction problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct all elements of design, including typography, imagery, iconography, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide critical analysis of user experience designs based on heuristics and other accepted design principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop personas, user stories and other design related documents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides mentoring and design leadership to designers. &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review designs against business requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flat hierarchy management style (empowerment, psychological safety, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate new and emerging methods and technologies in UX prototyping and identify best of breed to incorporate into your team’s toolkit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why would this role be challenging?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are currently rebuilding our platform, and we need to figure out how much we should be rebuilding from scratch. This is where your research expertise comes in handy. After the research phase, you will set the UI/UX strategy for the entire platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Redesign most of the UI components from scratch, setting out the best practices for each component &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage design libraries and design systems with adherence to our brand.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our team is small but scaling. So we are in the chaotic growing phase and we need help thinking through some of our design and design thinking processes. &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify areas that need alignment or could benefit from knowledge sharing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify design/research related inefficiencies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evangelizing the merits of good design and research - champions user needs at all levels and influences stakeholders to consider those needs in their objectives. In other words, we want a thought leader who actively defines and institutes best practices for design, while fostering innovation to address evolving consumer expectations and technological advances.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Must-haves:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a UX research expert by… &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recommend, plan and execute the research with the most appropriate tools/methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate results (Ex: unforeseen opportunities and issues that have a significant impact on product strategy and design) verbally and visually&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set a design strategy out of the result&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong UI skills, ability to create ascetically pleasing designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of user-centered design, interaction design principles, responsive design and accessibility standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactive, structured, attention to detail, growth mindset, no ego&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superior conceptual and critical-thinking abilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced with Figma&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills, including the ability to present complex concepts clearly and persuasively across diverse audiences at various levels of the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be willing to work 4 - 5.5 hours overlap with London time zone from 9am to 5pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nice to haves:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Typically has 5 years’ experience in UX / UI design role, using a wide variety of research methods and technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AB testing experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with HTML5, CSS3 and the use of various Javascript frameworks in interface design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Asynchronous working experience with a distributed team across many time zones&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cultural awareness and sensitivity, as this role will involve daily interaction with people in countries around the globe&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previously worked with EdTech and/or SaaS products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has worked at a start-up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Founder Story&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;TryHackMe started in 2018 by two cyber security enthusiasts, Ashu Savani and Ben Spring, who met at a summer internship. When getting started in the field, they found learning security to be a fragmented, inaccessible and difficult experience; often being given a vulnerable machine's IP with no additional resources is not the most efficient way to learn, especially when you don't have any prior knowledge. When Ben returned back to University he created a way to deploy machines and sent it to Ashu, who suggested uploading all the notes they'd made over the summer onto a centralised platform for others to learn, for free.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;To allow users to share their knowledge, TryHackMe allows other users (at no charge) to create a virtual room, which contains a combination of theoretical and practical learning components.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;The platform has never raised any capital and is entirely bootstrapped.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;As the UX/UI Designer you will work within the Software Engineering team and collaboratively with the Product team using agile methodologies (Scrum). This role is fast-paced and varied and there is space for you to help define this with your own expertise.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Perks &amp;amp; Benefits&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;💰 Salary &lt;/strong&gt;£70,000 to £90,000 (&lt;em&gt;experience dependent) ~$81k to $100k&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;🕒 Flexi Time &lt;/strong&gt;Choose when to start, finish and take breaks in your workday.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;💸 401k / Pension &lt;/strong&gt;TryHackMe makes it easy to save money for retirement.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;🧡 Health Insurance &lt;/strong&gt;Get health insurance if you're in a country that doesn't have public health care.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;🏗️ 10% Project &lt;/strong&gt;Devote 10% of your time developing anything you want, providing it benefits TryHackMe in some way.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;⛱️ Company Retreat &lt;/strong&gt;We're planning to have an annual company retreat (post-covid), fully paid for by us!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;🚣 Fully Remote &lt;/strong&gt;In a fully digital world, there is nothing stopping you from working anywhere you want.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;💪 Personal Development &lt;/strong&gt;Everyone gets a minimum annual training budget of £2,500. Use this for online courses, to acquire certifications, and more.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;💻 Tools &lt;/strong&gt;You'll receive a dedicated work laptop, and any other accessories you need to do your best work.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our Hiring Process&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stage 1: 15m chat to learn more about you (and vice versa)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stage 2: 1h design call presenting a case study from your portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stage 3: 1h management and culture fit call&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;(Optional) Stage 4: Meet some team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;🔥 &lt;strong&gt;Apply Now!&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/tryhackme-lead-ui-ux-designer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/tryhackme-lead-ui-ux-designer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 10:22:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 10:22:51 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/tryhackme-lead-ui-ux-designer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/tryhackme-lead-ui-ux-designer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/6274/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Cavallo: Cloud Architect </title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/6274/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Grand Rapids, Michigan
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.cavallo.com/"&gt;https://www.cavallo.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Senior Cloud Architect &lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Cavallo is seeking a Senior Cloud Architect who will lead the Development Teams in the innovation of new and existing SAAS platforms and features. The Senior Cloud Architect will be tasked with making high-level decisions throughout each stage of the architecting process in addition to managing and facilitating both the technical and design aspects of our complex SAAS solutions. An expert problem solver, the Senior Cloud Architect will need to see the big picture and create architectural blueprints that guide the Development Team in producing the high quality applications that Cavallo is known for. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;A typical day of a Senior Cloud Architect would include:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with the Product and DevelopmentTeams to determine requirements for new and existing SAAS applications; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing high level product architectures and specifications with special attention given to system integrations and feasibility; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Defining and overseeing technical standards, including software coding standards, guidelines and best practices; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifying tools, technologies/tech stacks and methodologies that improve or leverage the design and operating effectiveness;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Governing on topics related to cloud solutions.  Owning and maintaining all Cavallo design documentation, architectural models, etc.;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leading Developers in the creation of new SAAS applications or improving existing ones; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overseeing the work of the Development Team through code reviews to ensure their work complies with coding standards, best practices and initial design;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Providing technical guidance and coaching on project requirements and objectives to the Development Team;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluating existing architectures and recommending changes to improve performance; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conducting research to identify new technologies that could be useful in future products. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;This may be the job for you if:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have 7-10 years of proven experience architecting large-scale SAAS applications; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have earned a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science or other related field (Advanced degrees a plus); &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are extremely knowledgeable in application design and architecture;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You possess experience using Git, Jira or other available code repositories and project management platforms; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a strong understanding of the major cloud service providers (AWS and Azure), certifications a plus;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a strong understanding of a broad range of software technologies and platforms;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are exceptionally organized and possess an ability to unify and coach a Team; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have the ability to collaborate with cross-functional teams across the organization; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a highly analytical mindset and are able to see the big picture without losing sight of the details; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You personify Cavallo’s Core Values;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are passionate about innovation and creating useful software applications;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are self-motivated, hard-working and strive to be the best version of yourself daily;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are looking to join a team of people who are eager to learn and share knowledge.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Why should you apply?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Become a member of a #PeopleFirst organization that believes in instilling excellence in the people who make up our team; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create exciting, innovative solutions for a fast growing software development company; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with collaborative colleagues who seek out and value each other’s input and feedback;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong leadership who believe in creating enormous and measurable value for our Customers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Key Benefits:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive Salary Package&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, Dental, Vision, Life and STD Insurance&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4% 401(k) Employer Match&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generous PTO and Work/Life Synergy&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning and Career Development Opportunities&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;About Cavallo&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Cavallo is one of West Michigan’s largest, fastest-growing software companies. We’re seeking the self-motivated, the hard-working, the problem solvers, and the dedicated to join our team of experts. We're focused on helping businesses grow, expand, or reshape how they do things by approaching each and every problem with energy, creativity, and confidence. Ingenuity, adaptation, and evolution are at the core for us at Cavallo.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our Grand Rapids-based headquarters is focused on helping change the way organizations do business through our software products, customizations, expertise, and support. Our enterprise software solutions work with leading business applications, Microsoft Dynamics GP and Business Central, and integrate with a wide range of apps and platforms. Cavallo has been in the business of helping manufacturing and distribution companies increase productivity and efficiency since 2003. We got our start when a small business owner tasked a software developer with transforming a pile of clipboards and legal pads into a streamlined, efficient inventory management system. We have been sharing ideas and innovating ever since.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;At Cavallo, we're always looking for talented individuals to join our team of professionals. We believe our success is built on the abilities of our employees, and we strive to create a challenging and rewarding environment where all individuals are respected and encouraged to grow. Reach out to us today!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/cavallo-cloud-architect"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/cavallo-cloud-architect&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:43:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 17:43:17 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/cavallo-cloud-architect</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/cavallo-cloud-architect</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0076/2096/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Viva Translate: Senior UX Web Designer (Latin America only)</title>
      <region>Latin America Only</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0076/2096/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; USA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://vivatranslate.com/"&gt;https://vivatranslate.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Viva Translate is led by a team of engineers from top companies and institutions, such as Google and MIT, with a shared dream. We are creating a world where language and culture are no longer barriers to work and opportunity, and we are starting across Latin America.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Technology is at the core of our product. Viva is building a tool that helps people read, write, and speak better across English, Spanish, and Portuguese. We have an incredible dream for the future of borderless work. But we know that great dreams start with great people.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;What's your story? If you too are an explorer, a dreamer, and a builder, we'd love to meet you.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you'll be doing&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unique design perspective - insightful into delight and play&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User Experience - Lead all phases of product design for different web projects, ensuring the best user experience in each initiative.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research - Conduct user and industry trend research, define our customers’ use cases, needs &amp;amp; personas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiments - Help run rigorous design experiments, quantitatively analyze user behaviors, rapidly test and iterate the designs to optimize performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High-fidelity designs - Create wireframes and detailed designs ready for engineering.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Product improvements - identify big swing opportunities, review existing user flows and propose areas of improvement, and work closely with Engineering and other teams to suggest &amp;amp; implement improvements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cross-functional collaboration - Collaborate with engineering and other teams to identify &amp;amp; implement product improvement opportunities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Must-have skills &lt;/strong&gt;💪 &lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience working in UX/UI, Web or similar positions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of user-centered design and interaction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a Product Design or UI/UX design portfolio with multiple case studies of products you worked on&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced in Figma&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess deep empathy for users and an eye for good web UX/UI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication and organization skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thrives in a fast-paced startup environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with ambiguity and adjust priorities as business needs shift&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Native Spanish or Portuguese speaker&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Based in Latin America with at least B1-B2 level of English fluency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Nice to haves &lt;/strong&gt;🍒&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience working in a high growth product-led startup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passionate about bridging communication gaps across cultures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have domain experience working in SaaS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our values 💛&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always leveling up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Science-based&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open integrity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Playfulness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we offer &lt;/strong&gt;✨&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully remote team 🌎&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ in-person retreats (past locations include Mexico &amp;amp; Colombia) annually&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Join an early-stage startup (9 people &amp;amp; growing 🚀)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Home office stipend &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited time-off &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health &amp;amp; fitness benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning stipend - we are here to support your personal &amp;amp; professional development journey&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/viva-translate-senior-ux-web-designer-latin-america-only"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/viva-translate-senior-ux-web-designer-latin-america-only&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 16:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 16:28:50 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/viva-translate-senior-ux-web-designer-latin-america-only</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/viva-translate-senior-ux-web-designer-latin-america-only</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viva Translate: Senior Product Design Engineer (LLM focus)</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; USA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://vivatranslate.com/"&gt;https://vivatranslate.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Viva Translate is led by a team of engineers from top companies and institutions, such as Google and MIT, with a shared dream. We are creating a world where language and culture are no longer barriers to work and opportunity, and we are starting across Latin America. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technology is at the core of our product. Viva is based on a translation platform that automates workplace communications and enables global teams to collaborate seamlessly. We have an incredible dream for the future of borderless work. But we know that great dreams start with great people. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What's your story? If you too are an explorer, a dreamer, and a builder, we'd love to meet you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you'll be doing&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Language learning model interface design/engineering - comfortable with designing and/or developing LLM interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unique design perspective - insightful into delight and play&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Product improvements - identify big swing opportunities, review existing user flows and propose areas of improvement, and work closely with Engineering and other teams to suggest &amp;amp; implement improvements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cross-functional collaboration - Collaborate with engineering and other teams to identify &amp;amp; implement product improvement opportunities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User Experience - Lead all phases of product design for different web projects, ensuring the best user experience in each initiative.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research - Conduct user and industry trend research.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define our customers’ use cases, needs &amp;amp; personas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiments - Help run rigorous design experiments, quantitatively analyze user behaviors, and rapidly test and iterate the designs to optimize performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High-fidelity designs - Create wireframes and detailed designs ready for engineering.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Must-have skills &lt;/strong&gt;💪 &lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience working in UX/UI, Web or similar positions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with designing/developing LLM interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of user-centered design and interaction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a Product Design or UI/UX design portfolio with multiple case studies of products you worked on, one of which showcases an LLM-related product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced in Figma&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess deep empathy for users and an eye for good web UX/UI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication and organization skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thrives in a fast-paced startup environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with ambiguity and adjust priorities as business needs shift&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to haves ✨&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Product design engineering background, likes to tinker and build &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience working in a high-growth product-led startup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passionate about bridging communication gaps across cultures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have domain experience working in SaaS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some Spanish and/or Portuguese proficiency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our values 💛&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always leveling up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Science-based&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open integrity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Playfulness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we offer&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully remote team 🌎&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ in-person retreats (past locations include Mexico &amp;amp; Colombia) annually&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Join an early-stage startup (9 people &amp;amp; growing 🚀)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Home office stipend &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited time-off &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health &amp;amp; fitness benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning stipend - we are here to support your personal &amp;amp; professional development journey&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/viva-translate-senior-product-design-engineer-llm-focus"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/viva-translate-senior-product-design-engineer-llm-focus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 14:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 14:20:54 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/viva-translate-senior-product-design-engineer-llm-focus</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/viva-translate-senior-product-design-engineer-llm-focus</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0016/9187/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Power Home Remodeling: Mid-Level User Experience Designer.</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0016/9187/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Suburban Philadelphia, PA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.powerhrg.com"&gt;http://www.powerhrg.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mid-Level User Experience Designer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Looking to make a real impact in a dynamic and collaborative workplace? Power, the largest home remodeling company in the nation, is looking for a passionate and motivated User Experience Designer to join our us. You’ll have the chance to define how users will interact with our custom, innovative technology products, and collaborate with a team that is constantly pushing ourselves to improve and build tools that people genuinely want to use.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;To see our design team's work visit: https://dribbble.com/powerhrg&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we do here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Fancy a unique work environment that is constantly pushing you to try something new? or perhaps stretch your skills by designing for an industry you’ve always wanted to improve?&lt;br&gt;At Power, we build our own application suite of products to run our entire business. We build complete solutions for finance, recruiting, sales, contact center, and even meeting software. These are just some of the areas you’ll get an opportunity to tackle.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We also design solutions for augmented reality in the home, satellite photo measurements, and artificial intelligence suggestion engines.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We get to dip our toes in many different fascinating areas and solve unique challenging problems that would on their own, be standalone apps or companies. We’re a tech powerhouse built inside a remodeling company.&lt;br&gt;Our teams are distributed so we live and die by our ability to successfully collaborate. We communicate using our own slack-like chat client. We use our own handoff tools to support our User Experience team to create and collaborate with the development and business groups.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Like design systems? We also believe that a design system unites product teams around a common visual language, so we’ve built 2 open source projects to support this effort called Playbook.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The user experience team is a small and diverse team made up of UX Designers and UX Engineers. We value diversity of all types at Power and our team is made up of a kind, thoughtful group of people with a wide range of backgrounds. We actively try to find people with different perspectives and experiences to the ones we already have.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;With a distributed group it’s important to connect in person, so we fly the whole team to Philadelphia 3 times a year for our week-long event called Create, which focuses on connecting and learning from each other and the business.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;At Power we have all the upsides of a startup, move fast, ship rapidly, and iterate quickly, but with the benefit of an established organization that is well funded and profitable.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The biggest perk of working at Power is that we have a small, talented team with a very large audience. This means you have the ability to make a huge impact on the product and the company while having really interesting and challenging problems to work on. We believe deeply in what we do and we're all in this to build something lasting, sustainable, and positive.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Power has been awarded Computerworld’s Best Places to Work in IT, Fortune Magazine’s #1 Workplace for Millennials, one of Glassdoor’s Best Places to Work, one of Inc. 5000’s Fastest Growing Private Companies, and Philadelphia Magazine Coolest Companies.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MUST PROVIDE A LINK TO YOUR PORTFOLIO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 3 years of industry experience in product design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to design projects across the entire product lifecycle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong written and verbal communication and presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong collaboration skills across disciplines to drive change into products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage and work on multiple projects concurrently&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with and building design systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to define problems and goals, map user flows, prototype interactions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to support the building process across with development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A deep understanding of user problems to create elegant but practical solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough knowledge of many design approaches, methodologies and lo-fi and high-fi prototyping skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to identify problems and act on opportunities to improve the product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nice to have: Experience with front-end development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nice to have:  Ruby on Rails, and or React.js experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary and Benefits:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full medical, dental, life and disability insurance plans that can be tailored to your specific needs and the needs of your family&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A competitive 401(k) retirement savings program matched by Power&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary - We pay very well at market rates reflecting both location and experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All the tech you need - We'll pay for whatever hardware and software you need to work and make sure you're regularly upgraded to the latest versions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personal development - Personal development books, courses, &amp;amp; conferences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid parental leave - When the time comes to welcome a new member of the family, we offer paid parental leave.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nitro Create: Powers own tech conference (3 times per year).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/power-home-remodeling-mid-level-user-experience-designer-1"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/power-home-remodeling-mid-level-user-experience-designer-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 13:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 13:41:54 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/power-home-remodeling-mid-level-user-experience-designer-1</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/power-home-remodeling-mid-level-user-experience-designer-1</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/8129/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Listings Project: Product/UX Designer</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/8129/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; 
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.listingsproject.com/"&gt;https://www.listingsproject.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;bout the Role:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Listings Project is seeking a Product/UX Designer to join our small, all-remote, community-based, twenty-year-old company. As our Product Designer, you will work closely with our leadership team to plan the overall direction of our product and translate those high-level product goals into a delightful design and excellent user experience rooted in equity, diversity, and justice. You will be involved in all phases of the design process and responsible for delivering designs from concept, implementation, through deployment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Role Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with the leadership team to understand business goals, community needs to shape and identify product priorities and direction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create high-fidelity designs and production-ready design assets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with CTO (the “engineering team”) to implement designs in the final product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gather, analyze, and glean actionable insights from our community and customer experience team for continually improving our product user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;About You: A successful candidate must have the following skills and experience:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Product Design Experience. Vast and recurring success in a product or user experience (UX) design role for the web and a track record of delivering excellent web application user experience designs including thoughtful interface and interaction design. You are familiar with the capabilities and constraints of modern HTML, CSS, and other front-end web technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design Point of View. You have an excellent understanding eye for detail, aesthetic design, and customer appeal. You are a champion for designs that sustain our commitment to our justice-focused community.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication and Collaboration. Thrives working with an all-remote team, with excellent communication, collaborative and organization skills.  You communicate promptly, clearly and solicit feedback in an ongoing, structured way. You effectively organize your work to remain productive with asynchronous communication cycles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with project management software such as Asana.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equity Analysis and Practice. You are aware of your group identities and how they have shaped your life and experiences at work. You have an analysis of how racism and other forms of oppression in society impact relationships, systems, and culture. You bring experience and skills for working effectively with colleagues across group identities and roles. You are committed to self-transformation and are on a lifelong journey to expand your equity analysis, skills and practice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nice to Haves:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong front-end coding skills for the web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience effectively analyzing user data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has a passion for serving Listings Project community of artists and creative people&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest in and familiarity with the real estate industry, housing justice and/or tenant’s rights advocacy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pay &amp;amp; Benefits:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote, Full time, salary range $100K – $125K.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited vacation/personal days, scheduled with business needs in mind, with an expectation that employees take at least 15 days over the course of a year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;QSEHRA Health Reimbursement Arrangements (HRAs) are employer-funded group health plans from which employees are reimbursed tax-free for qualified medical expenses up to a fixed dollar amount per year. Unused amounts may be rolled over to be used in subsequent years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(K) with company match.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Role Requirements: &lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are an all-remote team who works on an Eastern time zone schedule. We anticipate travel for in person meetings 2-4 times each year with 3-5 days of travel per trip.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This role requires the candidate to own a video-chat capable computer with reliable Internet access.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be legally authorized to work in the US&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be based in the US&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Listings Project is an equal opportunity employer:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our policy is to select, place, train and promote the best-qualified individuals based upon relevant factors such as work quality, attitude, and experience so as to provide equal opportunity for all of our employees in compliance with applicable local, state and federal law, and without regard to non-work-related factors such as sexual orientation, gender identity or expression, race, color, religion, national origin, sex, age, marital status, disability, economic status, personal appearance including height and weight, family responsibility, matriculation, political affiliation or any other status protected by applicable law. This policy applies to all activities, including but not limited to, recruiting, hiring, training, transfers, promotions, and benefits. This policy governs all aspects of employment, including selection, job assignment, compensation, discipline, termination, and access to benefits and training.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;To Apply:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide a portfolio with examples of your work demonstrating your product design experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please remove any school names from your resume. You may leave your degree (e.g., “B.A. Communication”), but please remove any undergraduate or graduate school names. This is aimed at opening this opportunity to more candidates, reviewing applicants on performance assessments, and mitigating bias in the decision-making process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;This position will remain open until October, 28, 2022.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Equity and Inclusion:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Listings Project is an organization committed to anti-racism. As part of our commitment, we cultivate a community and a platform that is inclusive, where people can interact in a way that is respectful, life-affirming, and justice-focused. We believe that creating opportunities for all people to have equitable access to commercial, residential, and public spaces contributes to more resilient, healthy, compassionate, transparent, and sustainable communities. Listings Project strives to create a culture in which all transactions among our members (and beyond them) are rooted in authenticity, inclusion, respect, and kindness. We embrace the fundamental premise that our diversity is an asset that can strengthen us. At Listings Project, we strive to learn what we can from all of the communities to which we belong—and to create something altogether new. This is why we are committed to doing our own justice-focused work. This entails interrogating and understanding our individual attitudes, as well as ensuring that our company’s daily operations and hiring practices are aligned with our vision. We actively establish opportunities for restorative conflict resolution between groups and individuals in our community. Running a company that is equitable and inclusive is an ongoing process that requires constant commitment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/listings-project-product-ux-designer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/listings-project-product-ux-designer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 06:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 06:22:00 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/listings-project-product-ux-designer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/listings-project-product-ux-designer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0000/0020/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Big Cartel: iOS Development Lead</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0000/0020/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Salt Lake City, UT
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.bigcartel.com"&gt;https://www.bigcartel.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;We are looking for an experienced iOS developer to join our Product Engineering team. In this role, you’d work alongside the Web and Android teams to bring the Big Cartel admin experience to Apple platforms. In collaboration with designers, you'd help determine how Big Cartel’s design language translates to native platforms and craft user interfaces that are beautiful and functional. A track record of building and launching apps both independently and in a small team environment is a must for this position.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The "ideal" candidate&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Note: We’d still love to hear from you even if some of the below attributes don’t describe you, so long as you’re excited about Big Cartel and eager to contribute.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wants to build tools that make an impact on the lives of artists and creators&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can work alone or as part of a small team to build and launch ambitious projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has comprehensive knowledge of Apple frameworks and tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stays up to date with latest techniques and builds apps using modern approaches where possible (Swift, SwiftUI, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is able to build integrations with APIs including Restful JSON and GraphQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has experience with e-commerce platforms and payment processors like Stripe&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can balance and prioritize bug fixes, new features, and codebase maintenance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoys collaborating with support teams to debug and resolve customer issues in the wild&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understands techniques for monitoring and improving user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finds solace in automated testing, CI/CD&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reads the Apple HIG for fun&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/big-cartel-ios-development-lead"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/big-cartel-ios-development-lead&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 18:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 18:05:11 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/big-cartel-ios-development-lead</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/big-cartel-ios-development-lead</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/7605/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Merit America: Senior Data Engineer </title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/7605/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Washington, DC
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://meritamerica.org"&gt;https://meritamerica.org&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Role Overview&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The primary mission of the Senior Data Engineer is to fully design and build a fully new data warehouse and data pipelines to help Merit America  accurately understand progress against key metrics, support learners and managers across the organization and enable services that make a positive impact across Merit America.  The Senior Data Engineer will champion the value of good data and help teams make the most of their data. The Senior Data Engineer will work primarily with product engineers and data analysts while supporting all teams across Merit America.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data Enablement&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Architect and maintain data warehouse to a high data quality for Analytics and Master Data Management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and maintain ETL pipelines using Alteryx and SQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support new data engineering requirements across the project lifecycle: initial project definition, planning, implementation, and testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data Strategy&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make design decisions on architecture that leads to efficient, responsible and easy to access data across all aspects of the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor data integrity across the organization and continuously enhance processes to improve data quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify, design, and implement internal process improvements: automating manual processes, optimizing data delivery, re-designing infrastructure for greater scalability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trusted Partner&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate with Salesforce Administrator and Engineering Lead to maintain high level of data quality and meet uptime goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document procedures for data quality across the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assemble large, complex data sets that meet business requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skills/Qualifications&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;We know that  women and people of color are often less likely to apply to a position if they don’t match 100% of the job qualifications.  Don’t let that be the reason you miss out on this opportunity!  We encourage you to apply if you can demonstrate many of these skills and competencies.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of SQL experience required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of Alteryx experience preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong track record of building and optimizing ‘big data’ data pipelines, architectures and data sets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion and savvy for communicating about technical requirements with non-technical audiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of using workflow management platforms (eg: Airflow)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keen interest in data analytic skills working with structured and unstructured datasets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Salesforce knowledge preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Python knowledge preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dedication to building new data capabilities for a growing organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sense of deep personal responsibility for our collective success&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Details/Logistics&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This position is fulltime&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The annual salary for this role is $127,500&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is a remote position&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;All employees receive the following perks:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Phone stipend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tech stipend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personal development stipend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Home office supplies stipend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition to the above, full time employees receive the following benefits:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, Dental and Vision Insurance (100% Paid Employee Only Coverage)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible Spending Account and Health Savings Account&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health reimbursement Account fully funded by Merit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education reimbursement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Short and long-term disability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited PTO (and yes we require you to use it)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid Parental Leave and Adoption benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10 federally recognized holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 Week Holiday Office Closure in December/January&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) retirement plan with company automatic Merit contribution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employee Assistance Program | Talkspace | Sanvello&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remote Work &amp;amp; Sponsorship&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Candidates must reside within the U.S. and have full authorization to work in the U.S. In addition, Merit America doesn't offer employment visa sponsorship. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Equal Opportunity Statement&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Building an inclusive, high-performing team that is diverse across lines of personal identity is integral to our success and we are proud to be an equal opportunity employer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;This means we do not discriminate against any job applicant or employee because of their race, ethnicity, color, religion, national origin, sex, disability status, genetics, protected veteran status, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, age or any other characteristic protected by federal, state or local laws. This applies to all terms and conditions of employment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We actively strive and evolve to develop and maintain workspaces that are fully inclusive. We encourage candidates from underrepresented groups to apply.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Still excited about our work?  You can learn more about our work in &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/OZ_A82n9tTQ"&gt;this video&lt;/a&gt; we made with our founding partner, Google.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;E-Verify Statement&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;This employer participates in E-Verify and will provide the federal government with your Form I-9 information to confirm that you are authorized to work in the U.S. If E-Verify cannot confirm that you are authorized to work, this employer is required to give you written instructions and an opportunity to contact Department of Homeland Security (DHS) or Social Security Administration (SSA) so you can begin to resolve the issue before the employer can take any action against you, including terminating your employment. Employers can only use E-Verify once you have accepted a job offer and completed the I-9 Form. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/merit-america-senior-data-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/merit-america-senior-data-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 13:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 13:17:30 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/merit-america-senior-data-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/merit-america-senior-data-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitStarz Casino: Motion Designer (Central European Time Zone)</title>
      <region>Europe Only</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Malta
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://bitstarz.com"&gt;https://bitstarz.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;BitStarz is looking for a highly talented Motion Graphic Designer to join our team. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Experience in casino or games industry&lt;br&gt;After Effects - Adobe Creative Cloud (+ any other common motion graphic design software).&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Work with the current design team to deliver content within tight timelines.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Must be organized and work quickly and efficiently.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;A strong portfolio of motion graphics work.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advantageous:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Experience in creating HTML 5 banners&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Knowledge of video editing.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why BitStarz?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Competitive salaries &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;International health insurance&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Annual team building events at luxury 5-star resorts  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The opportunity to work from anywhere in the world &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;A €5,000 p.a. travel allowance to visit colleagues across the globe&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;A fast paced start-up culture, where we believe people are our biggest asset &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The opportunity to work at a dynamic crypto focussed casino amongst industry leaders&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/bitstarz-casino-motion-designer-central-european-time-zone"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/bitstarz-casino-motion-designer-central-european-time-zone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 13:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 13:03:53 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/bitstarz-casino-motion-designer-central-european-time-zone</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/bitstarz-casino-motion-designer-central-european-time-zone</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/7837/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>amazee.io: DevOps Engineer </title>
      <region>Americas Only</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/7837/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Zurich, Switzerland 
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://amazee.io"&gt;https://amazee.io&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Grüezi, Howdy, and G’day! We’re &lt;a href="http://amazee.io/"&gt;amazee.io, &lt;/a&gt;a ZeroOps application delivery hub for engineering teams to deploy applications more easily. Our developer-centric, open source platform makes developers’ lives and jobs easier, minimizing the stress of managing infrastructure or operations. amazee.io supports organizations across the globe to accelerate their cloud and container adoption, along with providing easily managed Kubernetes for developer teams. We run anywhere in the world, with 24/7/365 dedicated support. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re looking for a DevOps Engineer to join our remote team. As a DevOps Engineer with amazee.io you’ll be supporting our mission by engineering, managing and maintaining our hosting platform and infrastructure, allowing secure and scalable hosting. You’ll also be central to the future development of our services, looking for continuous improvement to the platform and supporting the roll out of new features and releases to keep us at the cutting edge of what we do. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you feel like this could be the role for you, then come and join a team of open source enthusiasts, committed to providing flexible hosting solutions in an open, transparent work environment, and having fun doing it.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be doing: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Onboarding and training clients on our platform, as well as providing them with post onboarding virtual support &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Guiding trouble free deployments of client projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specifying, implementing, documenting, and rolling out of features/updates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep diving into engineering and architecture topics, supporting the improvement and growth of our products and services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensuring the stability of our hosting environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implementing, practicing and advocating DevOps practices and methods &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicating via gifs and emojis&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Tech you’ll be using on the daily: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kubernetes, Docker, AWS, Terraform, PHP, MySQL, nodejs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll bring: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Production experience working with Kubernetes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfort working within Cloud environments (AWS, GCP, Azure)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands on experience designing and engineering microservices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience system engineering in/with Linux, Nginx, Varnish, MariaDB/MySQL and PHP, Docker &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfort communicating and documenting in English &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Work location:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Location is not important, although we have a preference for an Americas time zone for your working hours&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;amazee.io is dedicated to providing a work environment of trust, transparency, and inclusion for everyone. As a fully remote company we offer flexibility when it comes to working hours and location, but that’s not all, here’s some other things you can expect from us.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we’ll bring:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A fully distributed team of creative colleagues in a flat, open and transparent organization &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible working hours, and time off in lieu when you work more than you should&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote working &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 paid days off a year for conference attendance or education related commitments &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An annual education benefit of $1,500 or equivalent to dedicate to your professional development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An annual wellbeing benefit of $500 or equivalent to dedicate to your physical or mental health &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A connectivity benefit of $100 or equivalent a month, to help with internet/data costs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your own tech budget with the freedom to choose your setup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sweet, sweet Swag - Hoodies and other goodies &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;amazee.io Quest!&lt;/strong&gt; - After 3 years, you’ll get 3 weeks paid off work to undertake a profound personal goal, or undertake a bucket list type challenge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So what’s next?: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Apply! Send us your CV and cover letter showcasing who you are, your technical skills, and anything else you think we should know! &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The amazee.io Team.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/amazee-io-devops-engineer-2"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/amazee-io-devops-engineer-2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 10:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 10:51:07 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/amazee-io-devops-engineer-2</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/amazee-io-devops-engineer-2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0017/0504/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Designlab: Product Design Mentor</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Contract</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0017/0504/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Remote
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://trydesignlab.com"&gt;https://trydesignlab.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;🎉 Our mission is to build the best experience in the world for learning creative skills online. We’re doing this through courses that combine project-based learning with 1-on-1 mentorship from the best professionals in the industry. That's where you come in.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Designlab’s courses focus on web, UX and UI design. As a Designlab mentor, you will work with amazing students from around the world; connect to other top designers; and earn money while giving back to the design community. If your application is successful, you will be paired with students whose availability matches yours and you will mentor them through the duration of their course.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🎯 Mentor Responsibilities:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leave online feedback about your students' project work within 48 hrs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct 1:1 video sessions with your students (via Skype/Zoom/Hangouts etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate student progress according to the student’s course goals—assist with weekly lesson planning/time management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help students with any topics or issues they’re currently struggling with&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide guidance on professional development—overall sanity check&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure that the quality of the deliverables is as high as it can be based on the student goals. For example, if a student wants to do a career change into UX we would expect you to be more rigorous with this student than with one who's just learning a new skill for fun&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;🌈 Experience:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of UX/UI design experience, senior or manager experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong English communication skills, both written and spoken&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong problem-solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for education, design, and creative work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;At Designlab, we know that building a diverse, equitable and inclusive team empowers our community to achieve beyond the ordinary. We are committed to celebrating our differences as they are core to ensuring that our journey is both unique and powerful.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/designlab-product-design-mentor-1"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/designlab-product-design-mentor-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 18:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 18:13:53 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/designlab-product-design-mentor-1</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/designlab-product-design-mentor-1</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/8865/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Create Ape, inc.: UX Copywriter</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Contract</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/8865/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Irvine, California
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://createape.com/"&gt;https://createape.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Are you a UX ninja ready to break out of the corporate world?  Want to work for a fun and slightly nerdy crew that lets you flex your creative muscles and build a super diverse portfolio?  Then we’ve got a spot for you here at CreateApe!  We’re a full-service UX/UI agency that’s growing fast and making waves in the digital design world.  Join our fully remote team of design and development experts from all around the world and get rid of that boring office commute.  We want to invest in YOU and your UX career – meaning the more you contribute and become an integral part of our team, the more room for professional growth.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;This is a fully remote position, not restricted by commutes or a particular geographic area.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Office hours: Monday through Friday, 9AM - 5PM Pacific Time &lt;/strong&gt;(&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;PST UTC-8&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;), this position requires individuals to be available for meetings and duties during this window.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;At CreateApe, UX Copywriters collaborate with our Designers, Project Managers and Developers.  We are looking for an expert copywriter that can support our design team by creating content for emails, blog posts, managing social media, and more.  At CreateApe, we invest in YOU, and if you are able to contribute to and become an integral part of our team, there’s plenty of room for growth.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you’re missing some of the requirements below, don’t sweat it. Send us an application anyway and we’ll take a look and reach out to you if the fit is right.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Craft copy for email marketing campaigns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write website and mobile application copy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publish blog posts each month&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage social media, including crafting and scheduling content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other writing as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who You Are: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of the English language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adaptability to change voice and tone to suit client needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of digital marketing best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with social media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organizational skills and attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to collaborate effectively with both internal and external teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portfolio of writing samples that are enjoyable to read and have driven conversations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Not Required, But Helpful to Have&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Figma, PowerPoint, Slack, Google Docs, Microsoft Word&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical writing experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with creating RFPs (former sales careerists, we’re looking at you)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/create-ape-inc-ux-copywriter"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/create-ape-inc-ux-copywriter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 23:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:14:13 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/create-ape-inc-ux-copywriter</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/create-ape-inc-ux-copywriter</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maharishi Foundation International: Design System Specialist</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; London (Remote)
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.maharishi.foundation/"&gt;https://www.maharishi.foundation/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Maharishi Foundation International (MFI) is a US-registered non-profit that supports the development of new technologies and outreach opportunities for the worldwide Transcendental Meditation® (TM®) organisations. Over the past 60 years, more than 10 million people worldwide have learned the TM technique through personal instruction by tens of thousands of certified teachers. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;MFI is a growing, fully remote team of nearly 50 people, located around the globe but mainly in North America and Europe. As an organisation we are committed to leveraging modern technology and progressive management practices to make the TM technique and its related programmes more available to people everywhere. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We favor a healthy and balanced work environment with opportunities for personal development.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are seeking a talented and passionate Design System Specialist to join our team to be responsible for managing design systems and driving visual experience across our new mobile app and other projects. You will be part of a growing design team, working closely also with our product and tech team, to improve and maintain a meditation mobile application. You will participate in and oversee a variety of projects and collaborate with members of cross functional teams to conceptualize, prototype and design usable, useful and beautiful user interfaces. This role is remote and reports to the team lead in Berlin. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About You&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You are a customer-focused, detail-oriented, creative UI designer who tackles complex problems with deep brand awareness and refined aesthetics. You have experience with various digital initiatives and you’ve designed several mobile and web applications in the past. You should have experience designing web components for mobile and desktop use, and with creating and maintaining design systems in general. You can produce interactive prototypes and test them with users in a rigorous, data-driven way. You can demonstrate a command of usability and accessibility standards in partnership with visual and interface design principles. You have a broad experience and a deep understanding of people’s behaviour to recommend UI solutions to customer needs. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and refine visual design for our interfaces and digital products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the creation, maintenance, and extension of a unified, flexible design system for our digital products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate and set best practices and visual design standards. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design useful, usable, and desirable interfaces while considering research findings, business goals and requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with stakeholders on translating brand identity into design for our products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with our Engineering team on making sure designs are implemented correctly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skills and Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-6 years of experience as a UI Designer within a large-scale consumer facing organization, digital agency or media company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Broad experience in designing web and mobile apps and ability to create lightweight prototypes for testing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in designing web and mobile components, and creating, maintaining, and extending design systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with designers and developers in an agile work environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep care about aesthetics and a great eye for typography, layout and visual design in general.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong track record backed by an outstanding portfolio showcasing latest works.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in best practices for mobile design, as well as strong knowledge of usability principles and techniques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of HTML &amp;amp; CSS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Storybook is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, presentation, and interpersonal skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English (written and verbal).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work autonomously and remotely.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motivated for self-improvement and a healthy lifestyle, and open to / interested in meditation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you are passionate about this work but do not have all of the skills listed we are still interested in speaking with you and encourage you to apply!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pay and benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our pay levels are set according to a formula that combines above-median market rate data for the role (we pay 55th percentile of market rate for this role, based on &lt;a href="https://www.payscale.com/"&gt;Payscale&lt;/a&gt; data) adjusted for your local cost of living based on &lt;a href="https://www.numbeo.com/cost-of-living/rankings_current.jsp"&gt;Numbeo&lt;/a&gt; data.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We take the issue of equitable pay very seriously, and we apply our pay formula to all workers who work 80% or more of full time hours with us.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diversity and inclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We care about diversity - we strive to ensure all of our team feel included and can bring their whole selves to work but we also know that this work is never ‘done’ or complete, and that we can always improve.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our team is fully remote, living and working across 20 countries across the world, and we’d love to hear how you can add to our special culture at MFI.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/maharishi-foundation-international-design-system-specialist"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/maharishi-foundation-international-design-system-specialist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 16:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 16:33:27 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/maharishi-foundation-international-design-system-specialist</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/maharishi-foundation-international-design-system-specialist</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Springboard: Mentor - UI/UX Design Career Track (Part-time/Remote)</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Contract</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; San Francisco, CA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.springboard.com/"&gt;https://www.springboard.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Company &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;At Springboard, we’re on a mission to bridge the world’s skills gap, offering transformative online education in data science, UI/UX design, machine learning, and coding. Our courses may be tech-enabled, but we're ultimately human-centric: each student taps into a vast community throughout their time with us, engaging with fellow students, industry-expert mentors, student advisors, and career coaches, the goal of which is to successfully transition students into their dream job. Through this hybrid approach, we’ve helped thousands of learners revamp their careers and, by extension, their lives, with hundreds of top-notch job offers received every year and a near-perfect placement rate for our program graduates.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Opportunity&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Springboard runs an online, self-paced UI/UX Design Career Track in which participants learn with the help of a curated curriculum and 1-1 guidance from an expert mentor. Our mentor community is the biggest strength of our programs with a Net Promoter Score rated as world class.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you are as passionate about mentoring as you are about UX and UI, and can give a few hours per week in return for an honorarium, we would love to hear from you.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What does mentoring mean at Springboard?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Mentoring encompasses many levels of support at Springboard. We believe in giving a personalized approach to mentoring students. What this looks like is grading student deliverables on a weekly basis, offering detailed feedback, teaching/modeling concepts that are challenging for students, and/or giving them career pointers about the industry. Depending on your mentees you’ll lean on a teaching approach, being a motivator, advisor, or you may have high level conversions to guide them throughout the course. A mix of diverse students, skills, and abilities offers opportunities to renew your skills or take your skills to the next level. Mentors have said it’s a rewarding opportunity to grow professionally and make a lasting impact. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Please reach out to us with any questions at mentorrecruiting@springboard.com :-)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Program:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Completely online&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-paced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Students become proficient in UI/UX with the help of a curated online curriculum, an industry design project, and project-based deliverables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coursework is made up of 700+ hour expert-curated curriculum&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On average, students finish in 9 months&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Students are working professionals from all over the world, dedicated to switching careers into UI/UX Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Students have a weekly 30-minute checkin with their mentor to discuss questions, projects, and career advice!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Students communicate with mentors outside of calls on an as-needed basis to support learning and career objectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are as passionate about teaching design as about design itself&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are proficient in the topics covered in our&lt;a href="https://www.springboard.com/workshops/ui-ux-design-career-track/"&gt; UI/UX Design Career Track&lt;/a&gt; (we are looking for designers who have equal experience in UI and UX)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have at least 3 years of relevant work experience, and a high quality  portfolio to showcasing your UI and UX skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are available for weekly, 30-minute video check-ins for each student to help them set and achieve learning goals, provide feedback, and help them move towards getting a job&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are able to utilize Zoom for the 30-minute calls with students&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are available outside of weekly calls for each student to review projects and answer questions as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have experience critiquing work, in particular giving meaningful feedback on visual/UI design, and be able to think on your feet quickly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are empathetic and have excellent communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Membership in a rich community of expert mentors from great companies like AirBnB, Uber, Google, and Pivotal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Change the lives of students in our program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help us revolutionize online education!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UI/UX career track mentors are paid an honorarium between $20.50-$37.50 per 30 minute call with students&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work at your convenience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;We are an equal opportunity employer and value diversity at our company. We welcome applications from all backgrounds, and do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;California Privacy Rights Notice for Job Applicants&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Under the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”), Springboard is required to inform California residents who are job applicants about the categories of personal information we collect about you and the purposes for which we will use this information. This &lt;a href="https://www.springboard.com/archeio/download/841f959e9c964e93a87abe993316cc1f/"&gt;notice&lt;/a&gt; contains disclosures required by the CCPA and applies only to personal information that is subject to the CCPA.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/springboard-mentor-ui-ux-design-career-track-part-time-remote"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/springboard-mentor-ui-ux-design-career-track-part-time-remote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:19:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:19:53 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/springboard-mentor-ui-ux-design-career-track-part-time-remote</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/springboard-mentor-ui-ux-design-career-track-part-time-remote</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0071/4772/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Atlas Obscura: Digital Product Designer</title>
      <region>North America Only</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0071/4772/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; New York City - Remote First
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://atlasobscura.com"&gt;http://atlasobscura.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Atlas Obscura is seeking a Digital Product Designer to join our expanding team. Reporting to the VP of Product, the Digital Product Designer will be responsible for creating engaging online user experiences and for providing thoughtful design solutions to grow our business. If you have a passion for inspiring, elegant, forward-thinking visual design and an enthusiasm for user research, prototyping, and interaction design, then we want to hear from you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Atlas Obscura is a remote-first company, so you can work from anywhere within the United States or Canada.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own the user experience for all digital touchpoints, including the responsive website, email, notifications, and more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recommend approach and conduct user research with external users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define, prototype and validate solutions with external users and internal stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build production ready assets and designs for our cross-platform digital experiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with our Product Managers and Engineers in all phases of agile product development, from discovery to delivery to iteration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with our Head of Design to build best-in-class, on-brand experiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and evolve our digital design system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of experience successfully designing digital products in an Agile product development environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience creating an inspiring user experience for desktop and mobile devices as well as native mobile apps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise with Figma and the Adobe Creative Suite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills and the ability to confidently share your work at any stage of your process with a variety of internal audiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Robust prototyping skills and user research experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fantastic visual design skills (e.g.; layout, composition, typography, color) showcased through a refined and inspiring portfolio.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A willingness to give and receive feedback and an openness to follow creative direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A passion for Atlas Obscura’s mission of inspiring wonder and curiosity about the incredible world we all share.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;Compensation is competitive and includes equity. Benefits for full-time employees include family health, dental, and vision plans and a generous vacation policy. At Atlas Obscura we believe exploration is for everyone and encourage diverse applicants. We are committed to an equitable hiring process and an inclusive work environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To apply for this role, please submit your resume, portfolio, and cover letter detailing your qualifications and interest at the following link: https://atlasobscura.applytojob.com/apply/QdYw42qHXA/Digital-Product-Designer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;About Atlas Obscura&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Atlas Obscura is an award-winning travel company founded in 2009. Widely celebrated for building the definitive, community-driven guide to the world's hidden wonders, the company also offers unique online and in-person experiences, produces once-in-a-lifetime trips, and has published two New York Times bestselling books with more than a million copies in print. Atlas Obscura has been nominated for three National Magazine Awards, a James Beard Award, three Webby Awards, and in 2020 was named one of Inc. 5000’s fastest growing companies. Having raised a $20M, Series B led by Airbnb last summer, Atlas Obscura is well-positioned for growth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/atlas-obscura-digital-product-designer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/atlas-obscura-digital-product-designer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 17:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 17:40:21 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/atlas-obscura-digital-product-designer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/atlas-obscura-digital-product-designer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0071/4150/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>A.Team: Senior Independent UX/UI Designer ($110-$190/hr)</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Contract</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0071/4150/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; NYC, SF, and TLV
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://build.a.team/viaweworkremotely"&gt;https://build.a.team/viaweworkremotely&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="https://build.a.team/wwrdesignerfasttrack"&gt;A·Team&lt;/a&gt; is a VC-backed, stealth, application-only home on the internet for senior UX/UI designers (along with developers &amp;amp; product folks) to team up with the hand-picked, high-growth companies on their next big thing. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After talking with hundreds of independent engineers, designers, and product folks, we heard over and over that finding vetted, high-quality, consistent clients is hard, and projects are often too small to be rewarding. A·Team matches small teams of the most talented builders in the world with companies backed by a16z, YC, Softbank, General Catalyst, etc. on a contract basis for many of their most important initiatives. We quietly launched in May 2020, and have helped A·Teamers earn $11.4+ million since.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As part of A·Team, you can expect:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;High-paying, meaningful UX/UI design missions with the most audacious companies&lt;/strong&gt; sent your way; generally $110-$190/hr, with vetted, fascinating clients doing work that matters. We're picky about who we partner with; new clients only come in via trusted referral. We've worked with Lyft, McGraw Hill, ClearCo, irl.com, the former CEO of Waze, the leading vaccine production software, several new unicorns we can't say here, and dozens of startups backed by a16z/YC/Softbank/etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Work alongside friends old &amp;amp; new: &lt;/strong&gt;our niche is small/diverse product teams, since clients with larger budgets and higher-impact work tell us they want teams, not individuals. Of course, we keep friends together whenever we can.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Full autonomy:&lt;/strong&gt; say "no" to things that don't excite you. The most talented builders often juggle a few things at once, so there's never pressure to join an A·Team mission if you don't have the bandwidth. If we're no longer a fit, it's easy to leave or pause too. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Small, curated, off-the-record gatherings:&lt;/strong&gt; for conversations hard to have elsewhere. Long-term, we're creating micro-communities for the world's top builders to become friends around the things they care about.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Keep 100% of what you earn: &lt;/strong&gt;if you charge $130/hr, you get $130/hr. A·Team makes money by charging a small, flat, transparent platform fee on &lt;em&gt;top&lt;/em&gt; of your rate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to apply:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Go here: &lt;a href="https://build.a.team/wwrdesignerfasttrack"&gt;https://build.a.team/wwrdesignerfasttrack&lt;/a&gt; + mention WWR under how you heard about A·Team. No resume or cover letter needed; we respect your time so the application is short. We're also much more interested in seeing what you've made, and excited to chat more if there’s a fit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What you’ll do:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once part of A.Team, you’ll regularly be invited to be the lead designer for impactful missions that match your interests, which you can accept or decline. Take your pick from early-stage incubations with world-class founders, to fast-growing super-funded companies, to old-school non-tech incumbents looking to build as a tech giant would.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Missions usually involve building an ambitious piece of software from 0 to 1 as part of a small 3-4 person team. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ll be paid to scope it out, give the client options, guide strategy, and execute on the selected solution. Sometimes the client has a clear vision, sometimes not; which is why A.Team builders tend to be senior folks who can work together to find the right direction. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who A&lt;/strong&gt;·&lt;strong&gt;Team is for:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Senior UX/UI Designers who left large companies and high-growth startups to pursue their craft with autonomy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Those who prefer consistent contract work over a full-time role, who want to create a variety of new products alongside other top-tier builders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The majority of A.Teamers spend most of their time doing independent work, but a sizeable percentage are either employed full-time (but testing out client work), bootstrapping a side project, or looking for their next big thing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who A&lt;/strong&gt;·&lt;strong&gt;Team is &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; for:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;People looking for small gigs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Folks looking to build simple wordpress/wix/squarespace-style websites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Those still early in their careers and recent university/bootcamp grads (at least not yet).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our long-term vision:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://build.a.team/wwrdesignerfasttrack"&gt;A·Team&lt;/a&gt; is a new type of company for a new kind of independent software builders. We call them "unhirables": people who traditional companies couldn’t hire full-time even if they wanted to, but who want to do their most meaningful work with their favorite people in small, autonomous, distributed expert teams. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;To help us secure amazing missions, we raised $5 million+ (not public, yet) from NFX, Village Global, and Box Group, along with the former CEO of Upwork, the founders of Fiverr and Lemonade, Apple's Global Head of Recruiting, YC Partner Aaron Harris, Wharton's Adam Grant, and Duke's Dan Ariely.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/a-team-senior-independent-ux-ui-designer-110-190-hr"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/a-team-senior-independent-ux-ui-designer-110-190-hr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 23:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 23:05:33 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/a-team-senior-independent-ux-ui-designer-110-190-hr</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/a-team-senior-independent-ux-ui-designer-110-190-hr</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0018/4213/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Aurora Solar: Product Designer</title>
      <region>North America Only</region>
      <category>Design</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0018/4213/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; San Francisco, CA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://aurorasolar.com"&gt;https://aurorasolar.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;About the role:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aurora Solar is a fast-growing Series C company on a mission to create a future of solar energy for all. Aurora makes the software that is enabling society to transition to a world powered by solar power. It’s our goal to have every solar installation in the world pass through our software, which has already been used to design millions of solar projects. Named one of “The Best Places To Work in 2021” by &lt;a href="https://www.builtinsf.com/company/aurora-solar"&gt;BuiltInSF.com&lt;/a&gt; and awarded #1 Solar Software platform by Solar Power World, Aurora is disrupting the energy industry and changing the course of history. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a Product Designer, you’ll drive research, design, and best practices for our growing product. We’re looking for a systems-level thinker with a dedication to craft who enjoys collaborating with product management, engineering, and other designers to create intuitive, delightful, and innovative experiences.  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are a passionate and diverse team that aspires to be the best place for the best people and we’re looking for talented individuals to accelerate our exponential growth as we continue to scale. If you are looking for a stimulating and fulfilling role, come join us!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll do&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create solutions that make the process of designing and selling solar easy and intuitive for solar professionals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive solutions towards the articulated vision through an iterative and collaborative process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in maintaining and updating the design system for our product suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner closely with cross-functional teams to develop elegant solutions that delight our users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive product design process from research, high level user journeys, concepts, wireframes, and prototypes all the way to excellent visual execution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rapidly produce pixel-perfect and low-fidelity concepts and prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inform and guide the work of team members  by providing clear, helpful, and actionable feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate user observations and interviews to uncover insights and create an exceptional user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we value&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience shipping responsive web and/or mobile applications &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent visual designer who cares about delivering meaningful beauty with a great eye and passion for aesthetics and design systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portfolio that showcases a systems-level approach to solutions with attention to beauty&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dedication to craft and ability to iterate rapidly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to conduct user research, user interviews, usability testing, and to know when each is needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great communicator who can design frameworks to help us find opportunities, brainstorm and illustrate concepts, and effectively showcase stories&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with animation and complex transitions is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building out complex consumer-grade B2B products is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aurora is dedicated to building a diverse and inclusive workforce of people who believe in and are passionate about creating a future of solar energy for all. We are an equal opportunity employer, we welcome and consider qualified applicants regardless of gender identity, sexual orientation, race, religion, age, national origin, citizenship, pregnancy status, veteran status, or any other differences. We encourage you to apply even if you believe that you do not meet all of the above criteria!&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aurora-solar-product-designer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aurora-solar-product-designer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 00:33:25 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aurora-solar-product-designer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aurora-solar-product-designer</link>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
