<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss">
  <channel>
    <title>We Work Remotely: Front-End Programming Jobs</title>
    <link>https://weworkremotely.com/categories/remote-front-end-programming-jobs.rss</link>
    <description>We Work Remotely: Front-End Programming Jobs</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0074/7274/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Toggl: Remote Frontend Developer (JavaScript + React)</title>
      <region>Europe Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0074/7274/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Tallinn, Estonia
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://toggl.com/jobs/"&gt;https://toggl.com/jobs/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We are looking for a Frontend Developer to join our engineering team as we have too many ideas and not enough developers :-)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;The salary for this position is &lt;strong&gt;€63,000&lt;/strong&gt; annually, plus great benefits (see below). We are committed to increasing salaries every year based on company and individual performance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;You can work &lt;strong&gt;from anywhere in Europe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;About the team&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Toggl Hire is on a mission to revolutionize the way hiring happens. We are big believers that modern day recruiting should be effortless and enjoyable. That means no more resumes or cover letters, no more endless hours screening through applications, no more interpreting past roles into current experience, no more bias and gut feeling, but informed decisions based on data.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We are a fully remote team, with headquarters in Tallinn, Estonia. We are highly skilled, highly motivated, and most importantly, a fun, friendly bunch. We value transparency, communication and results over effort and excuses. We have regular in-person meetups all over the world!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;The engineering team has a Product Manager, a Designer, a Lead Engineer, 3 frontend and 3 backend developers. We also help the other 2 developers focusing on the growth experiments and their Product Manager.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We have been recently named as one of the best remote companies to work at.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;As a Frontend Developer your main responsibilities will be:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working independently with minimal supervision and handholding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building and maintaining product features, ensuring performance, security and scalability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finding best possible technical solution for new features implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributing to technical design and architecture with a steep growth in mind&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Doing code reviews or researching and implementing new tools when needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;About you/Requirements&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You will fit in well in our team if:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have demonstrated strong experience working with large SaaS data infrastructure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are a great team-player and communicator when working with anyone from engineers to specialists like product managers and when working with other teams, and with your manager and other stakeholders. You are responsive to feedback and always seek to learn and improve.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can come up with creative approaches to problem solving and can provide feedback to others on their work, be it your fellow developers, the designer or the product manager&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You always approach new challenges with a critical thinking mindset and make sure to look at the big picture.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You want to take ownership and work independently while being part of a tight-knit team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have efficient time management skills as well as the eagerness to learn new skills and tools are something you value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a strong engineering background and enjoy the startup life. You have seen many projects through from conception to delivery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;The main technologies you will be working with are:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript, Typescript, React, GraphQL, Heroku, AWS, CircleCI.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We use Golang and PostgreSQL in the backend.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Freedom to choose when and how much you work - we only measure results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;24 days of paid time off a year, plus your local holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-person meetups for team-building (expenses covered)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-6 weeks paid sabbatical (depending on the tenure)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Laptop budget up to €2,500 and it renews every 3 years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;€2,000 budget to set up your home office, and additional €300 every year after 3 years of tenure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;€250 per month for co-working space membership and/or internet service at home&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;€4,000 per year contribution to use for training, workshops, and conferences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;€2,000 per year contribution for any equipment or services to improve and/or maintain your physical and mental health&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support for buying tools you need for doing your best work (even eyeglasses if you need a new pair)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/toggl-remote-frontend-developer-javascript-react-1"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/toggl-remote-frontend-developer-javascript-react-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 11:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 11:44:10 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/toggl-remote-frontend-developer-javascript-react-1</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/toggl-remote-frontend-developer-javascript-react-1</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/9513/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Shape: Senior iOS Developer</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/9513/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Copenhagen, Denmark
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://shape.dk"&gt;https://shape.dk&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Shape is an award-winning native app development studio. We are known for building high-quality mobile apps that tackle real problems and push businesses forward.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;At Shape, you will work with talented designers and developers to build awesome digital products. You will put your existing skills to good use, and learn new ones by working together with other skilled people.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re looking for a Senior iOS Developer to join a new remote-first team of developers from all over the world.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The opportunity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;In this role, you will join a new remote-first team of developers distributed across the world. You will work closely with your peers to build world class products - all the way from proposal to release. You will architect high-impact solutions using the newest technologies and execute them against a set of success-criteria. You will also:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Step up to resolve product issues - large and small.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tackle everything from huge new features to important bug fixes, from start to finish.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take ownership of major features and lead their maintenance and improvements over time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with peers remotely during brainstorms, technical design discussions, design reviews and code reviews.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you will bring to Shape&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid experience with developing native iOS apps using Swift and the iOS SDK.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for writing pragmatic, performant and testable code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skills to lead and collaborate on high-impact and complex projects from proposal through release.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently and be self-driven in all aspects of your work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills. We’re a distributed team, so frequent and clear communication is a must.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why join Shape?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;History of success.  &lt;/strong&gt;For over a decade, we have brought impactful digital products to life and while we are not in it for the accolades, it is nice to be recognised for what you do. With over 50 national and international awards and honors under our belts, it shows we are doing something right in our quest to deliver results for those we work with.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Be on the front line of progress and innovation.  &lt;/strong&gt;We are passionate about building great products using the latest technology while creating reusable components, empowering teams to ship apps faster and with better user experience.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;International team.  &lt;/strong&gt;Shape is very international and so far includes people from over 30 different countries. Our company language is English.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Take charge of your schedule.  &lt;/strong&gt;You will join a remote-first team working asynchronously giving you the freedom and flexibility to organize your own work schedules.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Work/life balance&lt;/strong&gt;.  From day one, we have been committed to making a place where people can do the best work in a meaningful way. This means working reasonable hours, spending each day in a welcoming environment, and taking time off when you need it. We believe in doing everything we can to help our people live healthy and full lives while doing work that makes a tangible difference.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we have to offer you&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A team of exceptional developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6 weeks vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A 37.5 hour work week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work from anywhere in the world&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take charge of your own schedule&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The opportunity to attend or present at global conferences and meetups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yearly company offsite with travel expenses paid&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The possibility to visit our office in Copenhagen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/shape-senior-ios-developer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/shape-senior-ios-developer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 15:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 15:24:58 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/shape-senior-ios-developer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/shape-senior-ios-developer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clevertech: Senior Frontend Developer - Javascript React</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; New York, NY
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://clevertech.biz"&gt;https://clevertech.biz&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Experience Remote done Right. Over 20 years of remote experience, all 500+ staff are 100% remote and we still grow vibrant relationships, provide exceptional opportunities for career growth while working with stellar clients on ambitious projects&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're working on:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Enterprise companies turn to us to help them launch innovative digital products that interact with hundreds of millions of customers, transactions and data points. The problems we solve every day are real and require creativity, grit and determination. We are building a culture that challenges norms while fostering experimentation and personal growth. In order to grasp the scale of problems we face, ideally, you have some exposure to Logistics, FinTech, Transportation, Insurance, Media or other complex multifactor industries&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7+ years of professional experience (A technical assessment will be required)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Senior-level experience with Javascript, React, Redux, Websockets, Async/Await&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create clean, modern, testable, well-documented code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;English fluency, verbal and written&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional, empathic, team player&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Problem solver, proactive, go getter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Straight from the Devs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Watch short snippets of actual developers (Real, not scripted) share why they joined &lt;a href="https://cleverte.ch/3"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YouTube Playlist&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Clevertech is an amazing place to work at&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;At Clevertech, you can expect that you will:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be 100% dedicated to one project at a time so that you can hone your skills, innovate and grow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a part of a team of talented and friendly senior-level developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on projects that allow you to use cutting edge tech. We believe in constantly evolving your mastery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;The result? We produce meaningful work and we are truly proud and excited to be creating waves in an industry under transformation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits of joining the Clevertech team&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We know that people do their best work when they’re taken care of. So we make sure to offer great benefits:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive Salaries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 Month Paid Time Off For You&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personal Development Fund&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tenure-Based Rewards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible Family Leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clevertech University&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clevertech Gives Back&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amazing Culture &amp;amp; Strong Community&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clevertech-senior-frontend-developer-javascript-react"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clevertech-senior-frontend-developer-javascript-react&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 13:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 13:48:10 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clevertech-senior-frontend-developer-javascript-react</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clevertech-senior-frontend-developer-javascript-react</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/9182/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Narrative: Web Software Engineer (Remote)</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/9182/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; New York, NY
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://narrative.io"&gt;https://narrative.io&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Web Software Engineer (Remote)&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What You Will Do&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Here's what you will do in a nutshell:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create new features for Narrative's Vuejs web application. Work with Product and Design teams to create the best user experience and create modular, maintainable components.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, implement and maintain embedded applications on Narrative's Data Marketplace which enhance the ability of customers to manage and manipulate data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help select technologies and define the strategic direction for our system architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on Narrative's Tacklebox UI library, designing creating reusable components and modules for use in all of Narrative's web applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review and evaluate team members' code contributions, delivering transparent, honest and direct feedback to your peers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;While most of the work focuses on the frontend, this position is ideal for someone who would like to improve his/her backend and Functional Programming skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technical Stack&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;In a nutshell, our technical stack looks like:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Frontend&lt;/strong&gt;: Vuejs, Sass, Pug, and Functional JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Backend&lt;/strong&gt;: scala, AWS, spark, Iceberg, cats, cats-effect, http4s, and doobie&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Ops&lt;/strong&gt;: EC2, Fargate, Lambda, Terraform, EMR, DynamoDB, S3, RDS, Step Functions, Jenkins, and Datadog&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;The Ideal Candidate&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are not looking for a 100% fit on all the technology buzzwords, but we are looking for someone with strong personal and technical skills who is eager to pick up new technologies as necessary. We are obviously going to expect much more from a senior candidate than we would from a junior one.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The ideal candidate should:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have extensive experience in one or more web frameworks (Vue, React, Angular etc.) and the ES6/JavaScript/HTML/CSS ecosystem.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have proven experience using Amazon Web Services to deploy and host web applications and databases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be able to debug various aspects of web application code, such as cross-browser Javascript quirks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thoroughly understand the HTTP lifecycle and how the browser interacts with web APIs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy building fast, user-friendly UIs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not be afraid of contributing to the entire stack when the need arises, given that frontend doesn’t simply mean HTML/CSS. For instance, a feature might require&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;some metrics to be computed from a Spark Report&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;creating a PostgreSQL migration script&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tweaking S3 permissions and terraform scripts for deployment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have the ability to lead the creation of architectural and design documents, collect requirements as well as feedback from the development and product teams and evalute new technologies as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive success in a flat organization with minimal process, interfacing with technical and non-technical team members as necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate potential technical issues to relevant teams and adapt to changing requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be mindful of the compromises that need to be done to be reactive on the business side while keeping the systems manageable in the long run.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Live/work within +/- 3 hours of EST&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Team (Remote US and Canada)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are a small, early stage, remote-first team looking for great developers who want to jump in and take major systems and user-facing features from design to launch.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our Mission&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are building a data streaming marketplace that makes it easy to buy, sell, and win.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We do this by creating tools that reduce the friction and increase transparency in the data buying process, creating a win-win relationship between buyers and sellers.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;You can learn more about Narrative by visiting https://www.narrative.io/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apply Now&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Apply by sending an email to &lt;a href="mailto:hiring-dev@narrative.io"&gt;hiring-dev@narrative.io&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you would like to have a chat to learn more about the company, our culture, or the team before formally applying, that's is fine too: just drop us a line at dev@narrative.io.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/narrative-web-software-engineer-remote"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/narrative-web-software-engineer-remote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 23:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 23:22:24 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/narrative-web-software-engineer-remote</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/narrative-web-software-engineer-remote</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/9155/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>EventMobi: Frontend Technical Team Lead - Remote</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/9155/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; 151 Yonge Street 11th Floor Toronto, Ontario M5C 2W7
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://eventmobi.com"&gt;https://eventmobi.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;** EventMobi is a remote-first company and this is a remote job. You may reside anywhere in the world to do this job. However, you must be willing to work during Eastern Standard Time business hours. The salary range for this role is between 60k - 90k CAD per annum. This posting is open to all candidates globally.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;WHY EVENTMOBI?&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;EventMobi is an award winning tech startup with offices in Toronto, Berlin and Manila and over 1500 clients across the globe.  We are on a mission to revolutionize how event planners create, market and manage their events. Millions of attendees around the world experience conferences and events with the help of EventMobi’s event tech platform including clients like Motorola, Ralph Lauren, Nestle, and Intel. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re looking for a Technical Lead to help us tackle challenging engineering problems in an evolving industry. Whether you want to build Progressive Web Apps, work with service &amp;amp; web workers, architectures to manage data services, or manage memory usage &amp;amp; latency of large scale Javascript applications, this is a role that requires you to think holistically about building the next generation of cross-platform mobile &amp;amp; web apps. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Ideally, you care about good architecture &amp;amp; design, quality, and scalability as part of your work. You enjoy leading and coaching individuals on your team and you're looking for a place where you can approach your problems creatively. You enjoy collaboration with an incredibly smart &amp;amp; talented team and are able to bring your expertise to help shape our technical vision and determine how we will execute on it.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If this sounds like just the role you've been hoping for, please apply and tell us more about yourself!​&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;WHAT YOUR WORK WILL FOCUS ON&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Mentorship&lt;/strong&gt; - One of the most senior software developers on staff.  Provide technical mentorship and assistance to a team of 4-7 developers, and create opportunities for professional development.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Technical Strategy&lt;/strong&gt; - Responsible for EventMobi’s overall software design, helping to align technology with business goals.  Lead research into new technology options, tools or patterns to discover opportunities to create new business value for EventMobi’s customers.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Architecture&lt;/strong&gt; - Empower and guide technical leads in product and application level architecture choices. Ensure consistency in technology choices and enable experimentation with new tools and approaches where appropriate to drive new business value.  Lead resolution of architecture and technology choices and challenges that cut across all teams. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Development Best Practices&lt;/strong&gt; - Hands on keyboard to provide clarity and support tech leads in expanding standards and writing clean code.  Pair with team members to solve the hardest coding challenges.  Contribute to continuous improvement in our software development processes as we take initiatives from concept, feasibility, and design to implementation, testing, and release.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Performance &amp;amp; Scale&lt;/strong&gt; - Build measurement frameworks for performance, scalability, etc, including setting expected standards of performance against those metrics in consultation with product management and business stakeholders.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;WHAT YOU WILL BRING TO THE TEAM &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience growing high performing software development teams focused on outcomes versus just outputs.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with long-term development, enhancement and maintenance of a SaaS application/platform. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skilled in guiding technology and architecture choices with a focus on delivering business value&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest in leading the evolution of an existing code base and architecture versus solely focusing on green field development.   &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Mobile and Web development (a true polyglot), ideally with proven skills working with React and Capacitor, Python, and RESTful APIs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have start-up experience; big company experience okay in combination, but not exclusively&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge about React and web development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2-3 years of experience managing a team (at least 2 reports, preferably a larger team or multiple teams) of React developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A passion for development and solving problems, and a desire to be actively involved in writing code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ideas about everything, the resolve to convey your point clearly, and the graciousness to listen to alternate ideas and choose the best option. You’re constantly thinking “how can we do this better?”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience maintaining Jira and managing the lifecycle of tickets in a cross-team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data-driven decision making and experience guiding a team in selecting and achieving realistic-yet-challenging OKRs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A passion for growing and supporting your team through 1:1 meetings, mentorship and coaching, and working on career progression plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to think about the big-picture roadmap and technical vision of the product, and integrate those plans into near-term sprint planning and project architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Confidence in running standups, sprint planning, backlog grooming, and retrospective meetings that align with the company roadmap while balancing maintenance and the needs of the team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eagerness to work with a team of strong, fun-loving developers that love to learn from and teach each other&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of DevOps &amp;amp; Infrastructure (AWS) is nice to have&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;WHAT WILL YOU GET FROM EVENTMOBI?&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We offer the experience of a lifetime working with a dynamic, open-minded and diverse team, who are excited to come to work every day and passionate about what they do and the clients they help&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive compensation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company Stock-Options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A modern MacBook Pro to use for work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A great culture with much more along the way&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;REMOTE WORKSPACE REQUIREMENTS: &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a safe, comfortable, and ergonomic workspace and working environment - a private and quiet workspace is vital for doing your best work!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a reliable internet connection capable of participating in video calls, with at least 30Mbps download speed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/eventmobi-frontend-technical-team-lead-remote"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/eventmobi-frontend-technical-team-lead-remote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 20:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 20:04:27 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/eventmobi-frontend-technical-team-lead-remote</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/eventmobi-frontend-technical-team-lead-remote</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/9154/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>EventMobi: Senior Front-End Engineer - Remote</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/9154/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; 151 Yonge Street 11th Floor Toronto, Ontario M5C 2W7
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://eventmobi.com"&gt;https://eventmobi.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;**EventMobi is a remote-first company and this is a remote job. You may reside anywhere in the world to do this job. However, you must be willing to work during Eastern Standard Time business hours. The salary range for this role is between 60k - 90k CAD per annum. This posting is open to all candidates globally.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;WHY EVENTMOBI?&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;EventMobi is an award-winning tech startup with offices in Toronto, Berlin and Manila with thousands of clients across the globe. We believe that live events bring people together to enable change, for businesses and society at large. At EventMobi we have a huge impact on enabling success for events and their attendees. We are on a mission to revolutionize how event planners create, market and manage their events and how attendees experience conferences and tradeshows. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;ABOUT YOU&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you're looking for a software development role that allows you to drive the web forward by utilizing the latest technologies, you've come to the right place! Developers at EventMobi focus on building powerful front-ends that work across devices, are offline-capable, and are just as, if not more powerful, than their native counterparts. We use the best tools for the job, including React+Redux, Capacitor, Material  UI and Webpack to develop a platform that generates &amp;amp; deploys thousands of apps annually and we're constantly looking to push the bar with your help!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;WHAT YOUR WORK WILL FOCUS ON&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Modern Web App - &lt;/strong&gt;You will be involved in enhancing our responsive web app, solving interesting problems along the way - real-time content updates, offline content, UI and architecture scaling for performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Ownership&lt;/strong&gt; - From initial design to deployment, test automation to performance monitoring, you own what you build end-to-end. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Architecture &amp;amp; Scale&lt;/strong&gt; - Gathering insights and employing strong design principles, you will determine the best tech to address our customers' needs while optimizing for scale. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Development&lt;/strong&gt; - Best practices, craftsmanship, well thought out code, and mentorship to your team is your ideal and you preach this in your own work as well as with your teammates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Quality&lt;/strong&gt; - You will help grow the team around you in not only pushing new capabilities for our customers but also maintaining the utmost quality in everything we build. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;WHAT YOU WILL BRING TO THE TEAM&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years experience as a software developer working on large or fast scaling products &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years experience working with Javascript and a deep understanding in React/Redux including concepts such as Hooks and functional components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to architect elegant solutions to complex problems using appropriate abstractions and techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working with large code bases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Restful APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient using JSX/ES2020+/HTML/CSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Material UI or Ant Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Champion best practices and performance improvements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with automated testing suites like Jest and React Testing Library&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to debug a codebase in a self-sufficient manner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of SOLID Principles, Domain Modeling, and Design Patterns is a major benefit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to mentor and grow team members, and provide technical guidance and oversight on implementation direction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;NICE TO HAVE: &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with WebRTC, RTMP and video codec&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Typescript and writing strongly typed React components and hooks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with React-Query or similar libraries for API-driven React components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of developing mobile applications through Capacitor, Cordova, or React Native&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Docker, AWS, and CI/CD like GitHub Actions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Python or other server-side languages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;SOME OF THE INTERESTING THINGS YOU WILL GET TO WORK ON:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implementing API calls with a Stale-With-Revalidate paradigm to support fast, network-first data access with offline caching&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utilizing Redux and dynamic reducers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;React based page builder that generates React components with API integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adding more engagement features (chat/group discussions/1:1 video meetings/breakout rooms)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;WHAT WILL YOU GET FROM EVENTMOBI? &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We offer the experience of a lifetime working with a dynamic, open-minded and diverse team, who are excited to come to work every day and passionate about what they do and the clients they help&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive compensation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company Stock-Options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A great culture with much more along the way&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;REMOTE WORKSPACE REQUIREMENTS: &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a safe, comfortable, and ergonomic workspace and working environment - a private and quiet workspace is vital for doing your best work!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a reliable internet connection capable of participating in video calls, with at least 30Mbps download speed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/eventmobi-senior-front-end-engineer-remote"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/eventmobi-senior-front-end-engineer-remote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 19:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 19:40:49 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/eventmobi-senior-front-end-engineer-remote</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/eventmobi-senior-front-end-engineer-remote</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/6863/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Shneorweb: Frontend UI Developer wizard</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/6863/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; London, UK
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://shneorweb.com"&gt;http://shneorweb.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;We're developing an outstanding application and looking to hire a frontend UI developer wizard to work on the application UI, responsive, transitions and interactions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This role is fit for someone with&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding HTML/CSS and JavaScript knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of developing an advanced UI with modern transitions and interactions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Background in user experience and modern user interfaces.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;div&gt;We're a London-based startup company founded by ex-startups.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The role is open for worldwide candidates.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Office hours: 9AM - 6PM IST&lt;/strong&gt;, this position requires individuals to be available for meetings and duties &lt;em&gt;at least&lt;/em&gt; a six (6) hour block during this window.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Starting immediately &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;**Individuals only - NOT OPEN FOR AGENCIES OF ANY KIND**&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/shneorweb-frontend-ui-developer-wizard"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/shneorweb-frontend-ui-developer-wizard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 11:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 11:40:12 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/shneorweb-frontend-ui-developer-wizard</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/shneorweb-frontend-ui-developer-wizard</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0064/4632/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Fleetio: Web Developer</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0064/4632/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Birmingham, Alabama
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://fleetio.com"&gt;https://fleetio.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;We are looking for an experienced Web Developer who is passionate about building websites that attract and convert. We're looking for someone who not only has front-end development abilities but also has a self-motivated creative spirit, strong collaborative DNA and a focus on growth throughout the entire customer journey.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;About Fleetio&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Fleetio is a modern software platform that helps thousands of organizations around the world manage their fleets. Transportation technology is a hot market and we’re leading the charge, with raving fans and new customers signing up every day. We raised a $21M Series B in late 2020 and are on an exciting trajectory as a company.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;More about Fleetio&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fleetio overview video: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IlvIbwZT3oU"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IlvIbwZT3oU&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fleetio Go overview video: &lt;a href="https://www.fleetio.com/go"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://www.fleetio.com/go&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More about the Fleetio platform: &lt;a href="https://www.fleetio.com/features"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://www.fleetio.com/features&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Test drive Fleetio to get an even better feel for what we're building: &lt;a href="https://www.fleetio.com/register"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://www.fleetio.com/register&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You'll Be Doing&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a part of our growing Marketing Team, you’ll help to maintain our most important marketing asset, the marketing website. This means implementing new web experiences and building high-converting landing pages across device types, testing new product trial workflows and ensuring brand consistency, all with a focus on customer acquisition. Be sure to mention your favorite coffee in your application so we know you actually read this.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What's In It For You&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a part of an incredible team of “A” players who go above and beyond to make Fleetio a successful company. So many different types of companies and organizations operate a fleet each day, and Fleetio is a good fit for most of them (it’s a huge market).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work remotely (within the United States, Canada) or at our Birmingham, AL HQ. Over 50% of our company works remotely and we have promoted a strong remote working culture since the beginning (2012).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We place great emphasis on work/life balance. We have families and hobbies and know you do, too.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of successful web development experience, B2B SaaS is a huge plus!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical expertise in the standard front-end technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript/ES6+&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to translate wireframes and design prototypes (Figma) into accurate, working code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with version control systems like Github&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent organizational skills to work independently and efficiently, managing projects with many moving parts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional collaboration skills to work with the marketing team and other teams to concept, iterate on and complete projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personal interest in staying up-to-date on the latest trends and emerging best practices in the development community&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Considered a Plus&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with ReactJS, TypeScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Next.js&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Netlify, Vercel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Tailwind or CSS-in-JS frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You know a thing or two about the Fleet management industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% health/dental coverage (50% coverage for family)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vision insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Incentive stock options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) match of 4%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PTO - 4 weeks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8 company holidays + 2 floating holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parental and bonding leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dependent care and medical FSA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Short and long term disability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Community service funds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional development funds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health and wellness initiatives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mac laptop + new hire equipment stipend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monthly catered lunches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully stocked kitchen with tons of drinks &amp;amp; snacks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote working friendly since 2012 #LI-REMOTE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/fleetio-web-developer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/fleetio-web-developer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 19:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 19:22:44 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/fleetio-web-developer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/fleetio-web-developer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0076/1075/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>ClickMagick: React Native Developer - Part-Time</title>
      <region>Americas Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Contract</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0076/1075/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Austin, TX
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://clickmagick.com"&gt;https://clickmagick.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;We recently released v1.0 of our mobile app, and we're looking for someone to help develop it further.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So we need your help to add new features, fix bugs and polish the UI on a part-time, but long-term basis.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a flexible contract of anywhere from 15-25 hours per week, and perfect for a freelancer looking to work with a few long-term clients. We pay top rates for top talent.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If that sounds good and the following describes you, let's talk!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* You have 5+ years experience working with React Native &amp;amp; APIs&lt;br&gt;* You have built and deployed apps to both iOS and Google Play Store&lt;br&gt;* You have good attention to detail, test your work, and don't push broken code&lt;br&gt;* You're comfortable working with Github and communicating via Slack&lt;br&gt;* You speak English fluently&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clickmagick-react-native-developer-part-time"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clickmagick-react-native-developer-part-time&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 22:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 22:34:26 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clickmagick-react-native-developer-part-time</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clickmagick-react-native-developer-part-time</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0064/4519/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>ShotFlow: iOS Developer</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0064/4519/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Atlanta, Georgia
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://shotflow.com/"&gt;https://shotflow.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;We are in search of an experienced iOS and/or macOS Developer (remote) to continue evolving our existing iOS and macOS apps.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;What you’ll be doing&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serving as a key part of our Apple team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with the Apple team lead to define new functionality together.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Researching solutions and solving complex problems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating cool new features that push the envelope of iOS.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Who you are&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have 2+ years experience developing production iOS apps in Swift using UIKit or SwiftUI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferably, you also have experience with Objective-C and with building macOS apps in AppKit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are familiar with core iOS frameworks and technologies and what problems they might solve.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You understand iOS design principles and general design patterns, you know when to use them, and when to keep things simple.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re comfortable working closely with product owners and other developers to define the best way to implement features with high technical standards.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You share our passion for the highest-quality code and won’t settle for anything less.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You thrive on excellence, autonomy and questioning conventional wisdom.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Who we are&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;ShotFlow helps the world's best-known retail and apparel brands create product imagery and other visual content faster and easier.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A product page full of beautiful pictures doesn't just happen by magic, it takes whole teams of studio production professionals to create that compelling content.  ShotFlow is the workflow tool simplifying complex production processes behind the scenes, enabling a better visual shopping experience for millions of customers.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;What we offer&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A fully remote international team. Every person is free to live and work wherever – and whenever – they want.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An asynchronous schedule, providing more flexibility, less pressure, and a better work-life balance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A self-determined job with personal responsibility to move things forward, shape the processes and choose the tools you need to do your best work.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personalized software/hardware budget to set up your work environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ll travel with us for team gatherings to catch up, have fun and plan our future.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A generous vacation policy, keeping you ready for new challenges.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A fun and friendly company culture. Share some memes on Slack and catch up with us on the weekly social calls.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sounds like a match?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you’d like to learn more and apply, send your CV to recruitment@shotflow.com and we'll be in touch!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/shotflow-ios-developer-1"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/shotflow-ios-developer-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 11:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 11:16:16 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/shotflow-ios-developer-1</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/shotflow-ios-developer-1</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0064/4683/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Close: Senior or Staff Frontend Engineer - React (100% Remote)</title>
      <region>Americas Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0064/4683/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Remote
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://close.com"&gt;http://close.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;At &lt;a href="https://close.com/"&gt;Close&lt;/a&gt;, we're building the sales communication platform of the future. With our roots as the very first sales CRM to include built-in calling, we're leading the industry toward eliminating manual processes and helping companies to close more deals (faster). Since our founding in 2013, we've grown to become a profitable, 100% globally distributed team of ~55 high-performing, happy people that are dedicated to building a product our customers love.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our app’s frontend is a single-page JavaScript web app mostly written in React (originally built with &lt;a href="http://backbone.js/"&gt;Backbone.js&lt;/a&gt;). We bundle with Webpack and target only modern browsers. We test with Jest and React Testing Library. Our UI updates in near real-time and is written in LESS/CSS (with flexbox and grid layout) using CSS modules and takes advantage of fun technologies like Websockets and WebRTC. We house our design system in Storybook.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We care about performance (e.g. route-based code splitting), maintainability, and testability of our frontend code. We sweat the UI/UX details and work collaboratively with the Product team throughout the design process. This means diving into lo-fi wireframes, and communicating continuously when those ideas are brought to life using Figma and code.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our frontend app is built on top of our REST API &amp;amp; GraphQL endpoints. Our backend &lt;a href="https://stackshare.io/close-crm/close"&gt;tech stack&lt;/a&gt; consists of Python/Flask, MongoDB, Postgres, Elasticsearch, and Redis. We run our services in Docker on AWS.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We ❤️ open sourcing our code and ideas on &lt;a href="https://github.com/closeio"&gt;our GitHub&lt;/a&gt; and on &lt;a href="https://making.close.com/"&gt;The Making of Close&lt;/a&gt;, our behind-the-scenes Product &amp;amp; Engineering blog. Check our projects such as &lt;a href="https://making.close.com/posts/introducting-react-custom-scroller-component"&gt;react-custom-scroller&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://making.close.com/posts/introducting-use-infinite-scroll-react-hook"&gt;use-infinite-scroll&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://making.close.com/posts/introducting-use-abortable-effect-react-hook"&gt;use-abortable-effect&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://making.close.com/posts/introducing-smart-tooltip-delay-library"&gt;smart-tooltip-delay&lt;/a&gt; or insights from our day-to-day work on such as &lt;a href="https://making.close.com/posts/highlights-from-a-complex-downshift-js-refactor/"&gt;Highlights From a Complex Downshift.js Refactor&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://making.close.com/posts/reactizing-a-complex-backbone-view"&gt;A Case Study in"Reactizing" a Complex Backbone View&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://making.close.com/posts/finding-the-cause-of-a-memory-leak-in-jest"&gt;Finding the cause of a memory leak in Jest tests&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About You&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We're looking for an experienced full-time (or part-time) Frontend Software Engineer to join our engineering team. Someone who has a solid understanding of web technologies and wants to help design, implement, and launch major user-facing features.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You should have senior level experience (~5 years) building modern frontend applications in JavaScript, HTML, and CSS, with at least 3 years of that experience using React.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You should have significant experience designing, debugging, and optimizing frontend applications to make them fast and reliable. You have significant experience with REST APIs and thoroughly understand HTTP requests. You have experience participating in code reviews and providing overall code quality suggestions to help maintain the structure and quality of the codebase.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You should have great product sense and be able to think through user experience issues before diving into the code, and you exhibit a love for great UI.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You’re comfortable working in a fast-paced environment with a small and talented team where you're supported in your efforts to grow professionally. You are able to manage your time well, communicate effectively and collaborate in a fully distributed team.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Note: this role requires you to be located in an Americas time zone. If you're not located in one of these time zones, check out our other posting &lt;a href="https://jobs.lever.co/close.io/10a1e32b-1a59-48dc-b8f4-e6f0dfae4e20"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are open to hiring mid, senior and staff level engineers for this role.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bonus points if you have...&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience implementing real-time (e.g. websockets, polling, etc.) web apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with GraphQL endpoints&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An eye for design and experience with Figma, Sketch, Abstract, Photoshop, or similar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Led small project teams building and launching features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributed open source code (core or plugins) for a popular frontend framework such as React, Vue, or Angular&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Built B2B SaaS products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with sales or sales tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Come help us with projects like...&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conceiving, designing, building, and launching new user-facing features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with Twilio's API, WebSockets, and WebRTC to improve our &lt;a href="https://close.com/calling/"&gt;calling features&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building user-facing analytics features that provide actionable insights based on sales activity data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improving real-time collaboration user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expanding our frontend GraphQL usage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extending our React component library&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why work with us?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZbyGnLhtj0o&amp;amp;feature=youtu.be"&gt;Culture video&lt;/a&gt; 💚&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% remote company &lt;em&gt;(we believe in trust and autonomy)&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choose between working 5 days/wk (standard full-time) or 4 days/wk @ 80% pay&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gKjyXMz-q-Q&amp;amp;feature=youtu.be"&gt;Annual team retreats&lt;/a&gt; ✈️&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quarterly virtual summits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 weeks PTO + Winter Holiday Break&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 additional PTO days every year with the company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 month paid sabbatical every 5 years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Co-working stipend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue Share (after 1 year)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid parental leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, Dental, Vision with HSA option (US residents)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401k matching at 6% (US residents)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dependent care FSA (US residents)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributor to &lt;a href="https://stripe.com/climate"&gt;Stripe's climate&lt;/a&gt; initiative 🌍❤️ &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;a href="https://close.io/about/"&gt;Our story and team&lt;/a&gt; 🚀&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Our application process was designed to promote equitable and unbiased hiring practices. We ask a small series of questions that are similar to what would be asked in the first interview. This helps us learn more about you right from the start so please be sure to answer each question thoughtfully. Each application will receive two screens by two different reviewers. Regardless of fit, you will hear back from us letting you know if we'll be moving forward.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Interested in &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://close.com/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Close&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; but don't think this role is the best fit for you? View our &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="http://jobs.close.com/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;other positions&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/close-senior-or-staff-frontend-engineer-react-100-remote-1"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/close-senior-or-staff-frontend-engineer-react-100-remote-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 19:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 19:20:35 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/close-senior-or-staff-frontend-engineer-react-100-remote-1</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/close-senior-or-staff-frontend-engineer-react-100-remote-1</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0018/9489/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>MartianCraft LLC: Native iOS Engineer</title>
      <region>North America Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0018/9489/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Norfolk VA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://MartianCraft.com"&gt;http://MartianCraft.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;MartianCraft has an exciting opportunity for someone that enjoys technically-challenging iOS problems and producing real time apps that have a direct impact on the users. MartianCraft has been full time remote for 17 years!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are looking for a smart and experienced iOS engineer to work with MartianCraft’s team of senior developers. This is a remote work opportunity—MartianCraft is a fully remote company. You must thrive in a fast-moving work environment, be able to adapt to changes quickly, anticipate business needs, and be effective with minimal structure and process. The broad range of applications and team members makes excellent communication skills a priority.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build advanced applications in Swift&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrate with existing APIs and data sources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with teams to develop new APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unit-test code for usability, reliability, and robustness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix bugs and improve application performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interact directly with client teams to determine requirements and task prioritization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use project management tools like Jira to organize work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of software development experience on Apple platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to quickly become familiar with large, complex code bases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly skilled in Swift and Objective-C&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience with Core Data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well-versed in Auto Layout with Storyboards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience with Core Graphics and Core Animation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with complex data visualization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Promises&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced with Git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with GitHub Enterprise and Jenkins&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Past experience working remotely&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent proactive verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to collaborate effectively with teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to deliver high quality work under tight deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This is a full-time employment position with a full benefits package including medical/dental/vision/Rx insurance, paid time off, and a 401(k).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Compensation range: $115k-$135k plus benefits depending on experience. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This position is also available as a full time 1099 Contract position if preferred by the applicant. &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/martiancraft-llc-native-ios-engineer-1"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/martiancraft-llc-native-ios-engineer-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 19:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 19:11:48 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/martiancraft-llc-native-ios-engineer-1</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/martiancraft-llc-native-ios-engineer-1</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/8545/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>ev.energy: React Native Engineer </title>
      <region>North America Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Contract</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/8545/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; London
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://ev.energy"&gt;https://ev.energy&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What are we looking for? &lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent commercial experience with React Native, React, and Flow or TypeScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience building scalable, performant products loved by users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills and a collaborative approach, having worked in cross-functional teams in the past&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A desire to mentor and share skills with other engineers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A keen interest in our product and mission&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The important details&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Starting: Immediately;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Location: Remote, core hours 10:00 am – 4:00 pm London time;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Term: Contract&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/ev-energy-react-native-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/ev-energy-react-native-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 13:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 13:02:27 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/ev-energy-react-native-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/ev-energy-react-native-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/8440/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Nova Labs: Frontend Engineer</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/8440/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; 
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.nova.xyz"&gt;https://www.nova.xyz&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nova Labs is the founding team behind the Helium Network, the world’s fastest-growing decentralized wireless network, now live in over 74,000+ cities and 182 countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nova Labs was founded in 2013 by Napster Founder Shawn Fanning, Amir Haleem, and Sean Carey, with a mission to make it easier to build connected devices. The company has raised equity funding from some of the most prominent Venture Capital (VC) firms in the world including GV (formerly Google Ventures), Khosla Ventures, FirstMark Capital, Marc Benioff, MunichRe and others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re searching for an experienced hands-on front end engineer to help us build out and maintain the Nova Labs website.  This role will work closely with our Product, Marketing, and Design teams to develop a robust and beautiful website, develop content, and drive website traffic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Building and testing aesthetic, functional, and user-friendly websites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coordinating with designers, content providers, and management or business owners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Implementing and ensuring website security and data protection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deploy and maintain websites using hosting providers such as Heroku or Fly.io&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monitoring and analyzing site performance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Updating website content and monitoring how the site shows up in search results, and social media posts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ensure our UI components and libraries are reliable, secure, extensible and accessible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2+ years of professional hands-on software development experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Product-focused, driving the design, development, and implementation in order to turn a user's pain points into simple and elegant solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Building web applications using React, HTML, and CSS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You excel at building data visualizations using libraries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You develop visualizations that enable engineers and leaders to explore and understand data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to have&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next.js&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Familiarity with digital marketing tools&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adwords, A/B testing, Meta Ads&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;100% company-paid health insurance premiums (medical, dental, and vision) for you and your dependents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flexible paid vacation with a vacation stipend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paid company holidays.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monthly wellness stipend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Annual hardware stipend&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;401K plan (no match)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fully remote&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/nova-labs-frontend-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/nova-labs-frontend-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 20:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 20:17:22 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/listings/nova-labs-frontend-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/listings/nova-labs-frontend-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/6523/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>TextUs: Senior Software Engineer, Frontend</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/6523/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Denver, CO
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://textus.com/"&gt;https://textus.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;OVERVIEW&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;TextUs is looking for a Senior React Engineer to join our team and to help us build our applications. These include a UI, Chrome Extension and Mobile Application.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO YOU ARE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of writing software overall &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience developing production React applications professionally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working in a 100% remote environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An included statement in your application on how you have worked with React at production scale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You are also&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Driven to create and maintain stable, re-usable interfaces in collaboration with our UX designers  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in writing excellent documentation to guide our partners, development and support teams. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excited to mentor junior developers in good development practices for clean code and reliable software. Someone that has empathy for others and enjoys helping them when they are stuck.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with functional design patterns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to demonstrate pragmatic decision-making and problem-solving abilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passionate about the craft of programming, taking the time to think through hard problems and using your tools to develop reliable and maintainable software.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eager to maintain a robust CI/CD tooling, processes, testing, and procedures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willing to take ownership of different sections of the application, becoming the go-to person on the team for all aspects of it, from planning and stories to QA and support questions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is our stack:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;React&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ruby on Rails&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Typescript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;React Native&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Material UI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Postgres&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ElasticSearch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Heroku and AWS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skills (Must Have)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Functional React&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hooks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Typescript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Redux&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;React Testing Library&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skills (Nice to Have)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Material UI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Websockets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nivo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;RxJS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EMPLOYMENT DETAILS&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Job Type:&lt;/strong&gt; Full Time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Compensation Range:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;$130,000 - $150,000&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Location:&lt;/strong&gt; Remote / Denver, CO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;# of hires for this role: &lt;/strong&gt;1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Target Start Date:&lt;/strong&gt; 4 weeks from offer date&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Reporting to:&lt;/strong&gt; Engineering Manager&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;By submitting your resume for this role - you consent to communication via email and text&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;INTERVIEW PROCESS&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Interview w. Hiring Manager (30 mins via Zoom Video)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Topics: Culture, leadership, skills, role overview&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Pairing Session w. Backend Team (2 hrs via Zoom Video)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Topics: Culture, skills, role overview&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Rembrandt Assessment (Self Paced)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Rembrandt assessment allows TextUs to assess how your personality fits within the role and the TextUs culture. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Q&amp;amp;A w. CTO (30 mins via Zoom Video)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Topics: Culture, leadership, skills. Also, please come prepared with questions about the role, team, and product to ensure this role is the best fit for you.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY TEXTUS&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Our Engineering Team is guided by high empathy and high responsibility. This means that we care about our engineers’ career trajectory and their thoughts on our product direction and implementation. Our engineers are trusted with autonomy: the latitude in how and when work gets done. We are a collaborative, learning and data-driven culture with an experienced and proven leadership team. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TextUs Benefits include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive pay&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health / Dental / Vision Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HSA contributions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401K with company match&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited PTO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equity within the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cell phone + internet reimbursement for $100/month&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One-time $1,000 home office stipend once you’ve been with TextUs for 6 months&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up to 12 weeks of Parental Leave &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8 Observed Holidays + End of Year Shutdown&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;U.S. remote first with optional WeWork office space in downtown Denver, CO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;TextUs does not discriminate based on race, color, religion (creed), gender, gender expression, age, national origin (ancestry), disability, marital status, sexual orientation, or military status, in any of its activities or operations. We are committed to providing an inclusive and welcoming environment for all members of our staff, volunteers, subcontractors, vendors, and clients.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/textus-senior-software-engineer-frontend"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/textus-senior-software-engineer-frontend&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 16:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 16:02:37 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/textus-senior-software-engineer-frontend</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/textus-senior-software-engineer-frontend</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/8347/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Onko Health: Senior Front-End Engineer</title>
      <region>UK Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/8347/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; London (Paddington)
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://onkohealth.co.uk/"&gt;https://onkohealth.co.uk/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Onko Health is hiring a remote front-end engineer for our cancer support application, working with Angular and other languages.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re a healthtech scaleup company. Our cancer health journey mobile apps blend remote support and coaching from expert oncology practitioners with self-help approaches, backed by a data handling platform.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We serve a number of UK healthcare providers and NHS trusts, delivering improved outcomes for patient health and care giving. We're bringing development in-house, growing a new engineering team to deliver upon our ambitious international growth plans. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Collaborating with our domain experts, product owner, UX and engineering colleagues, you'll help build the UI that manages how clinical and care-giving staff manage patients' whole health journey. This brings the patient closer to the care provision, and leverages the latest in health research, digital and web tech, consumer wearables etc.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We place emphasis on a really usable UI and tight integration with our native apps and Node.js back-end.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your role includes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implementing our newly re-designed front-end and user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building consoles that bring the patient and cancer care experts closer together&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Displaying a variety of health and care data, including from consumer wearables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with data security, maintainability and scalability in mind, influenced by clean code principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keeping up to date with trends in front-end engineering, Angular and healthtech&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping evolve our development culture, methods, automation and tooling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We're looking for&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Someone with a good knowledge of the TypeScript ecosystem, especially Angular&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with RxJs, Bootstrap, Karma/Jasmine and Protractor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong foundations in web technologies like HTML, CSS, JSON, REST&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An emphasis on attention to detail, code quality, TDD, and with solid experience with refactoring&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a progressive Agile environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knows how to manage technical debt, identify design issues and prioritise them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with AWS, Auth0, Firebase is a bonus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You may also bring - or optionally like to gain - skills or interests around any of&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Front-end architecture | helping evolve pipelines for testing and deployment, working with a DevOps colleague | Swift or Kotlin | integration with wearables and third party applications &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary and benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;£70,000 - £85,000 - reviewed at six months - we're keeping an open mind&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share scheme for formative team members (once proven value to the business)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;25 days holiday (plus bank holidays) and five days unpaid leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible working practices - tell us what you need - e.g. optional four day week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personal development plan that you can shape, with budget for related training/certifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/onko-health-senior-front-end-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/onko-health-senior-front-end-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 09:43:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 09:43:38 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/onko-health-senior-front-end-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/onko-health-senior-front-end-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clevertech: Senior Javascript Engineer - React</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; New York, NY
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://clevertech.biz"&gt;https://clevertech.biz&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Experience Remote done Right. Over 20 years of remote experience, all 500+ staff are 100% remote and we still grow vibrant relationships, and provide exceptional opportunities for career growth while working with stellar clients on ambitious projects&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're working on:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Enterprise companies turn to us to help them launch innovative digital products that interact with hundreds of millions of customers, transactions and data points. The problems we solve every day are real and require creativity, grit and determination. We are building a culture that challenges norms while fostering experimentation and personal growth. In order to grasp the scale of problems we face, ideally, you have some exposure to Logistics, FinTech, Transportation, Insurance, Media or other complex multifactor industries&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7+ years of professional experience (A technical assessment will be required)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Senior-level experience with Javascript, React, Redux, Websockets, Async/Await&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create clean, modern, testable, well-documented code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;English fluency, verbal and written&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional, empathic, team player&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Problem solver, proactive, go getter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Straight from the Devs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Watch short snippets of actual developers (Real, not scripted) share why they joined &lt;a href="https://cleverte.ch/3"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YouTube Playlist&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Clevertech is an amazing place to work at&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;At Clevertech, you can expect that you will:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be 100% dedicated to one project at a time so that you can hone your skills, innovate and grow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a part of a team of talented and friendly senior-level developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on projects that allow you to use cutting edge tech. We believe in constantly evolving your mastery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;The result? We produce meaningful work and we are truly proud and excited to be creating waves in an industry under transformation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clevertech-senior-javascript-engineer-react-8"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clevertech-senior-javascript-engineer-react-8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 18:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 18:13:42 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clevertech-senior-javascript-engineer-react-8</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clevertech-senior-javascript-engineer-react-8</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0071/4666/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>TestGorilla: Senior Frontend Engineer (Angular)</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0071/4666/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Amsterdam, The Netherlands
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/"&gt;https://www.testgorilla.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Hi there,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;I’m Nicolas, TestGorilla’s Head of Engineering. We’re a fast-growing HR tech startup that helps hiring teams make better hiring decisions faster and bias-free.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Over the past year, we’ve experienced tremendous growth. More than 7,500 companies have replaced CVs with our assessments to screen candidates in an unbiased and data-driven way.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As we scale our efforts in 2022 and beyond, we’re looking for a &lt;strong&gt;Senior Frontend Engineer&lt;/strong&gt; who’s passionate about joining our quest to help people land dream jobs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;The proposition&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping shape a fast-growing HR tech startup as an early employee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully remote position with bright, motivated, and friendly colleagues around the world &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary incl. bonus and stock options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible hours and vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid parental leave &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;€1000 remote working budget per year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3.5% of salary learning &amp;amp; development budget&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;The role in context&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are looking for a &lt;strong&gt;Senior Frontend Engineer&lt;/strong&gt; to join our engineering department and help us bring our product to Enterprise level maturity. Your work will directly impact hundreds of thousands of users around the world.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a senior member of the engineering team, you will build and deliver frontend solutions to provide extraordinary product experiences for our users, including SPAs and reusable components for the rapid growth of all our products.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You’ll own the design, code, and deployment of solutions and make sure they perform and scale in production. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;You’ll spend time on the following&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take full &lt;strong&gt;ownership&lt;/strong&gt; of the frontend; from low-level optimizations to improving user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build &lt;strong&gt;reusable&lt;/strong&gt; code and libraries for future use&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure the technical feasibility of &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/test-library/role-specific-skills-tests/ux-ui-design-test/"&gt;UI/UX designs&lt;/a&gt; and propose features and functionalities to the product team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Optimize&lt;/strong&gt; the application for maximum speed and scalability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the entire &lt;strong&gt;software development and delivery&lt;/strong&gt; cycle from ideation to deployment and everything in between&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Efficiently utilize &lt;strong&gt;DevOps&lt;/strong&gt; tools and practices to deliver high-quality software as well as value to end customers as early as possible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in a collaborative, talented &lt;strong&gt;distributed team&lt;/strong&gt; across Europe, United States, South America, and Asia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will act as a &lt;strong&gt;mentor&lt;/strong&gt; for less-experienced team members through both your technical knowledge and leadership skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Here’s what we’re looking for&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are inspired by our mission to put &lt;em&gt;one billion people in dream jobs&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are fully aligned with our &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/careers/"&gt;values&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience designing, implementing, running, and maintaining production front-end code using modern client-side development frameworks based on JS/TS such as &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/test-library/programming-skills-tests/angular-test/"&gt;Angular&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You strive for excellence: pixel-perfect, high-quality code, and lightning-fast load times&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You care deeply about building a world-class engineering team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a solid understanding ofUX/UI design, usability, and accessibility&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are passionate about improving skills and learning new technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You enjoy influencing others and always advocate for technical excellence while being open to change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re resilient in ambiguous situations and can approach challenges from multiple perspectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have strong written and verbal communication skills. You can validate your decisions and communicate them clearly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;We typically expect candidates with at least &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;7 years of  Senior Frontend Engineer experience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to have the skills mentioned above.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Bonus points if ...&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;you have experience in a SaaS product based company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;you are comfortable with Agile methods, such as Extreme Programming (XP), Scrum, and/or Kanban&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;you have a working knowledge of cloud technology such as &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/test-library/role-specific-skills-tests/aws-test/"&gt;AWS&lt;/a&gt;, Azure, Kubernetes, and Docker&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Interested?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;Here at TestGorilla, we eat our own dog food. We use our assessment platform to make sure we make the best hiring decisions faster and bias-free. I took one too and I enjoyed it!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;So if this role sounds like a good fit for you, I’d like you to take an assessment so we can get a better idea about whether you would fit the role. It’s also a great opportunity for you to get to know our product! Simply use the Apply button.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you’re hired, I’ll do everything I can to help you succeed at &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/"&gt;TestGorilla&lt;/a&gt; and throughout the rest of your career.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-frontend-engineer-angular"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-frontend-engineer-angular&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 08:44:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 08:44:57 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-frontend-engineer-angular</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-frontend-engineer-angular</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0075/9084/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>TestGorilla: Frontend Engineer (Angular Developer)</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0075/9084/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Amsterdam, The Netherlands
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/"&gt;https://www.testgorilla.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Hi there,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;I’m Nicolas, TestGorilla’s Head of Engineering. We’re a fast-growing HR tech startup that helps hiring teams make better hiring decisions faster and bias-free.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over the past year, we’ve experienced tremendous growth. More than 7,500 companies have replaced CVs with our assessments to screen candidates in an unbiased and data-driven way.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As we scale our efforts in 2022 and beyond, we’re looking for a&lt;strong&gt; Frontend Engineer&lt;/strong&gt; who’s passionate about joining our quest to help people land dream jobs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;The proposition&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping shape a fast-growing HR tech startup as an early employee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully remote position with bright, motivated, and friendly colleagues around the world &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary incl. bonus and stock options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible hours and vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid parental leave &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;€1000 remote working budget per year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning &amp;amp; development budget of 3.5% of salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;The role in context&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are looking for a&lt;strong&gt; Frontend Engineer&lt;/strong&gt; to join our engineering department and help us bring our product to Enterprise level maturity. Your work will directly impact hundreds of thousands of users around the world.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a member of the engineering team, you will build and deliver frontend solutions to provide extraordinary product experiences for our users, including SPAs and reusable components for the rapid growth of all our products.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You’ll own the design, code, and deployment of solutions and make sure they perform and scale in production. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;You’ll spend time on the following&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take full &lt;strong&gt;ownership&lt;/strong&gt; of the frontend; from low-level optimizations to improving user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build &lt;strong&gt;reusable&lt;/strong&gt; code and libraries for future use&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure the technical feasibility of &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/test-library/role-specific-skills-tests/ux-ui-design-test/"&gt;UI/UX designs&lt;/a&gt; and propose features and functionalities to the product team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Optimize&lt;/strong&gt; the application for maximum speed and scalability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the entire &lt;strong&gt;software development and delivery&lt;/strong&gt; cycle from ideation to deployment and everything in between&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Efficiently utilize &lt;strong&gt;DevOps&lt;/strong&gt; tools and practices to deliver high-quality software as well as value to end customers as early as possible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in a collaborative, talented &lt;strong&gt;distributed team&lt;/strong&gt; across Europe, United States, South America, and Asia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will act as a &lt;strong&gt;mentor&lt;/strong&gt; for less-experienced team members through both your technical knowledge and leadership skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Here’s what we’re looking for&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are inspired by our mission of putting&lt;em&gt; 1 billion people in dream jobs&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; You are fully aligned with our &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/careers/"&gt;values&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have 4-6 years of experience designing, implementing, running, and maintaining production &lt;strong&gt;front-end code&lt;/strong&gt; using modern client-side development frameworks based on JS/TS such as &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/test-library/programming-skills-tests/angular-test/"&gt;Angular&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You strive for &lt;strong&gt;excellence:&lt;/strong&gt; pixel-perfect, high-quality code, and lightning-fast load times&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You care deeply about building a &lt;strong&gt;world-class engineering&lt;/strong&gt; team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a solid understanding of&lt;strong&gt; UX/UI design, usability, and accessibility&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are passionate about improving skills and &lt;strong&gt;learning&lt;/strong&gt; new technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You enjoy &lt;strong&gt;influencing others&lt;/strong&gt; and always advocate for technical excellence while being open to change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re &lt;strong&gt;resilient&lt;/strong&gt; in ambiguous situations and can approach challenges from multiple perspectives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have strong written and verbal &lt;strong&gt;communication skills&lt;/strong&gt;. You can validate your decisions and communicate them clearly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Bonus points if ...&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;you have experience in a SaaS product based company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;you are comfortable with Agile methods, such as Extreme Programming (XP), Scrum, and/or Kanban&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;you have a working knowledge of cloud technology such as &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/test-library/role-specific-skills-tests/aws-test/"&gt;AWS&lt;/a&gt;, Azure, Kubernetes, and Docker &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Interested?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;Here at TestGorilla, we eat our own dog food. We use our assessment platform to make sure we make the best hiring decisions faster and bias-free. I took one too and I enjoyed it!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;So if this role sounds like a good fit for you, I’d like you to &lt;a href="https://assessment.testgorilla.com/testtaker/publicinvitation/dfb458d5-b49e-4c93-a830-fdfa210e733f"&gt;take an assessment &lt;/a&gt;so we can get a better idea about whether you would fit the role. It’s also a great opportunity for you to get to know our product! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you’re hired, I’ll do everything I can to help you succeed at &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/"&gt;TestGorilla&lt;/a&gt; and throughout the rest of your career.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-frontend-engineer-angular-developer-3"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-frontend-engineer-angular-developer-3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 08:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 08:32:52 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-frontend-engineer-angular-developer-3</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-frontend-engineer-angular-developer-3</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0077/5406/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Aldrin: Senior React Native Mobile Developer Web3 (Remote)</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0077/5406/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; London
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://aldrin.com"&gt;https://aldrin.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;The Role&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are looking for a Senior React Native Mobile Developer with extensive experience in designing, building, and deploying highly secure, scalable, and maintainable client-facing UI systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You will be one of the senior developers of the mobile app working closely with our designers, product owners, and backend engineers to develop and maintain high-quality mobile applications for a global audience in an extremely fast-growing industry. We work with a modern tech-stack. We use Typescript, hooks, eslint, reanimated, automated CI and deployments, etc. We work with a design system and an updated figma design.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you are extremely passionate about mobile platforms and translating code into user-friendly apps, we would like to meet you. Ultimately, you should be able to help design and build the next generation of our mobile applications that will impact and shape the financial lives of a growing audience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You will:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute code to our iOS &amp;amp; Android React Native apps from the get-go&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on integrating and collaborating with other crypto products to enrich the user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement features with the aim to provide long term stability of a highly scalable application&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing clean and reusable react native components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively contributing new ideas and innovative UX/UI patterns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Play an active role in evolving our mobile engineering practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong expertise in React Native with 5+ years of professional experience building high-quality mobile apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High-level experience with TypeScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have experience with best-in-class client-side data design and management, whether that’s experience with GraphQL/ Apollo or other such tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a passion for good design and attention to detail. You’ll collaborate with designers but undoubtedly have the opportunity to express your own design sense if desired&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Verbal fluency in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice-to-Have Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable portfolio of released applications on the App Store or the Android&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passionate about crypto markets, blockchain technology, and decentralized applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge/experience working on mobile financial applications/cryptocurrencies/wallets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Solana Web3 frameworks and technologies, especially on mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with a large codebase and detox or appium testing tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with responsive UI and debugging skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing high-performance mobile app interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors or Masters degree, preferably in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or other technical (STEM) field or an equivalent of experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote work in a dynamic, fast-growth Web3 startup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible working hours&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunity to work with a diverse, global, and passionate team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaboration with leading projects and thought leaders in the crypto space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;At Aldrin Labs, we celebrate a truly diverse and inclusive company culture and are committed to equal employment opportunity regardless of race, color, ancestry, religion, sex, national origin, sexual orientation, age, citizenship, marital status, disability, or gender identity.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aldrin-senior-react-native-mobile-developer-web3-remote-2"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aldrin-senior-react-native-mobile-developer-web3-remote-2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 10:43:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 10:43:30 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aldrin-senior-react-native-mobile-developer-web3-remote-2</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aldrin-senior-react-native-mobile-developer-web3-remote-2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgencyAnalytics: Frontend Engineer</title>
      <region>Canada Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Toronto, Canada
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://agencyanalytics.com"&gt;https://agencyanalytics.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Our Experience team is looking for a passionate Frontend Engineer to join us in creating amazing experiences for our users. Our team is one of the fastest growing within AgencyAnalytics! We work fast and iteratively to ensure our products are modern, easy to use and ultimately make our users happy. More importantly, we're looking for people to build a team of collaborative, supportive and high-skilled engineers that take our products to the next level. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You'll work with technologies like React, TypeScript, JavaScript and CSS to deliver industry-leading features. You'll have the opportunity work on a wide range of projects including high profile features, experimental UX/UI improvements, paying down technical debt, improving existing features and everything in between. We're undergoing sustained, high growth and there will be multiple career advancement opportunities for both managers and individual contributors! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether you're a looking to grow your responsibilities, simply want a change, or you're just getting a start in development, we'd love to hear from you!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This position is 100% remote and only eligible for those who are authorized to work in Canada.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and iterate on new features to deliver amazing experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuously review, improve and adjust all aspects of the user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Promote a culture of collaboration, care and high quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regularly conduct peer reviews, code audits and promote good practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with other teams to build a technical ecosystem that enables high velocity, low-waste development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Who You Are&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have several years of experience with React and JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have an attention to detail and obsess over the user's experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You care about code quality and advocate for best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Benefits&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully remote, no location restrictions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profit-sharing distributed quarterly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 weeks vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited paid sick days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extended health benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continued education allowance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Annual fitness allowance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuous events like happy hour &amp;amp; regular hosted meetups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/agencyanalytics-frontend-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/agencyanalytics-frontend-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 13:38:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 13:38:41 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/agencyanalytics-frontend-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/agencyanalytics-frontend-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0066/9305/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>OCR Labs: Front End Engineer - Full Time</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0066/9305/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; London / Sydney / San Francisco
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://ocrlabs.com"&gt;https://ocrlabs.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Full time – Remote - London / UK Timezone&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Join a new team of passionate engineers and build a world-class platform to fight identity fraud at a global scale.  The technology is awesome, interesting and solves real world problems.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;The Position&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are looking to add engineers to our team with strong front-end programming experience. You should be well-versed in component-driven development with a working knowledge of HTML, JavaScript, and CSS.  The role would include:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;·        Building new product features for both our customers and our product teams&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;·        Work closely with product managers, designers and backend engineers in order to create innovative and usable solutions&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;·        Helping shape the technical direction - your choices will become the building blocks of our infrastructure&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Needed qualifications&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Whilst technical competence is critical, we place great emphasis on passion, communication, and collaboration across the business. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;·        You have minimum 3 years of commercial front-end development experience with React, typescript and NodeJS.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;·        Minimum 3 years working with complex web applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;·        Proficient in JavaScript ES6, CSS3 and HTML5.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;·        Exposure to writing unit, integration and E2E tests&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;·        Optimising code to effectively run across multiple devices and browsers&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;·        Strong written and verbal skills&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;·        You have an In-depth understanding of Javascript, the DOM, and relevant concepts&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;·        Have a keen eye for UI details&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;·        Understanding of progressive web apps&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;·        Experience with webpack, docker, Git and CI/CD&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;·        Experience in mobile and responsive development&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Nice to haves…&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;·        Working on a SaaS product (B2B)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;·        Typescript&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;·        Experience with RUST&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;·        Experience working in a Fintech company&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;·        AWS Lambda / Microservices architecture&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;·        Any AWS technologies&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About us &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;OCR Labs is an identity verification software company that has developed world leading digital identity verification technology. Our technology eliminates identity fraud and makes sure people are who they say they are.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’ve built everything from the ground up and have a broad range of top customers across banking, telecommunications, government and more. We are growing very fast and scaling internationally.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The successful candidate can be based remotely but will report to the Product Owner in Sydney. The position is fulltime and remuneration is competitive, based on experience. You’ll need to have good written and spoken English. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Instructions on how to apply &lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;Send an email through to devjobs@ocrlabs.com with “I love developing” in the subject. Write a few lines about you and attach your resume.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt; Add any link you think will help us assess your soft and hard skills. If you peak our interest, we’ll set up an interview and go from there.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/ocr-labs-front-end-engineer-full-time-1"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/ocr-labs-front-end-engineer-full-time-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 00:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 00:58:53 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/ocr-labs-front-end-engineer-full-time-1</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/ocr-labs-front-end-engineer-full-time-1</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/7353/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Feather: Senior Frontend Engineer – React – EU remote or relocation to Berlin</title>
      <region>Europe Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/7353/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Berlin
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://feather-insurance.com"&gt;https://feather-insurance.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;We’re here to change a notoriously conservative industry that’s pretty against digitization and platform automation. Can you guess what it is? Yep, it’s &lt;em&gt;insurance&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;That’s why we need your help to change it! We want insurance to be honest, transparent, and simple, but we’re going to need some support.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;You’ll be joining a team of talented engineers from around the world to build the best and most useful insurance tools in the industry. This includes building a secure channel for our customers to send sensitive data through our web app, setting up a referral engine, and making sure our customers have a flawless sign-up process.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Your work will help us expand our existing products and launch new ones throughout Europe. You will be one of our go-to people to make core technical decisions that ensure a smooth customer experience. The platform you build will be used to make insurance a little less of a hassle and a lot more reliable.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Why apply to Feather?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Small team, flat hierarchy, mission-driven.&lt;/strong&gt; The usual buzzwords here, except we actually mean them. We’re small, lean, and we love what we’re doing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;A modern tech stack to work with.&lt;/strong&gt; We use ReactJS with TypeScript, &lt;a href="https://nextjs.org/"&gt;Next.js&lt;/a&gt;, and GraphQL with &lt;a href="https://www.apollographql.com/"&gt;Apollo&lt;/a&gt;. Our CI/CD is built with GitHub Actions, and we use Jest, Cypress and Reg-viz for testing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;You’ll be building a product that people need and are grateful for.&lt;/strong&gt; Our excellent &lt;a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/feather-insurance.com"&gt;Trustpilot&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.google.com/search?q=feather+insurance+berlin&amp;amp;ei=7IWjYKjjKszQaIDQroAL&amp;amp;oq=feather+insurance+berlin&amp;amp;gs_lcp=Cgdnd3Mtd2l6EAMyAggAOgcIABBHELADOgQIABBDUKYnWLw9YLpFaAFwAngAgAG2AogB9QqSAQcwLjcuMC4xmAEAoAEBqgEHZ3dzLXdpesgBCMABAQ&amp;amp;sclient=gws-wiz&amp;amp;ved=0ahUKEwioiZzS8tLwAhVMKBoKHQCoC7AQ4dUDCA4&amp;amp;uact=5#lrd=0x47a84f408d3fac27:0x76b64d5066963c2e,1"&gt;Google reviews&lt;/a&gt; speak for themselves. We’ve built our products around people, and they love it!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;There's plenty of space to grow.&lt;/strong&gt; As a senior member of the engineering team, you would have a choice to grow into a staff engineer or step on the manager's path.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;You'll have the freedom to experiment.&lt;/strong&gt; We do hack days/hack weeks where you can experiment with new technologies and new ways of working. Our design system (&lt;a href="https://dirtyswan.design/"&gt;dirtyswan.design&lt;/a&gt;) actually came out of a hack day. More on hack days can be found &lt;a href="https://dev.to/feather-insurance/hack-days-at-feather-44g3"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;You'll help us contribute to open source.&lt;/strong&gt; We're big believers in building in the open. We love the way GitLab, Artsy, Sentry, and others contribute to open source, and we're following that path too!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;You'll decide where to work from.&lt;/strong&gt; We are a remote company mostly hiring in Europe. You'll be able to work anywhere so long that you stay within +-1h the CET timezone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What you'll be responsible for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;In this role, you’ll work in a small cross-functional product team with other developers, product owners, and designers.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What working at Feather will be like:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A lot of hands-on coding on challenging projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentoring our junior and mid-level developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interviewing engineers and making hiring decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborating and communicating with other teams and departments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Giving technical talks as well as running technical demos and workshops&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proposing architectural changes using &lt;a href="https://blog.pragmaticengineer.com/scaling-engineering-teams-via-writing-things-down-rfcs/"&gt;our RFC process&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing posts for &lt;a href="https://dev.to/feather-insurance/"&gt;our technical blog&lt;/a&gt; and working on open source&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And much more!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;As an example,&lt;/strong&gt; check out some of the items from our roadmap in no particular order:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preparing for new countries – that is introducing localization, i18n and reusable signup flows – to offer our products outside Germany and in multiple languages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Setting up a headless CMS to help the marketing team iterate faster on landing pages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributing to our generic and type-safe questionnaire engine similar to Typeform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coming up with tools to help increase the speed of our Frontend team while maintaining top code quality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sharing parts of our development process as posts on our &lt;a href="https://dev.to/feather-insurance/"&gt;dev.to blog&lt;/a&gt; and giving talks at meet-ups and conferences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Iterating on our authentication system to protect customer accounts from XSS and share authentication patterns across multiple apps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building a secure, GDPR compliant way to communicate with customers inside our existing app&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Your profile&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re an excellent communicator both around technical and non-technical people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Significant experience as a frontend engineer with strong knowledge of JavaScript, HTML, and CSS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can write performant, consistent, and accessible user interfaces using modern JavaScript libraries (React, Vue, Angular, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using a component-oriented approach and thinking in a reusable way. &lt;a href="https://dirtyswan.design/"&gt;Our design system&lt;/a&gt; is a great example for that.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can write clean, maintainable, and reusable code and make design decisions regarding the architecture of the services that you’ll be implementing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are familiar with modern CI/CD and developer tooling such as linters and testing frameworks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with static typing and code analysis. We're using TypeScript for most of our projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have some experience with monitoring, logging, and caching solutions on frontend applications used by thousands of users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are proactive in suggesting alternative solutions and pushing your ideas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Does this sound like a good fit for you? Apply now!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At Feather, we are huge advocates for diversity and inclusion. From LGBTQ+ events to open discussions about eliminating bias, we highly encourage people from underrepresented groups to apply.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We encourage people without degrees to apply: we believe that what you’ve worked on and achieved is way more important than on-paper qualifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/feather-senior-frontend-engineer-react-eu-remote-or-relocation-to-berlin"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/feather-senior-frontend-engineer-react-eu-remote-or-relocation-to-berlin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 14:42:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 14:42:26 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/feather-senior-frontend-engineer-react-eu-remote-or-relocation-to-berlin</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/feather-senior-frontend-engineer-react-eu-remote-or-relocation-to-berlin</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/6914/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Proxify AB: Senior Front-end Developer: Long-term job - 100% Remote</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/6914/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Sweden
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://career.proxify.io"&gt;http://career.proxify.io&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are searching for a Senior Front-End Developer (Angular.js/React.js). You can be a perfect candidate if you are growth-oriented, you take pleasure in your work, and you enjoy working on new ideas to develop exciting products. By joining Proxify, you will get considerable opportunities to work with leading brands and amazing startups to build their next product and growth features. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we are looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have +3 years experience with React.js/Angular.js;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You follow best practices and conventions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant experience in CI/CD and related tools;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible and able to work with minimal supervision;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upper-intermediate English level;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can communicate well with both technical and non-technical clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nice-to-have:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Timezone: CET (+/- 3 hours);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic back-end knowledge for minor back-end jobs where necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build reusable code and libraries for future use;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure the technical feasibility of UI/UX designs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transform visual designs and wireframes into working products;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accurate planning of the feature delivery;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with other team members and stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;What we offer:&lt;/strong&gt;💻 &lt;strong&gt;100% remote work&lt;/strong&gt;: Work from anywhere.👌🏻 &lt;strong&gt;Flexibility&lt;/strong&gt;: The ability to change the project to another one.💵 &lt;strong&gt;Financial growth&lt;/strong&gt;: Competitive compensation and performance-based increases.🧘🏻‍♂️ &lt;strong&gt;Freedom&lt;/strong&gt;: Very flexible working schedule.🚀 &lt;strong&gt;360 degree growth&lt;/strong&gt;: Opportunities for professional development and personal growth.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your benefits with Proxify:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Be part of Proxify community&lt;/strong&gt;: Network with like-minded and enthusiastic individuals to make a difference. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Make an impact&lt;/strong&gt;: You get the opportunity to work on the projects that inspire you and add value to your career.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Transparency&lt;/strong&gt;: Contracts with transparency in earnings and working hours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Save your time&lt;/strong&gt;: Fast and efficient hiring process to match you with the project of your preference.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Ownership: &lt;/strong&gt;Take ownership of your work and enjoy more freedom in your career.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/proxify-ab-senior-front-end-developer-long-term-job-100-remote"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/proxify-ab-senior-front-end-developer-long-term-job-100-remote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 12:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 12:47:24 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/proxify-ab-senior-front-end-developer-long-term-job-100-remote</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/proxify-ab-senior-front-end-developer-long-term-job-100-remote</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cavallo: Senior Front End Developer (React)</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Grand Rapids, Michigan
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.cavallo.com/"&gt;https://www.cavallo.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Cavallo is seeking a Senior Front End Developer to translate designs into code and build a thoughtful, functional experience for our customers. Working alongside our Product and Development Teams, the Senior Front End Developer will brainstorm on the look and feel of our solutions, generate website mockups/prototypes and create usable, aesthetically pleasing applications. The Senior Front End Developer should be a creative, innovative thinker that can help us continue to lead in our industry.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A typical day of a Senior Front End Developer would include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing functional and appealing web applications based on performance optimization and usability best practices;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with stakeholders in Product and Development to bridge the gap between design and technical execution;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating design and user-focused experiences;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Turning UX/UI Designs into prototypes that maintain brand consistency;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing well-designed, testable code with documentation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implementing new features using product owner specifications;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrating software components into a fully functional software system;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimizing applications for maximum speed and scalability;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyzing performance of applications and taking action to correct faults when required;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Staying up to date on emerging technologies and latest industry trends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is the job for you if:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have 5+ years of Front End Development experience and a strong knowledge base in React and Typescript;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have earned a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science or other related field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a keen eye for layout aesthetics;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a strong technical portfolio that showcases a variety of abilities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You personify Cavallo’s Core Values;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your curious nature has you unafraid to ask questions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are passionate about innovation and creating useful software solutions for the Wholesale Distribution Industry;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are self-motivated, hard-working and strive to be the best version of yourself daily;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are looking to join a team of people who are eager to learn and share knowledge.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why should you apply?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Become a member of a #PeopleFirst organization that believes in instilling excellence in the people who make up our team;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create exciting, innovative solutions for a fast growing software development company;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with collaborative colleagues who seek out and value each other’s input and feedback;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong leadership who believe in creating enormous and measurable value for our Customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Benefits:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive Salary Package&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, Dental, Vision, Life and STD Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4% 401(k) Employer Match&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generous PTO and Work/Life Synergy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning and Career Development Opportunities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Cavallo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Cavallo is one of West Michigan’s largest, fastest-growing software companies. We’re seeking the self-motivated, the hard-working, the problem solvers, and the dedicated to join our team of experts. We're focused on helping businesses grow, expand, or reshape how they do things by approaching each and every problem with energy, creativity, and confidence. Ingenuity, adaptation, and evolution are at the core for us at Cavallo.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our Grand Rapids-based headquarters is focused on helping change the way organizations do business through our software products, customizations, expertise, and support. Our enterprise software solutions work with leading business applications, Microsoft Dynamics GP and Business Central, and integrate with a wide range of apps and platforms. Cavallo has been in the business of helping manufacturing and distribution companies increase productivity and efficiency since 2003. We got our start when a small business owner tasked a software developer with transforming a pile of clipboards and legal pads into a streamlined, efficient inventory management system. We have been sharing ideas and innovating ever since.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;At Cavallo, we're always looking for talented individuals to join our team of professionals. We believe our success is built on the abilities of our employees, and we strive to create a challenging and rewarding environment where all individuals are respected and encouraged to grow. Reach out to us today!&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/cavallo-senior-front-end-developer-react"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/cavallo-senior-front-end-developer-react&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 15:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 15:35:12 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/cavallo-senior-front-end-developer-react</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/cavallo-senior-front-end-developer-react</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0064/3165/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>SocialHub: ReactJS Web Developer - Remote/SaaS (m/f/d)</title>
      <region>EMEA Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0064/3165/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Schütterlettenweg 4, 85053 Ingolstadt, Deutschland
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://socialhub.io/de/"&gt;https://socialhub.io/de/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;DOES THIS SOUND LIKE YOU?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You like to build clean and well structured Software that your clients love to use.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ve been making your way through the world of frontend frameworks for at least 3 years, have developed a variety of applications and have an understanding of the good and the bad aspects of each framework.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your ReactJS skills are strong. You know how to build large and scalable web applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You know how to spot performance issues and how to resolve them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using a DVCS like git comes natural to you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You enjoy working within a team, helping fellow team members find elegant solutions to complicated problems and would happily jump into a code review at a moment's notice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;YOUR REQUIREMENTS FOR THE JOB&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of commercial experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong proficiency in modern JavaScript, browsers (and their quirks) including stylesheets and DOM manipulation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous commercial experience building component-based web applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A practical approach to development including the reuse of shared components and open source projects rather than always reinventing the wheel.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge of the ReactJS ecosystem including Redux, Redux-Saga, Reselect, Styled Components.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An appreciation of good UI/UX design and the ability to translate wireframes into high quality, reusable code.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluid in the different approaches to storing and structuring data (e.g. Immutable Structures).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An understanding of test driven development with frameworks like Jest.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with browser-based debugging and performance optimisation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Common development tools such as Git, Babel, Create-React-App and Yarn have been part of your toolkit for a while.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some experience with React Native. Even if it was a small demo or side project.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Startup-Spirit (ambition, flexibility &amp;amp; willingness to experiment)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are able to work and communicate with your teammates through our core hours (11am to 4pm german timezone)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THESE SKILLS WOULD BE BENEFICAL FOR YOU&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of some of the new cutting-edge ECMAScript features.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you have experience with web workers and/or progressive webapps, you would definitely be hitting the ground running by bringing in new skills into the team!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some exposure to Typescript.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile app development in either/both the iOS and Android ecosystems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Commercial React Native experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience iteratively moving/upgrading an older code base to a newer platform. (We are currently migrating BackboneJS to ReactJS)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regular contributor or author to an open source project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WE HAVE TO OFFER&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company houses 2023: We rent houses worldwide - free of charge for you. Enjoy work and meet your teammates from all over the world. To work or to take a vacation, we leave it up to you!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible working hours and the possibility to work remotely.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An enthusiastic and friendly team in a productive working environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Varied and challenging activities in a constantly growing and future-oriented industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great coaching and development opportunities. We have an annual budget for external training courses and conferences. We previously attended GitHub Universe in London and Amsterdam.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An afternoon each sprint (every 2 weeks) to work on something that interests you. Want to learn a new programming language? That’s fine by us. It doesn't have to be work-related. It’s there to help you expand your skill set and keep the creative juices flowing. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always a cold Fritz-Kola in the fridge (if you decide to stop by our office). &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Join us for whole company get-togethers. Our past retreats have been in Belgium, Prague &amp;amp; Spain. Our next one is in Portugal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/socialhub-reactjs-web-developer-remote-saas-m-f-d-1"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/socialhub-reactjs-web-developer-remote-saas-m-f-d-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 13:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 13:01:51 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/socialhub-reactjs-web-developer-remote-saas-m-f-d-1</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/socialhub-reactjs-web-developer-remote-saas-m-f-d-1</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0077/5982/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Chameleon: Senior Frontend Engineer</title>
      <region>Americas Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0077/5982/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; San Francisco, USA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.chameleon.io"&gt;https://www.chameleon.io&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why we want to hire this role now&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We started &lt;a href="https://www.trychameleon.com/"&gt;Chameleon&lt;/a&gt; after being frustrated at poor user onboarding, and feeling required to speak with sales before we could start using new products.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As engineers, we want to solve the hardest problems, and apply our creativity to design beautiful software. It's tedious to build and maintain tooltips, or banners, so we built Chameleon to let the &lt;em&gt;product people handle that independently&lt;/em&gt;, while letting engineers focus on the core value proposition a product provides.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Chameleon exists as a layer between our customers' web applications and their users. This means that the software we build is for our thousands of customers and tens of millions of their end-users.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;As we gain more customers, they require our software to handle more and growing use cases. The way web applications are built is changing rapidly; UX patterns are getting smarter; organizations are embracing the product-led movement.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;As software becomes more self-serve, we will stay ahead of the curve to to better enable software around the world.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are looking for a &lt;strong&gt;Senior Front-end Engineer &lt;/strong&gt;who thrives in a remote startup environment, is passionate about building great software, and enjoys a wide variety of problems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You will be a key member of our engineering team, work closely with our CTO and enable us to improve our product velocity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What you will do specifically&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;You’ll be primarily working closely with the Product team on our React web-app in a modern tech stack.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Key activities we expect you to be doing include:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on our customer dashboard building new UI/UX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create, build and maintain reusable React components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write testable well documented code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make customer experience with Chameleon memorable and lovable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support keeping our platform secure and reliable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skills and experience that will aid success in this role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;6+ years&lt;/strong&gt; working full-time as a front-end engineer and &lt;strong&gt;4+ years&lt;/strong&gt; React experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience leading / collaborating with other engineers (Tuple)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency with React / JS / HTML / CSS. Opinionated about the right way to JS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfort and experience working with testing suites (Cypress, Jest)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Independent and self-motivated mindset; proactive in finding solutions while able to structure your own work with minimal management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be able to provide guidance and answers the first time, see blind spots and complexity before it impacts the flow of work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Derives joy and pride from refactoring and improving important code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a fully functioning workstation and a quiet place to work (and take calls) with a high-speed internet connection&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are in an &lt;strong&gt;Americas timezone&lt;/strong&gt; (EST, CST, MST, PST).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is your full-time job (no other part-time roles)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency (written and verbal) in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Learn more about our team, culture, and vision in &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/e38d308f67f641e8aaa0e4f687a3abb9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;our &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.notion.so/trychameleon/Work-with-us-at-Chameleon-e38d308f67f641e8aaa0e4f687a3abb9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;company page.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We believe individuals are so much more than their labels, and encourage candidates from all walks of life (all genders, ethnicities, ages, educational backgrounds, sexual orientations etc.) as we strive to build a diverse team. If you’re unsure, just apply! &lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/chameleon-senior-frontend-engineer-1"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/chameleon-senior-frontend-engineer-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 16:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 16:34:06 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/chameleon-senior-frontend-engineer-1</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/chameleon-senior-frontend-engineer-1</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maharishi Foundation International: Senior Front-End React Native Engineer</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; London (Remote)
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.maharishi.foundation/"&gt;https://www.maharishi.foundation/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.maharishi.foundation/"&gt;Maharishi Foundation International&lt;/a&gt; (MFI) is a US-registered non-profit that supports the development of new technologies and outreach opportunities for the worldwide Transcendental Meditation® (TM®) organisations. Over the past 60 years, more than 10 million people worldwide have learned the TM technique through personal instruction by tens of thousands of certified teachers. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;MFI is a growing, fully remote team of nearly 50 people, located around the globe but mainly in North America and Europe. As an organisation we are committed to leveraging modern technology and progressive management practices to make the TM technique and its related programmes more available to people everywhere. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We favor a healthy and balanced work environment with opportunities for personal development.  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are looking for a senior front-end engineer with a proven track record of developing React Native mobile applications. As we are a small but growing team, you will be responsible for the maintenance and support of existing app features as well as planning and scoping new feature additions and iterations.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You will be working closely with our team to launch a meditation and lifestyle application. Applicants should have a proven track record working on large scale, consumer-facing products with complex and intuitive UX/UI. Applicants should be comfortable working in a fast-paced environment, where each individual has a lot of influence and responsibility to deliver. You will play a vital role in the development and release of this application. There is an existing global community keenly awaiting the launch of this application, so the app will have an immediate, engaged user base. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The AWS backend is built using a serverless approach using AppSync (GraphQL), DynamoDB, Cognito and Lambda. Local development and stack deployment is managed using the Serverless framework, and CI pipelines have been implemented using CircleCI and Bitrise. Experience with any of these is a big plus.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About You&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You are passionate about creating beautiful, modern, and intuitive user interfaces on mobile devices. You are comfortable with cross platform development (for iOS and Android), and enjoy solving the challenges that come with such a codebase. You understand API architecture, and can take a data model and translate it into reusable and flexible components. You enjoy shipping clean, readable and reusable code. You are comfortable working on a distributed team spread across timezones and cultures. You are excited to use technology to have a positive impact in the world as a whole, and in an intimate way for each individual.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take over responsibility for the front-end development and maintenance, and work with our team to continue testing and releasing features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure the performance, quality, and responsiveness of the application&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with the engineering and design teams, contribute to the definition of specifications for new features, and own the development of those features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Guide the team regarding constraints and best practices in a mobile environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively identify and solve bottlenecks; fix bugs and performance issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain code quality, organization and automatization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure testing strategy is followed within the team - for unit and integration tests&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skills and Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in mobile app development &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience with React and React Native &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience on either IOS or Android native development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Typescript, Node.js, GraphQL and REST&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with code versioning tools (Git)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic understanding of using CI to deploy apps (we use Bitrise)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail to implement and bring designs to life using animations (we use Animated and Reanimated in some places)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of React Native limitations in native mobile environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of code signing for iOS and Android (we use Fastlane)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of best practices for mobile apps, like Material Design and Human Interface Guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of testing and deploying code in a production environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a global non-profit, working with a remote team or in a multinational organization preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English (written and verbal)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you are passionate about this work but do not have all of the skills listed we are still interested in speaking with you and encourage you to apply!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pay and benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our pay levels are set according to a formula that combines above-median market rate data for the role (we use 55th percentile of New York market rate for this role, based on &lt;a href="https://www.payscale.com/"&gt;Payscale&lt;/a&gt; data) adjusted for your local cost of living based on &lt;a href="https://www.numbeo.com/cost-of-living/rankings_current.jsp"&gt;Numbeo&lt;/a&gt; data. For Engineering roles, we pay the mid-point between unadjusted New York market rate and your locally adjusted formula rate.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We take the issue of equitable pay very seriously, and we apply our pay formula to all workers who work 80% or more of full time hours with us.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diversity and inclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We care about diversity - we strive to ensure all of our team feel included and can bring their whole selves to work but we also know that this work is never ‘done’ or complete, and that we can always improve.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our team is fully remote, living and working across 20 countries across the world, and we’d love to hear how you can add to our special culture at MFI.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/maharishi-foundation-international-senior-front-end-react-native-engineer-3"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/maharishi-foundation-international-senior-front-end-react-native-engineer-3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 15:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 15:04:45 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/maharishi-foundation-international-senior-front-end-react-native-engineer-3</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/maharishi-foundation-international-senior-front-end-react-native-engineer-3</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0077/5592/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Tesorio, Inc. : Frontend Engineer (Senior level) - North America/Latam (Remote)</title>
      <region>Americas Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0077/5592/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; San Francisco, CA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.tesorio.com/"&gt;https://www.tesorio.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Our mission is to build financial management technologies that enable the world’s most important companies to grow more quickly in a sustainable way that’s good for people, the planet, and business.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;When companies have strong cash flow performance they can shift from short-term acrobatics to long-term growth and innovation. These are the teams that change the world by being freed to optimize for all of their stakeholders, including their employees, business partners, and environment.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Opportunity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Cash flow is the toughest financial statement to understand but it’s fundamental to funding your own growth. We build the most intuitive and actionable tools for companies to optimize cash flow performance. Our platform analyzes billions of dollars of B2B transactions each year, users spend 70% of their workday in Tesorio, and we save finance teams thousands of hours. As a result, they can invest more confidently and anticipate their capital needs further in advance.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Our Accounts Receivable Automation platform is a leader in the market. We were named to the Top 50 Accounting &amp;amp; Finance Tools by G2 for 2022 and we were selected for the Intelligent Applications Top 40 by leading VCs and Goldman Sachs. Our customers are proud to say they partner with Tesorio.&lt;/strong&gt; We’re growing quickly and working with the world’s best companies, like Bank of America, Slack, Twilio, Box, and Ripple. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We recently raised our Series B. We are backed by top investors including BAMCAMP, Madrona, First Round Capital, Y Combinator, and Floodgate. We’re also backed by tenured finance execs, including the former CFOs of Oracle and NetSuite.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re now looking to hire talented Software Engineers in North and Latin America to join our growing team to help us implement a high volume of curated ideas and reinvent how complex financial transactions can be simplified. &lt;strong&gt;The projects you will be working on are critical infrastructure for many companies to maintain their cash flow. And the product is loved with an NPS of 67 and over 60% DAU/MAU.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We have a diverse, distributed workforce in over five countries. We don’t believe that people need to sacrifice being close to their families and where they’d prefer to live in order to do their best work.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What’s in it for you?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote from anywhere in North or Latin America.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our Engineering and Data Science teams work fully remote. We call our team "Remote Powered." At Tesorio, "remote" doesn't mean second-class.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fast paced environment where you have a daily impact.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;About you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are a passionate, talented frontend engineer ready to take ownership of high-impact product features in a fast growing company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can hold your own on the frontend.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are delighted by good design and bring that taste to your frontend work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have strong opinions, but you hold them loosely.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You love building and shipping magical products that will help thousands of companies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What you’ll do day-to-day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You'll work directly with product managers, UX designers, and backend engineers to build features on Tesorio's core product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on the frontend to develop new features from start to finish, including design of architecture, coding, and testing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tackle a wide variety of technical problems throughout the stack and contribute daily to all parts of our code base.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What you can expect:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will work on a small, nimble team with a product manager, UX designer, and backend engineers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will own high-impact features with your team from concept to launch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will have a strong influence on how features come together&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your team will have a chance to demo your work to the whole company each sprint&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ideal candidate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has 5+ years of work experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has strong knowledge of ES6&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert in React and related ecosystem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is resourceful and agile, and remains positive in the face of problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Empathetic towards colleagues and users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excited about the challenge of working in a fast-paced environment with a small and talented team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nice to have&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Typescript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Redux&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong bias towards frontend testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: we currently cannot sponsor visas.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/tesorio-inc-frontend-engineer-senior-level-north-america-latam-remote"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/tesorio-inc-frontend-engineer-senior-level-north-america-latam-remote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 21:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 21:43:20 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/tesorio-inc-frontend-engineer-senior-level-north-america-latam-remote</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/tesorio-inc-frontend-engineer-senior-level-north-america-latam-remote</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0076/4921/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Rainforest QA: Senior Engineer (Frontend)</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0076/4921/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Remote
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.rainforestqa.com/"&gt;https://www.rainforestqa.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Rainforest&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Rainforest QA is a distributed company full of smart, capable people from around the world who enjoy working together to make our customers successful.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our mission is to make product quality accessible for every software company. The Rainforest QA solution combines no-code test automation and crowdsourced testing in a single, one-of-a-kind QA platform, allowing anyone to get the exact insights they need to release with quality, quickly.  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a Senior Engineer at Rainforest QA you'll be part of an experienced and diverse team with members all over the world.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We were built as a distributed team from the beginning and we've committed to implementing tools and processes that allow for and support continuous and effective communication across the world.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Role&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on the Rainforest QA dashboard, our single page application where users manage their test suite, configure test runs, review results and set up their account&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on our tester application, where our crowd of testers connect to our virtual machine infrastructure to conduct tests and submit their results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on internal tooling to improve the development experience of other engineers and ship faster and safer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with product managers and our customer facing teams to analyze customer problems and design high impact features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead projects to implement those features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help other team members to achieve their goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuously learn about new technologies and ways to solve problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with our customer facing teams to triage, troubleshoot, and fix bugs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write unit and integration tests (using our own product!) to ship high quality software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About You&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience in Javascript and be extremely knowledgeable of the language and associated ecosystem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience in React (or equivalent framework / libraries) and be extremely knowledgeable of the framework and associated ecosystem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in writing and maintaining CSS for large projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enthusiasm with building web applications using modern tools like ES7, React, Redux, CSS Modules, Flow, and Webpack - amongst others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience of working on a Ruby on Rails codebase&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Even though this position is mainly frontend focused, we expect you to have some grasp of the whole stack to be able to effectively communicate with engineers across the team, and can make backend or infrastructure changes when the situation calls for it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience in engineering SaaS products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience leading projects with teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An ownership mindset: you should look not only at what you’re asked to do, but ask why you’re doing it and how it impacts on the rest of the product, our customers, and whether it makes sense. We expect you to be responsible for your work and to resolve any bugs you might ship&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excitement to learn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills and able to give and receive constructive feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Happy to review code and have your code reviewed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can work effectively remotely with remote team members (we are a fully distributed company)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable working in a large codebase with many stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How we’ll reward you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary plus equity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% company-paid medical, dental, and vision insurance coverage for employees, 75% for dependents (U.S., only).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited paid time-off (PTO).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A weekly allowance for lunches and a monthly allowance for remote office supplies or personal development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Semi-annual company off-sites in exciting destinations around the world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12 weeks of paid maternity leave and 8 weeks of paid leave for supporting parents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401k (U.S., only).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Note on Diversity and Inclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;At Rainforest we believe that diverse teams improve our business. We are an equal opportunity employer and do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, nationality, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Due to employment laws, we are unable to hire individuals internationally located in these following countries at this time: China, France, Iran, Egypt, Russia.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/rainforest-qa-senior-engineer-frontend"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/rainforest-qa-senior-engineer-frontend&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 17:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 17:45:25 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/rainforest-qa-senior-engineer-frontend</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/rainforest-qa-senior-engineer-frontend</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0071/4027/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Vaan: Frontend Web Developer for E-Commerce Agency [Templating languages,  Shopify experience a plus]</title>
      <region>Americas Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0071/4027/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; New York City
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.vaangroup.com"&gt;http://www.vaangroup.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Hi there! My name is Xavier Armand and I am the co-founder of The Vaan Group (www.vaangroup.com): a remote design and technology agency with headquarters in NYC. We’re looking to hire a &lt;strong&gt; frontend web developer &lt;/strong&gt;to work on e-commerce projects. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;What are we looking for? We're looking for someone who needs little to moderate oversight, has some well-informed opinions on their technical approach and is self-directed enough to get answers, can work with other developers, and are able to understand and maintain high-quality web applications. Well-qualified candidates have an excellent knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, deployment, refactoring, design patterns, and other programming practices. For this position, familiarity with templating languages/CMS's (i.e Shopify or Wordpress), are required. Again, experience with Shopify a major plus!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our clients range from large e-commerce enterprises (&amp;gt;$100M per year) to successful mid-stage ($1M - $75M per year) direct to consumer e-commerce brands. You can see the full range client work/portfolio at our website.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this role, you'd be improving, architecting, and supporting our portfolio of clients with their online stores. The is impactful work for brands that generate $10MUSD and beyond. Sometimes you'll be building custom themes using liquid. Other times, you'll be improving existing stores, implementing A/B tests and new feature ideas.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re a realistic group, not looking for rockstar ninja wizards. Our team resides (or is working from) New York, Poland, California, Spain, Brazil, Dominican Republic, The Netherlands and Norway.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Reasons to work at TVG:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exciting projects and clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multi-national team + remote team meetups in places like Warsaw, NYC, and Lisbon (once Covid passes)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profit-sharing program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/vaan-group-frontend-web-developer-for-e-commerce-agency-templating-languages-shopify-experience-a-plus"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/vaan-group-frontend-web-developer-for-e-commerce-agency-templating-languages-shopify-experience-a-plus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 22:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 22:49:30 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/vaan-group-frontend-web-developer-for-e-commerce-agency-templating-languages-shopify-experience-a-plus</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/vaan-group-frontend-web-developer-for-e-commerce-agency-templating-languages-shopify-experience-a-plus</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0006/6308/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Slab: Frontend Engineer </title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0006/6308/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; San Francisco
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://slab.com/"&gt;https://slab.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;At &lt;a href="https://slab.com/"&gt;Slab&lt;/a&gt;, we believe that knowledge is the foundation of any organization's success. When a team's collective knowledge is accessible, that team's potential is limitless. That's why we're making the workplace a source of learning and purpose through knowledge-sharing. Our product helps teams easily create, organize, and discover knowledge across the entire company, from non-technical to tech-savvy. Thousands of customers rely on Slab across their entire workforces, including Asana, Benchling, and Fivetran.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a small product-focused company, you'll join a team of experienced engineers, working on shipping features that delight users, fixing issues that get in their way while keeping our codebase, infrastructure, and tooling modern and well-maintained. We are globally distributed, with processes that minimize meetings and overhead, letting makers build on the maker's schedule.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technologies we use:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;React + TypeScript + Sass&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GraphQL + Apollo + Absinthe&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elixir + Phoenix&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Postgres + Redis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Docker + Kubernetes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google Cloud Platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sound like you?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a strong technical background, with experience solving complex engineering challenges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You love delighting users with great product experiences and resolving issues that get in their way&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You're curious to learn and demonstrate the ability to do so very quickly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You communicate with clearly and concisely, whether with teammates or users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are self-motivated and possess a strong work ethic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are passionate about knowledge-sharing and identify with Slab's mission and values&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we value:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Stay lean&lt;/strong&gt; - We strive for the greatest possible impact with the fewest number of employees. We empower our teammates with the most leveraged tools and efficient processes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Default to open&lt;/strong&gt; - We encourage and nurture open exchanges of knowledge and ideas — while acting with respect and regard for each other.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Think rigorously&lt;/strong&gt; - We act and execute after careful thought and examination of known information, while acknowledging the risks we accept in its absence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Say no&lt;/strong&gt; - We aim to deliver exceptionally high value in a small set of focus areas. We willingly abstain from good ideas to give only the most promising paths the attention they deserve.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;The best prevails&lt;/strong&gt; - Whether an idea or an individual, the best will rise to the top at Slab. Ideas we pursue can come from anywhere, and individuals gain responsibilities due to outperformance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Global optimization&lt;/strong&gt; - We believe that our mission — to make the workplace a source of learning and purpose — is the ultimate priority, above any single project, team, or individual.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Benefits:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full health insurance (USA) or stipend (International)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wellness &amp;amp; remote work stipends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$5k workspace setup, renewed biannually&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7-year options exercise window&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slab is an equal opportunity employer. We welcome people of diverse backgrounds, experiences, and perspectives.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/slab-frontend-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/slab-frontend-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 14:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 14:18:02 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/slab-frontend-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/slab-frontend-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BuildBook: React Software Engineer</title>
      <region>North America Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Greenwich, CT
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://buildbook.co/"&gt;https://buildbook.co/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;About BuildBook&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Home remodeling and construction projects are often a stressful and painful experience – but it doesn’t have to be that way. BuildBook is on a mission to eliminate that stress and bring joy back to home improvement – for everyone involved.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;BuildBook is the best construction management platform for home remodelers and builders. Our goal is to become the default choice for the over 550,000 small businesses focused on residential construction and remodeling. It’s a $540B dollar a year industry, and we plan to make a dent in it by creating the best product in the space. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Builders love us because we give them simple, powerful tools to run their business and help them keep their clients happy. Homeowners love us because we give them a feeling of control and help make renovations and new home builds less stressful.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are a remote-first startup with team members all across the US. We have a small, tight-knit team, a solid product that is gaining momentum daily, and big plans for the future. As an early member of the product team, your work is going to have a major impact on the future of the product and company. You’ll ship your work often and see its impact in the hands of real people every day.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Job&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;At this stage of our growth, we are seeking developers with experience or interest in startups and a love for building products that solve real-world problems. The ideal person for this role will be able to come in and hit the ground running. You’ll both help us iterate on our core existing feature set as well as develop completely new features from scratch. You'll need to work relatively independently, take feedback from everyone else in the company, mesh it with your own experience and opinions, and create an awesome product and experience for all of our users.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As an early member of the engineering team, you’ll have a lot of opportunity for growth both as an individual contributor and/or as a leader.  Your contributions will be foundational to the future of our rapidly growing platform. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our high-level tech stack is currently: Ruby on Rails, React, React Native, PostgreSQL, Redis, Bitrise and Heroku.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About You&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You have a passion for building apps that users love, and enjoy building technology products that help make doing business in the real world better for everyone.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You are intellectually curious and enjoy learning new things.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You are opinionated about technology while maintaining a sense of humility.  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You have experience with some part of our tech stack, either in part or whole.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You have an eye for design and genuinely care that your work functions correctly and also looks good.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You consider yourself a &lt;a href="https://signalvnoise.com/posts/1430-hire-managers-of-one"&gt;manager of one&lt;/a&gt;: You take ownership, set direction, make calls, and get projects across the finish line without a lot of oversight.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You understand that a successful product is a blend of engineering, business, and design input, filtered through the lens of user feedback.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You have the ability to wear multiple hats and/or have some relevant hidden talents or experience.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To be considered, you’ll need…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our requirements are flexible, as we’d rather be as inclusive as possible.  We’re interested in people of all experience levels, as long as they have some experience and aptitude for developing and shipping products, and the ability to work in a remote team.  As such, we’re looking for&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Several years of experience developing web or mobile apps; OR a portfolio of work to demonstrate your capabilities that includes at least one currently live revenue-generating product or open-source project with active users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with React; OR experience in a similar library (Vue, Ember, etc) and a willingness to learn React.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication skills and/or experience with remote work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Residence in North America and the ability to work in a North American time zone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Nice to have: BS in Computer Science, Math, EE, or other applicable degrees.  Experience with Ruby on Rails or a similar framework.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to Apply&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Please submit a cover letter that speaks directly to this position. Tell us about yourself, and tell us what interests you about this role at BuildBook. Share your past experience, portfolio of projects, lessons learned, and what excites you about building products.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We don't do whiteboard interviews or live coding - we care more about the work you've done than the algorithms you've memorized.  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The hiring process will look roughly like this:  a phone screen; a take-home project capped at an hour or two; a technical conversation on your project, past work, and experience; and a few conversations with your potential teammates.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compensation &amp;amp; Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We offer competitive compensation based on your experience and capabilities, as well as:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A generous benefits program that supports the whole you with medical, dental, vision, life, disability, and 401(k)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid holidays and flexible, take-it-as-you-need-it paid time off &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equity in a rapidly growing startup backed by top-tier VCs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monthly tech reimbursements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A culture built on innovation that values big ideas, no matter where they come from&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/buildbook-react-software-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/buildbook-react-software-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 21:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 21:57:51 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/buildbook-react-software-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/buildbook-react-software-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgencyAnalytics: Senior Frontend Engineer</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Toronto, Canada
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://agencyanalytics.com"&gt;https://agencyanalytics.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;We’re seeking a Senior Frontend Engineer to work in one of our product-driven teams, focused on building features that help our customers grow their business.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We work efficiently and iteratively to ensure our products are modern, easy to use and ultimately make our users happy. More importantly, we're looking for people to build a team of collaborative, supportive and high-skilled engineers that take our user's experience to the next level. You'll work with React, JavaScript and TypeScript to create new features, iterate on existing features and build a cohesive experience to our users. You'll have the opportunity work on a wide range of projects including greenfield features, experimental UX/UI improvements, paying down technical debt, improving existing features and everything in between.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You'll Work With&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Typescript &amp;amp; JavaScript utilizing ES2020+ standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;React ecosystem with Webpack, NPM and UI Router&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frontend mono-repo service architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Service-based API with query interface&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS Modules and an in-house tailored Component Library&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Non-blocking CI/CD tooling with on-demand staging for every PR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Automated testing via Jest &amp;amp; Cypress, formatting with EsLint &amp;amp; Prettier&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You'll Do&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your time will be divided between new features, UI/UX improvements, repaying technical debt, and improving existing features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You'll prioritize and work on multiple projects from start to finish, balancing quality, stability and project delivery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You'll review your teammates' work, help set high standards, and look for ways to improve the overall quality of our codebase&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You'll work within your team to achieve technical excellence by taking a collaborative approach to architecture, technical patterns, and complex problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work-life balance is a priority at AgencyAnalytics, so you'll have the flexibility to work the way that suits you best&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Job requirements&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have 5+ years of professional experience in the modern JavaScript ecosystem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have professional experience working in a cross-functional team of 5+ members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have the ability to communicate effectively with other engineers, while building trust, credibility, and mutual success with your peers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a strong understanding of the challenges of working in engineering and delivering products in a remote work environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have the drive to stay current with technological changes and set a high standard for yourself&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a strong sense for UI quality and a good understanding of user behavior&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You proactively take on a challenge and help the team solve problems from start to finish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we offer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully remote workplace&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible working hours&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 weeks paid vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited paid sick days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quarterly profit sharing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parental &amp;amp; Maternity leave top-ups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extended health benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health spend account&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equipment credit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fitness/Education credit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Internet reimbursement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Training and certification reimbursement\&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Travel reimbursement for company events&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our Application Process&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complete a self-assessment (5 - 10 minutes) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Non-technical introduction interview (15 - 30 minutes) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take-home engineering challenge &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interview with the Hiring Committee (30 - 45 minutes) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Offer extended to successful applicants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/agencyanalytics-senior-frontend-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/agencyanalytics-senior-frontend-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 16:52:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 16:52:33 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/agencyanalytics-senior-frontend-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/agencyanalytics-senior-frontend-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UpStack Technologies, Inc.: React.js Software Developer - Remote</title>
      <region>Americas Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; New York
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://upstack.co/careers?source=wework"&gt;https://upstack.co/careers?source=wework&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Upstack is a friendly team of the world’s most talented freelance developers, working remotely for some of the coolest start-ups. It’s fun and challenging to join the top 1% of the world’s developers. We have a strong focus on quality clients and developers and try to work on software that we love! Upstack is officially based in New York City and we have offices in NYC and LA. We also have development hubs opening up all around the place with our first in Brasov, Romania. Our developers work from home and co-working spaces and sometimes even on the beach! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;The work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Work with a small team of top-tier developers who are designing great user experiences and building truly great applications for web &lt;br&gt;- Participate in scrums consisting of cross-functional teams, both software and hardware &lt;br&gt;- Ensure that features are being delivered efficiently and on-time &lt;br&gt;- In addition to code contribution, you will also participate in architectural review and design &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Minimum qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Bachelor's degree in Computer Science or equivalent practical experience &lt;br&gt;- 5+ years work experience as a software engineer or relevant experience &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Preferred qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;- 5+ yrs of experience in developing JavaScript Applications &lt;br&gt;- Deep understanding of React.JS framework &lt;br&gt;- Proven track record of shipping software and successfully released apps (please include names and links on your resume) &lt;br&gt;- Strong attention to detail on every line of code, every unit test, and every commit message &lt;br&gt;- Comfortable with rapid development cycles and tight schedules &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Benefits when working with Upstack&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;remote first - you can work from anywhere you choose;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;flexible working hours;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ability to choose the project and the team;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;support for personal and professional growth;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;We love when engineers send us a link to their Github and/or StackOverflow accounts, technical blog, or links to apps they've shipped.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/upstack-technologies-inc-react-js-software-developer-remote"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/upstack-technologies-inc-react-js-software-developer-remote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 15:40:35 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/upstack-technologies-inc-react-js-software-developer-remote</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/upstack-technologies-inc-react-js-software-developer-remote</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0064/6098/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>CompanyCam: Mobile Developer</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0064/6098/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Lincoln, NE
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://companycam.com"&gt;https://companycam.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;The Role&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We’re looking for a sharp, self-motivated, problem-solving &lt;strong&gt;Mobile Developer&lt;/strong&gt; to join our engineering team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a &lt;strong&gt;Mobile Developer&lt;/strong&gt;, you’ll work alongside other engineers, designers, and product managers to tackle everything from huge company initiatives to modest but important bug fixes, &lt;strong&gt;from start to finish&lt;/strong&gt;. You’ll also collaborate cross-functionally with your product team on discovery, helping to assess the direction and feasibility of product changes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Most importantly, &lt;strong&gt;you’ll actively contribute to the evolution of the culture and processes of a growing engineering team&lt;/strong&gt;, especially our client engineering discipline (this is what we call the devs who work in React and React Native). We want developers with opinions on patterns, code organization, and processes to help make sure our codebases scale healthily, and an interest in mentoring to help make sure our developers do too. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Working at CompanyCam&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our engineering team is &lt;strong&gt;remote-first&lt;/strong&gt;, spanning every time zone in the United States. We welcome people from &lt;strong&gt;all backgrounds&lt;/strong&gt; and really don't care whether or not you have a CS degree or even a high school diploma. All that matters is that you're not an a**hole and you're good at what you do.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Our Product and Engineering departments also do things a little differently than what you might be used to.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We use a customized version of Basecamp’s &lt;a href="https://basecamp.com/shapeup"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shape Up&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; method (fused with empowered product teams a la Marty Cagan's &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/INSPIRED-Create-Tech-Products-Customers/dp/1119387507/ref=sr_1_1?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=inspired&amp;amp;qid=1591733279&amp;amp;sr=8-1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inspired&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;) to organize and execute our work. That means you’ll work in a close-knit team consisting of a product manager, a product designer, and other engineers on an area of the product in 3-week cycles.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;During cycles you'll spend most of your time implementing product improvements, but you'll also work with your team shaping (generating and vetting) product improvements for next cycle. After each cycle your team will stop, reset, and choose to tackle another cycle or take a 1-3 week &lt;strong&gt;cool-down&lt;/strong&gt; (a period of undirected work where you’ll pursue educational opportunities, work on pet projects, or smash some bugs that have been nagging at you). Rinse and repeat until code nirvana.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Wait, I think that &lt;strong&gt;cool-down&lt;/strong&gt; thing deserves an extra call out: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;We build into our process 25% of an engineer's time for undirected work&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Sounds nice, right? &lt;strong&gt;No sprinting, no scrumming, no death by 1,000 meetings&lt;/strong&gt;. We protect our engineers' time, treat them like adults, and trust them to get their work done. We’re also big on not overworking people. Put in your eight hours of focused, quality work and then TURN. SLACK. OFF. &lt;strong&gt;No nights and weekends&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our larger company culture is also refreshingly chill. We have fun, learn from each other, and don’t take ourselves too seriously.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We cover the important stuff too. We &lt;strong&gt;pay well,&lt;/strong&gt; offer &lt;strong&gt;unlimited vacation&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;meaningful equity&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;health insurance&lt;/strong&gt;, and&lt;a href="https://companycam.com/careers#Benefits"&gt;other benefits&lt;/a&gt;. This is a salaried position at CompanyCam. Our starting salary for this role begins at &lt;strong&gt;$145,000&lt;/strong&gt; and moves upward based on experience. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;And if I may (uncomfortably) toot our own horn for a second: our devs love working here! In this hyper-competitive software development job market, guess how many of our developers have chosen to leave in the last 2 years. Seriously, guess. Ready? ...One! &lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We Ask of You&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Must-haves&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;These are our non-negotiables:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Show up&lt;/strong&gt;: give us your best and have the courage to do difficult but necessary stuff.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Grow up&lt;/strong&gt;: take responsibility, learn continuously, and have a growth mindset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Do good&lt;/strong&gt;: treat your co-workers and customers the way you want to be treated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience with and knowledge of &lt;strong&gt;React Native&lt;/strong&gt;,&lt;strong&gt;iOS &lt;/strong&gt;(Swift, Objective-C), and &lt;strong&gt;Android &lt;/strong&gt;(Kotlin, Java) development&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;3 or more years of experience working as a professional software engineer&lt;/strong&gt;. (Not all years of experience are created equal, so this one isn't set in stone)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Reside permanently and currently somewhere in the U.S or Canada.&lt;/strong&gt; Alas, we're not set up to hire outside of the U.S and Canada.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Nice-to-haves&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Day to day, most of your work will be on the JavaScript side of React Native, but, of course, that’s not all you’ll work with. While experience with the following technologies are &lt;em&gt;not required&lt;/em&gt; (we’re cool with some on-the-job learning), you will see them with varying levels of frequency:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;React Native (often)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GraphQL &amp;amp; REST (often)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apollo &amp;amp; Redux (often)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Android Studio &amp;amp; Xcode &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Java &amp;amp; Objective-C&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OpenGL &amp;amp; Metal (just a touch)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ruby on Rails (just a touch)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Ready to apply?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you share our passion for serving our customers and &lt;strong&gt;bringing truth and transparency&lt;/strong&gt; to the contracting industry, we’d love to review your application!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;This position can be U.S. or Canadian remote &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;or &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;in our Lincoln, NE office. At least one year of remote experience is required if you plan on working remotely. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We are not accepting applicants outside the U.S. and Canada at this time.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/companycam-mobile-developer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/companycam-mobile-developer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 20:49:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 20:49:44 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/companycam-mobile-developer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/companycam-mobile-developer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0018/9927/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>NationBuilder: UI Engineer</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0018/9927/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Remote within the United States
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://nationbuilder.com/"&gt;https://nationbuilder.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;NationBuilder is seeking a visually oriented UI engineer with a strong command of React, HTML, and CSS. You will be a co-owner of &lt;a href="http://nationbuilder.design/"&gt;Radius&lt;/a&gt;, the NationBuilder product pattern library, and be responsible for translating design requirements into functional and polished user interfaces across the NationBuilder product. You will also be responsible for the maintenance and nurturing of NationBuilder’s stock website theme templates, used by hundreds of thousands of websites around the world. This is a remote position (within the U.S.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;This is an excellent position for someone who thrives working in creative environments. You should have experience hacking existing frameworks, and have no problem building your own. You will report directly to the VP of Design. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;NationBuilder offers everyone the technology and community infrastructure to power organizations, movements, and campaigns. Our customers range from nonprofits and political parties, to corporations and individuals just getting started - essentially anyone who’s building a community of people to make something happen in the world. To learn more about NationBuilder, read our&lt;a href="https://nationbuilder.com/mission"&gt; mission, beliefs and values&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are looking for someone who...&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has a strong command of HTML/CSS/JavaScript, cross-browser development, and writes semantic, scalable code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has experience creating React components, writing tests, and delivering delightful user experiences through their command of JavaScript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has experience building out polished, functional user interfaces in web applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has experience working on website themes and a familiarity with Bootstrap&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is strongly visually oriented and precise in code, communication, and documentation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is a pragmatic problem solver, knowing how to find the middle ground between "perfect, but takes forever to code" and "fixes it now, but nobody will ever be able to understand what I did."&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is a clear and concise communicator with excellent collaboration skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is humble, passionate about personal growth, and would rather be “better” than “right.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively seeks out feedback and welcomes it as an opportunity to grow.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has a strong work ethic, a quick learner and is willing to work with a fast-paced team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apply&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;To apply, submit your resume, a link to your portfolio or recent work, and tell us why you're a good fit for the job in 280 characters or less (like a tweet, but you don't have to actually tweet it)!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;NationBuilder is an equal opportunity employer and we value inclusion. We are committed to finding talent that is not determined on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/nationbuilder-ui-engineer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/nationbuilder-ui-engineer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:43:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:43:26 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/nationbuilder-ui-engineer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/nationbuilder-ui-engineer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0018/4200/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Aurora Solar: Software Engineer, Frontend (Remote)</title>
      <region>North America Only</region>
      <category>Front-End Programming</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0018/4200/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; San Francisco, CA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.aurorasolar.com"&gt;https://www.aurorasolar.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Aurora Solar is a fast-growing Series C company on a mission to create a future of solar energy for all. Aurora makes the software that is enabling society to transition to a world powered by solar power. It’s our goal to have every solar installation in the world pass through our software, which has already been used to design millions of solar projects. Named one of “The Best Places To Work in 2021” by &lt;a href="https://www.builtinsf.com/company/aurora-solar"&gt;BuiltInSF.com&lt;/a&gt; and awarded #1 Solar Software platform by Solar Power World, Aurora is disrupting the energy industry and changing the course of history. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are looking for a frontend software engineer who will help take our cloud-based solar design software, which is used by thousands of solar companies worldwide, to the next level of functionality and interactivity. If you are interested in bringing cutting-edge design methods to a fast-growing solar industry and want to help society transition to a more sustainable future, we would love to hear from you!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are a diverse team based in San Francisco, passionate about advancing the growth of solar energy. If you are looking for a stimulating and fulfilling role, come join us!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What you'll do:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build new functionality for our industry-leading solar design platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spearhead the development of new greenfield products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write high quality, well-tested code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement, guide, and influence Aurora Solar’s front-end engineering practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What we value:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of experience building maintainable, clean, and well-tested user-facing code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Love writing Javascript or TypeScript (React, Redux, Styled Components experience a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great engineering skills and strong computer science fundamentals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent teamwork and communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thoughtful balance between shipping code quickly and adhering to best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to perform and thrive in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with full-stack development is a bonus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Thank you for your interest in Aurora Solar. Currently, our interview process is taking longer than usual as we navigate the new normal of COVID-19. We appreciate your patience and look forward to speaking with you soon.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Aurora is dedicated to building a diverse and inclusive workforce of people who believe in and are passionate about creating a future of solar energy for all. We are an equal opportunity employer, we welcome and consider qualified applicants regardless of gender identity, sexual orientation, race, religion, age, national origin, citizenship, pregnancy status, veteran status, or any other differences. We encourage you to apply even if you feel that you do not meet all of the above criteria!&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aurora-solar-software-engineer-frontend-remote-2"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aurora-solar-software-engineer-frontend-remote-2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 20:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 20:27:39 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aurora-solar-software-engineer-frontend-remote-2</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aurora-solar-software-engineer-frontend-remote-2</link>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
