<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss">
  <channel>
    <title>We Work Remotely: Management and Finance Jobs</title>
    <link>https://weworkremotely.com/categories/remote-management-and-finance-jobs.rss</link>
    <description>We Work Remotely: Management and Finance Jobs</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/9141/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Front Of The Pack: Head of Supply Chain</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Management and Finance</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/9141/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Los Angeles, California, United States
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.fotp.com"&gt;http://www.fotp.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Head of Supply Chain will lead our end-to-end operations, including planning, sourcing, fulfilment, and logistics.  Your primary objective is to get the supply chain operation to a point where it can scale comfortably with our ambitious growth plans.  In doing so, you'll enhance our operating capabilities, optimize our processes, manage and improve our gross margin, ensure a consistent supply source, and oversee product initiatives from procurement and vendor management to logistics and distribution.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are growing very quickly, and the global supply chain headwinds are strong - but it will be fun and challenging.  As an early hire, you'll have the opportunity to significantly impact the business.  You'll be a crucial member of our senior leadership team and report directly to the CEO of FOTP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You'll Accomplish:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You'll drive overall supply chain strategy and execution, both short-term and long-term, across supply, inventory, 3PLs, transportation, manufacturing, and project management, ultimately scaling and leading the team required to take Front of The Pack to millions of customers and build the most loved and trusted pet nutrition brand on the planet.  This will include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;General project management&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Keep the wider FOTP team aware of timelines and expectations in physical product development progress and delivery.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Anticipate delays and bottlenecks and feed those expectations into project planning across the business by managing and fostering good relationships with all key stakeholders&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Managing Suppliers (including but not limited to...)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Ensuring all our trademark licensing agreements (TMLA's) are in place and up to date with suppliers&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Ensuring all relevant non-disclosure agreements (NDA's) are in place with suppliers&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Ensuring all invoices are paid on time to and are accurate to maintain relationships and good payment history with suppliers (we have a finance team to support)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Managing supplier relationships to keep pricing, minimum order quantities (MOQ's) and availability information up to date&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Ensuring all regulatory information correctly matches up with stock (CoA's, statements, data sheets) and label claims&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Ensuring our exclusivity agreement contracts are up to date and maintained&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;In time, identify and build relationships with new suppliers to scope out new materials and feed that information into product development plans&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Manage and execute PO's from start to finish (including but not limited to...)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Accurate forecasting of all ingredient, packaging and fulfilment materials&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Accurate placing of PO's whilst ensuring seamless documentation and communication of up and coming costs to finance&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Chase and hustle up on deliveries and ensure timely delivery across testing, manufacturing and packaging partners&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Problem solving when inevitably stock becomes unavailable or is subject to delay&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Deploy technical solutions to reduce administration time and increase accuracy / scalability&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Track stock level (including but not limited to...)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Keep a close eye on stock level and flag when new stock and/or components needs ordering&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Keep in contact with suppliers for accurate lead times&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Keep stock tracker up to date with locations and levels of stock across multiple sites&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Manage Co-manufacturers / Co-packers / Contract Laboratories:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Ensure our third party contract manufacturers and packers are fully and accurately briefed on technical specs for testing, blending and packaging&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Project manage production from end to end whilst keeping all relevant stakeholders fully informed on what is going on where and when&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Coordinate activities across tight timelines to ensure no delays by being on the front foot in managing very busy contract manufacturers who need tight management&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Stay on top of communications with co-mans/packers to ensure accuracy and attention to detail are maintained throughout the process to avoid any errors that could result in lengthy delays&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Ensure testing at third party labs is carried out accurately and on time&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Work closely with R&amp;amp;D/Innovation team to qualify and test new materials and raws&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Stay on top of release (quarantine) dates for raw materials and finished goods&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Manage third party logistics partners (3PL's):&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Ensure stock levels are maintained at 3PL's for pick and pack activities to continue uninterrupted&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Work with 3PL to ensure they are fully briefed on pack out procedures for all products new and old&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Anticipate and problem solve for delays (e.g. stock missing, wastage, damage and personnel issues)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Optimize processes to ensure our service levels meet the needs of our customers and business&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Margin management&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Own gross margin expansion strategy and execution end-to-end, driving sourcing, value engineering, distribution and opex initiatives.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Develop and implement processes and system enhancements to reduce costs and improve operational efficiency, accuracy, and customer service levels.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;New product development&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Work with leadership to advise and assist in the development of new products&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Help source suppliers and develop relationships with key industry figureheads in order to help in the development of new and innovative product ideas&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Confirm new suppliers with price, lead time, availability, and inventory projections&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Confirm new suppliers have a fully executed NDA's in place&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Manage expectations around lead times and product development&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Problem solve to help in developing options for bringing innovative products to life. This might include finding new contract manufacturers that work with niche materials, sourcing testing labs that work with specific niche ingredients, sourcing niche products to enable innovative product development.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;5+ years experience in supply chain roles, with exposure to sourcing, inventory management, demand planning, fulfillment, logistics and manufacturing.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Strong preference for manufacturing, supply and sourcing background; experience with consumer product or food categories and co-manufacturers a plus.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Experience in CPG omni-channel environment, including e-commerce and retail fulfillment operations; understanding of subscription business models a plus.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Demonstrable competency in demand planning, purchasing, and 3PL management.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Sense of urgency with bias for action.  A high level of motivation, disciplined mindset and self-starting capability with proven track record in operating in small or mid-sized companies; entrepreneurial nature and experience working in fast-paced start-up environments a plus.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Strong communication, teamwork, problem-solving and interpersonal skills with a proven ability to influence across functions and levels.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Ability to use data and evidence to inform and influence decisions.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Passion for health, wellbeing, dogs and/or animals a plus&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Working at Front of The Pack&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Being part of a small team means you will have the chance to really help shape the future of Front Of The Pack working closely with the leadership team and our team of world-class advisors.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;We are proud to be an equal opportunities employer and embrace diversity in our culture. We strive to create a happy and healthy workplace for the team.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;We promote a culture of flexible working - we're outcome/results driven &amp;amp; appreciate great people who have family lives too.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;We also offer a budget for personal and professional development as well as personal physical and emotional development.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;info&lt;/strong&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;FOTP is based in LA and London.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;FOTP has raised over $15m of venture capital by Tier 1 VC's in Europe and the US.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;This role is open to those who wish to be fully remote working but will be US-based.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;This role will come with stock options.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;This role has a comprehensive benefits package associated with it.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/front-of-the-pack-head-of-supply-chain"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/front-of-the-pack-head-of-supply-chain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 16:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 16:28:46 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/listings/front-of-the-pack-head-of-supply-chain</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/listings/front-of-the-pack-head-of-supply-chain</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growth Cave: Chief Operations Officer (COO) For eLearning / Online Course Company (Remote)</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Management and Finance</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Austin, Texas, United States
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://growthcave.com"&gt;https://growthcave.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Growth Cave is an eLearning company in the online marketing &amp;amp; advertising industry. We teach people how to sell online courses around their knowledge &amp;amp; expertise, using social media ads to get customers. &lt;strong&gt;Lucas Lee-Tyson (the CEO) started the business from his college dorm room when he had over $20,000 in student loan and credit card debt. In just 4 short years he has been able to grow the business to over $15M+ per year with 25+ full time employees, who all work remotely. Our reputation is one of the best in the online marketing industry and we are on pace to hit over $50M+ year within the next 2 years.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for an experienced Chief Operating Officer or COO to oversee, improve, and scale our organization's ongoing operations and procedures. You will be the company's second-in-command and responsible for the efficiency of business. You'll have to maintain control of diverse business operations, so we expect you to be an experienced and efficient leader.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Starting salary range: $150,000 - $225,000 per year&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is a fully remote position &lt;/strong&gt;- you will be expected to travel 1-2x per year for team meetups but other than that, you can live/travel wherever you like :) &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Design and implement business strategies, plans and procedures&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Set comprehensive goals for performance and growth&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Oversee daily operations of the company and the work of executives (IT, Marketing, Sales, Finance etc.)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Lead employees to encourage maximum performance and dedication&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Evaluate performance by analyzing and interpreting data and metrics&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Write and submit reports to the CEO in all matters of importance&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Manage relationships with partners/vendors&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Proven experience as Chief Operating Office or relevant role&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Demonstrated excellency in management, follow-through, delivery, focus, project management, and "people stuff"&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Demonstrable competency in strategic planning and business development&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of data analysis and performance/operation metrics&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Outstanding organizational and leadership abilities&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Aptitude in decision-making and problem-solving&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Training &amp;amp; Development&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Paid Time Off (Vacation, Sick &amp;amp; Public Holidays)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Work From Home&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Wellness Resources&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/growth-cave-chief-operations-officer-coo-for-elearning-online-course-company-remote"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/growth-cave-chief-operations-officer-coo-for-elearning-online-course-company-remote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 01:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 01:31:16 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/listings/growth-cave-chief-operations-officer-coo-for-elearning-online-course-company-remote</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/listings/growth-cave-chief-operations-officer-coo-for-elearning-online-course-company-remote</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EngagedMD: Director of Finance Planning &amp; Analysis </title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Management and Finance</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Washington, DC
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://engaged-md.com"&gt;https://engaged-md.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;You’re an extremely skilled financial planner and analyst looking to make an impact at a rapidly growing startup and lead the team helping to make that impact reality. We’re EngagedMD and we have a patient journey application used by more than 1 million users nationwide and internationally since its launch, and we continue to see enormous growth and adoption from medical clinics across multiple markets. This is an exciting opportunity to join us in our mission to make life easier for clinics and patients alike. You will have the opportunity to own the full FP&amp;amp;A strategy and process end-to-end, including building and maintaining financial models, performing month-end accounting and financial analysis, leading our analytics team and our contracted accounting associates, preparing reports for our board and briefing executives on key SaaS FP&amp;amp;A metrics. You’ll lead our analytics specialist and our revenue operations manager, and be the internal manager for our external accounting partners. In short, you’ll be the go-to finance and analytics expert in our organization while also closely collaborating with our executives and internal teams. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;This fully remote role reports to our Operations Leader, and candidates are required to reside in the United States. This role requires legal authorization to work in the United States. EngagedMD is unable to sponsor current H1B visa holders for this role.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What You’ll Do&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build sophisticated financial models in Microsoft Excel and Google Sheets to uncover and communicate the root cause of financial metric movement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead accounting professionals to deliver accurate and timely monthly financial reports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure the revenue cycle remains efficient and analyze each cycle for continuous improvement opportunities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leverage analytics to identify opportunities within the revenue generating portions of the business&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare quarterly financial reports for senior management and company investors &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track key metrics across the company, supporting detailed analysis of key company initiatives, KPIs and OKRs &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the team that manages and analyzes the company’s data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What You’ll Bring&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8+ years of advanced financial modeling experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced Excel and/or Google Sheets skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience with forecasting and budgeting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with accounting principles (US GAAP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong orientation towards analytical thinking and ability to perform data analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience building teams with a passion for providing mentorship, coaching, and development of the team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An ability to model EngagedMD’s core values and action principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A mission-driven orientation to all you do &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superior written and verbal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to thrive in a small, fast-paced organization &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in Finance, or equivalent, or CPA or CFA credentials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s Also Nice If You…&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are proficient with SQL or Python&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are familiar with data warehousing concepts and their connection to analytics and data-driven decision making&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have at least a passing familiarity with the fertility and/or healthcare industries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have successfully worked remotely with distributed teams in the past&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What We Offer&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive compensation and equity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, dental, and vision coverage heavily subsidized by the company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open Paid Time Off&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid family and medical leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generous paid holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) retirement savings plan &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;EngagedMD is an equal opportunity employer. We’re committed to diversity, equity, and inclusion. We believe our company and products are made better by the varied perspectives of our employees, each of whom we seek to empower and support in their individuality. We hire our team members on the basis of merit, qualifications, and the needs of our business in order to best achieve our mission to make life easier for the clinics and patients we serve.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;About EngagedMD&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;EngagedMD is a fast-growing B2B software company that has developed the leading patient journey management solution for the fast-growing fertility sector. Nearly half of fertility patients in the US use our eLearn and eSign tools and we also have increasing international presence. Clinics use our software to reduce repetitive, manual tasks and streamline the patient journey, which helps them increase capacity and growth while improving the patient experience and reducing doctor and staff burnout. We are known for having a collaborative, friendly, high energy and fast-moving culture and a focused, start-up atmosphere.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/engagedmd-director-of-finance-planning-analysis"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/engagedmd-director-of-finance-planning-analysis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 18:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 18:30:40 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/engagedmd-director-of-finance-planning-analysis</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/engagedmd-director-of-finance-planning-analysis</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/9069/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Cloudlinux: HR Administrative Assistant - REMOTE</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Management and Finance</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/9069/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Georgia
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.cloudlinux.com/"&gt;https://www.cloudlinux.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CloudLinux is a global remote-first company. We are driven by our principles: Do the right thing, employees first, we are remote first, and  we deliver high volume, low-cost Linux infrastructure and security products that help companies to increase the efficiency of their operations. Every person on our team supports each other and does what we can to ensure everyone is successful. We are truly a great place to work.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We are the maker of the #1 OS for web hosting providers. We develop CloudLinux OS, KernelCare, and Imunify360 by using the most innovative technologies. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a dynamic HR Administrative Assistant who has a passion for Human Resources and is looking to grow with our team! The ideal candidate should have strong organizational skills, open to learn all aspects of Human Resources and Talent Management from the ground up. In this role, the HR Administrative Assistant will work closely with the HR Operations Manager and our Talent Business Partners. This role will provide the ideal candidate with an opportunity to grow within all areas of HR.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As our HR Administrative Assistant &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;you will be responsible for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Manage and implement all employee engagement initiatives; send announcements and provide gifts/bonuses for birthdays, anniversaries, and other achievements&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Administer and track effectiveness of onboarding program&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Maintain and administer general HR operations tasks&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Assist finance team with benefit spend tracking&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Assist with employee relations issues&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Support the Talent Business Partners with the team's sourcing strategy &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Assist with managing the interview process &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Assist TBPs and HR Ops with onboarding new hires&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Other HR duties as assigned&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To be successful in this role you should have&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Good verbal and written communication skills.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal skills.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Great attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of Google Suite&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;English (B2 or higher), Russian (native or bilingual)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;At least 2 years of experience as an HR assistant or similar position&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Ability for teamwork as well as working individually.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Ability to work under pressure and meet tight deadlines&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Resourcefulness, initiative, driven to grow and learn&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What's in it for you?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;A focus on professional development;&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Training reimbursements&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Mentor programs&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Knowledge-Exchange programs&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Interesting and challenging projects&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Flexible working hours&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Paid 24 days of vacation per year and unlimited sick leaves&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Medical insurance reimbursement&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Co-working and gym/sports reimbursement&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;The opportunity to receive a reward for the most innovative idea that the company can patent.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/cloudlinux-hr-administrative-assistant-remote"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/cloudlinux-hr-administrative-assistant-remote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 14:03:11 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/listings/cloudlinux-hr-administrative-assistant-remote</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/listings/cloudlinux-hr-administrative-assistant-remote</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/8374/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>webShine: Search Engine Marketing Account Manager</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Management and Finance</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/8374/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Basalt, Colorado
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://webshine.com/"&gt;https://webshine.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;webShine helps businesses increase their website traffic so they can grow their revenue, even if they are limited by budget. We do this through targeted Google Ads and SEO campaigns. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Based in Basalt, Colorado, we work with small to medium-sized businesses in the US and beyond.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are hiring for a Search Engine Marketing Account Manager. This position has leadership and growth opportunities. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our work environment offers flexibility for in-person and remote work to whatever extent best suits your schedule and preferences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;** While this position is remote, we do require US-based residency. **&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;Account managers are responsible for the SEO and Google Ads campaigns for 20-30 clients. Client accounts range from 1 hour/month of investment to 10 hours/month. The estimated time to manage this set of accounts is 100 - 120 hours/month. Primary responsibilities include:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyzing monthly client reports, writing a summary recap, and emailing this to clients by the 7th of each month, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regularly handling phone calls with customers,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reviewing existing Google Ads campaigns each month and making incremental improvements to keywords, bid strategy, ad text, and more in an effort to maximize return on investment,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing client’s ad spend on Google Ads to ensure we don’t overspend,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing client’s content marketing schedules including reviewing copy from our copywriters, getting client approval, and publishing it on their websites,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responding to client questions about SEO strategy and tactics,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing client’s Google Maps listings in Google Places for Business,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic technical SEO optimizations including fixing broken links and responding to page not found errors with 301 redirects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Why webShine?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are a small, nimble agency that is dedicated to delivering results for our clients while maintaining a work/life balance for our team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We work with small to medium-sized businesses that see outsized results from basic campaigns that are consistently managed. At webShine, you won’t run the most complex Google Ad or SEO campaigns for enterprise customers. Instead, you’ll make a profound impact with basic campaign strategies for companies that deeply value your work. You will have the autonomy to make campaign changes, website updates, and more to continually drive results.  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Our work environment offers flexibility for in-person and remote work to whatever extent best suits your schedule and preferences. We encourage you to take the time to live a healthy lifestyle while working hard and having fun.  Our team members aren't micromanaged — getting great results for our clients is what counts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Experience Required:&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work interactively with a fully remote team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of experience in SEO and Google Ads.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Application Process&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;Please email a resume to lindsay@webshine.com. &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/webshine-search-engine-marketing-account-manager"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/webshine-search-engine-marketing-account-manager&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 15:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 15:55:37 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/webshine-search-engine-marketing-account-manager</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/webshine-search-engine-marketing-account-manager</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/8161/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Clever Real Estate: Director of Finance </title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Management and Finance</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/8161/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; St. Louis, MO
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://careers.listwithclever.com/"&gt;https://careers.listwithclever.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Job Location: &lt;/strong&gt;Anywhere in the US &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;The Opportunity&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are looking for our first&lt;strong&gt; Director of Finance &lt;/strong&gt;to oversee all of our financial operations. You will have the unique opportunity to partner directly with our executive team to build out our financial forecasting, reporting, and accounting processes. You will lead critical operational areas of the business related to bookkeeping, preparing comprehensive budgets and forecasts, and overseeing audit and tax functions. You will help develop Clever’s strategic and financial planning goals. As our first senior Finance leader, you will have the opportunity to manage and support our accounting team, as well as expand the department as we continue to grow!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You will:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead Clever’s financial planning and ongoing reporting processes, including our annual budget and forecasting for important expense areas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage, coach, and develop three direct reports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze, report, and translate financial data and performance, giving guidance on opportunities and risks affecting the business&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide strategic guidance on financial record classification and oversee the month-end close process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee accounts payable and accounts receivable efforts, including working directly with customers on billing-related questions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure financial compliance and stay on top of ever-changing requirements; lead internal compliance audits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage partners involved with accounting processes and oversee external audits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in payroll, ensuring all tasks are completed accurately and on time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain the privacy and security of Clever financial data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You have:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8+ years of experience working in finance or accounting – with at least three of those in leadership roles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep knowledge of accounting standards and financial planning principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep experience overseeing the month-end close process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience forecasting and analyzing financials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical skills and experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills and the ability to interact with people at all levels of the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a fast changing, start-up environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Grit and perseverance when solving unfamiliar problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An ownership mindset – the ability to self-manage deliverables and deliver work on time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and/or interest in managing outsourced activities and ensuring high quality work is achieved&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Incredible attention to detail and high integrity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compensation &amp;amp; Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$150k–$180k&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote work and flexible working hours&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personal Time Off starting at 18 days per year that grows with your tenure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6-12 weeks of paid parental leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive health, vision, and dental plans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;Clever is committed to a diverse and inclusive workplace where we can learn from each other. As an equal-opportunity employer, we actively welcome people from all backgrounds, experiences, perspectives, and abilities! Learn more about Clever here:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://careers.listwithclever.com/"&gt;https://careers.listwithclever.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clever-real-estate-director-of-finance"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clever-real-estate-director-of-finance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 17:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 17:51:29 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clever-real-estate-director-of-finance</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/clever-real-estate-director-of-finance</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photobooth Supply Co: Customer Teams Project Manager</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Management and Finance</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Santa Ana, California, United States
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.photoboothsupplyco.com"&gt;http://www.photoboothsupplyco.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you thrive in organizing complicated projects? Does working with cutting edge technology sound like your kinda Monday? ☕️  Oh boy, do we have a job for you. Bonus points if you also have a fascination for how the Events Industry works behind the scenes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We at &lt;a href="https://photoboothsupplyco.com/" class="external"&gt;Photobooth Supply Co&lt;/a&gt; are searching for an organized and motivated Customer Facing Project Manager to work with various customer facing teams within our company. Our ideal candidate has prior experience in project management and product launches, experience working with customer facing teams, and is comfortable with a fully remote team - spread throughout the world!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You would be coordinating everything required to advertise, support, and educate our clients on our new products. 🤩&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Goals&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensure all Customer Facing teams are executing their projects on time and with impeccable quality&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Oversee customer facing projects related to all new and existing PBSCO products for the following departments:&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Customer Experience (Support)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Customer Success&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Sales&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Marketing - internal and external partners&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Content - including our internal team and external partners&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Manage these projects and team members by:&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Maintaining and refining our project management tool for these teams&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Facilitate necessary meetings on these projects: take notes, lead meeting, record action items&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Attend relevant department meetings to ensure alignment on projects within team's day-to-day roles&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Using team capacities, you would be responsible for determining timelines and realistic deadlines for each team member and project&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Primary Liaison for Product Related Projects&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Main point of contact to communicate with all relevant Directors on team member progress within each department&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Main point of contact to communicate on the Product Launch progress and needs&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Oversee all relevant SOPs and workflows for supporting and launching Products&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Create &amp;amp; update workflows and SOPs when needed&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Regular review of team members utilizing SOPs and addressing as needed&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Ensure the team adheres to all Product related SOPs laid out by Dev and Product Teams&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Track &amp;amp; Manage Project Based Metrics&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Use &amp;amp; manage metric systems within our dedicated project management tools&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Be familiar with typical project management metrics and how to use them for forecasting&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Maintaining Product Support for Customer Facing Teams &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Managing the needs of updating KBAs, website pages,  workflows, FAQs — assigning these tasks and managing&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Most importantly, you MUST be kind, respectful, and thoughtful. Strong opinions are very welcome. Jerks are not.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Project management&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Project management applications&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Communicating with our fully distributed teams with excellent skill and care&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Strong familiarity with standard project management workflows and SOPs&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Proven creativity to meet deadlines despite all odds being against you&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🏥 Health Benefits&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;👴 401K for California Based Employees&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;📚 Education Stipend&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;💻 Remote Work&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;💰 Bonus Plan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🏝️ Annual Retreat&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;✈️ Generous PTO and Holiday Schedule&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;💼 Quarterly Financial Meetings&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;📊 Open Book Management&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;💪 Intimate Team&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/photobooth-supply-co-customer-teams-project-manager"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/photobooth-supply-co-customer-teams-project-manager&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 23:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 23:01:59 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/listings/photobooth-supply-co-customer-teams-project-manager</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/listings/photobooth-supply-co-customer-teams-project-manager</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toggl: Finance Lead</title>
      <region>Europe Only</region>
      <category>Management and Finance</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Tallinn
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://toggl.com/jobs/"&gt;https://toggl.com/jobs/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We are looking for a talented Finance Lead who strives to design, develop and maintain finance solutions and financial information at Toggl to enable effective budgeting, financial reporting, financial discipline and support decision making on management level.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;The salary for this position is &lt;strong&gt;€85,000&lt;/strong&gt; annually and we are committed to increasing salaries every year based on company and individual performance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You can work &lt;strong&gt;from anywhere in Europe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;About the Team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We are a global team of 100+ awesome people working from over 40 countries around the globe. We hire globally, you work locally - in the heart of London, a beach outside of São Paulo, or a quiet village near Florence, the choice is yours. Every few months we travel to meet up somewhere in the world and spend some quality time together. We place a huge amount of trust in our people, and we measure the outcomes rather than the work itself. Our values fuel our results.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Role&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As the leader of a small, cross-functional finance team, this role will be dynamic and hands-on at first, but we expect you to take a strategic grip of our finance domain shortly after settling in.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Your main responsibilities will be:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop, automate, and take ownership of budgeting and financial reporting processes that will empower our awesome remote team to make informed decisions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure financial compliance according to local and group policies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protect assets by establishing, monitoring and enforcing internal controls and audits;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely mainly with Toggl's senior management team to answer questions that inform and validate both current financial situation, as well as future financial outlook of the company and provide our team with the insights they need, where and when they need it;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead a small finance team and coordinate cooperation with external service providers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;One day you may be crunching through the numbers and preparing management reporting, another you could be designing a new automated financial process or coming up with a strategic direction for Toggl's finance domain.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About You&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are looking for someone with significant experience in finance who can think strategically about how the finance function works within a mature SAAS company.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;In particular, we would love to hear from you if:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have significant leadership experience. You take the well-being and growth of your team seriously and want to help each team-member succeed in their role. You give genuine, candid and productive feedback that helps the receiver learn and improve, even in difficult situations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a good understanding of financial reporting and the ability to distill complex analysis into accurate and easily understandable takeaways will be keys to your success;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have strong instincts and judgment about the business-side implications of sound financial management and planning;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You feel comfortable working with business stakeholders at all levels of seniority to understand their needs towards all things finance;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your English communication, both written and verbal, is great and you prefer to over- rather than under-communicate. You like transparency, openness, and asking questions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You lead by example and never say “that’s not my job." You are accountable for your team’s results, good or bad. You give credit where credit is due, and take responsibility for failure when necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;Bonus points for:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have experience with investor relations management or you have gone through a process where the company acquired external investments.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Freedom to choose when and how much you work - we only measure results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;24 days of paid time off a year, plus your local holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-person meetups for team-building (expenses covered)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-6 weeks paid sabbatical (depending on the tenure)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Laptop budget up to €2,500 and it renews every 3 years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;€2,000 budget to set up your home office, and additional €300 every year after 3 years of tenure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;€250 per month for co-working space membership and/or internet service at home&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;€4,000 per year contribution to use for training, workshops, and conferences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;€2,000 per year contribution for any equipment or services to improve and/or maintain your physical and mental health&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support for buying tools you need for doing your best work (even eyeglasses if you need a new pair)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/toggl-finance-lead-2"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/toggl-finance-lead-2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 12:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 12:40:55 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/toggl-finance-lead-2</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/toggl-finance-lead-2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/6463/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Community Phone: Senior Executive Assistant to the CEO (up to $100k per year depending on experience and location)</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Management and Finance</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/6463/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Boston, MA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://communityphone.org"&gt;https://communityphone.org&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;About the Opportunity&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Community Phone is looking for an Executive Assistant to provide organizational and administrative support for our CEO. This EA will be a key business partner to the CEO - helping to enable continued success. This individual will help manage interactions internally with team members at all levels of the organization, very often managing sensitive and confidential information. This person will also skillfully interact with external partners and customers.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What to expect?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Manage all aspects of the CEO's calendar across internal meetings and external engagements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Help identify the needs of the CEO, including To-Do-List management, facilitating introductions within and outside of the CEO’s network, ensuring he takes personal time, etc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Work with the CEO and other team members to create agendas and content for key meetings while developing critical action items and next steps.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Attend key meetings and track follow-ups and deliverables in partnership with the CEO.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Help to organize and plan internal and external meetings such as staff meetings, team building events, Company All-Hands, offsites, travel, etc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Coordinate all domestic and international travel and corresponding expense reporting requirements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Take ownership of key initiatives, helping the CEO reach his highest potential.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do you need to be successful?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Minimum of 4 years experience in supporting at the VP/C-Level.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Ability to demonstrate expert professionalism, discretion, and confidentiality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Ability to interact with individuals at all levels of the organization.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Bias to action, including experiencing keeping the VP/C-Level person accountable.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Strong collaboration and superb listening skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Expert prioritization and communication skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Flawless judgment in the management of confidential and sensitive information.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Experience executing administrative activities with high attention to detail, organization, and process.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What's in it for you?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Join an ambitious tech company reshaping the way people communicate&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;A generous amount of paid time off&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Enjoy various virtual events, including workshops, guest speakers, and fun team activities, supporting learning and networking beyond the usual work duties.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/community-phone-senior-executive-assistant-to-the-ceo-up-to-100k-per-year-depending-on"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/community-phone-senior-executive-assistant-to-the-ceo-up-to-100k-per-year-depending-on&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 22:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 22:13:39 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/community-phone-senior-executive-assistant-to-the-ceo-up-to-100k-per-year-depending-on</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/community-phone-senior-executive-assistant-to-the-ceo-up-to-100k-per-year-depending-on</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/7419/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Intent: SEO Specialist</title>
      <region>UK Only</region>
      <category>Management and Finance</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/7419/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Dawson House, 5 Jewry Street, London, England, EC3N 2EX
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://intent.uk/"&gt;https://intent.uk/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;The Role:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We’re looking for a creative and ambitious SEO Specialist to take control of our SEO efforts across one of our flagship financial comparison sites – &lt;a href="https://moneytransfers.com/"&gt;MoneyTransfers.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;The ideal candidate will work closely and is expected to take ownership of many core SEO functions including keyword research, technical SEO, onsite optimisation, staying on top of industry updates &amp;amp; all-round SEO support.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;As a self-starter you will be able to independently execute SEO work for the brand, chase results and be able to identify both quick SEO wins and longer term projects. You’ll be working closely with both the Head of SEO and VP of Financial Services to take the website to the next level.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;You will be responsible and accountable for the SEO performance of the website from top to bottom and not shy away from getting stuck in to fix errors, improve performance and ultimately grow our organic offering to drive revenue in both existing and new markets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilites:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working alongside the Head of SEO, SEO Manager, a Senior Digital PR manager and Content Manager and team of writers to achieve SEO growth through targeted content and campaigns within financial services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ownership of the SEO performance across MoneyTransfers.com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify weaknesses within the SEO profile of the website and develop strategies for growth in multiple international markets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep a minimum standard of technical and onsite SEO operational at all times – taking into account the impact of development projects and product launches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keeping ahead of and reacting to Google Algorithm updates, analyzing changes across the market and actioning projects as a result/in preparation of these updates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing freelance SEO specialists for international optimisation and localisation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Researching and prioritizing relevant information to form a content plan with SEO growth within it based both on internal needs and your own ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performing keyword research to identify search opportunities to ensure our brands appear in revenue driving SERPs (Eng &amp;amp; Non-Eng)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On-site content optimisation (best practice for E-A-T, internal linking, titles, content editing etc.) – including briefing a Content Manager on best practices for SEO within content briefs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Briefing technical site improvements, schema, page speed, sitemaps etc. into product and ensure they mean all Google guidelines / carrying out technical updates where possible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Error auditing, diagnosis and solution handling (fixing crawl errors, render issues, LCP issues etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Site maintenance (redirects, broken links, site cleanup, duplicate content etc..)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively performing on site audits and implementing improvements ongoing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/intent-seo-specialist"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/intent-seo-specialist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 14:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 14:46:48 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/intent-seo-specialist</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/intent-seo-specialist</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlphaSights: Engineering Manager (Remote) – US</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Management and Finance</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; New York, NY
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.alphasights.com/"&gt;https://www.alphasights.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This position is remote friendly. You will have the option to opt into one of the following work environments: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In-office: New York, NY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remote: Only if you have/will have a permanent address in NY, NJ, PA, CT, NC, GA, FL, TX&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;AlphaSights is the global leader in knowledge on-demand. We connect investment and business leaders with a dynamic network of industry professionals whose informed perspectives help our clients make superior investment and business decisions. With 1200+ employees and nine offices across the US, Europe, Middle East, and Asia, AlphaSights regularly ranks as one of the fastest-growing companies in the world. Learn more at &lt;a href="http://alphasights.com/"&gt;alphasights.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We’ve made terrific progress working in this new space, but there is still an incredible amount of work to do. We’ve only just scratched the surface on how we can apply technology to this problem.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;AlphaSights' Engineering Managers are the technical team leaders that excel at unlocking their team’s potential for high quality delivery.  They manage both the technical and the people side of their teams; being both a career mentor as well as a technical mentor for their developers.  They spend a majority of their time ensuring the technical excellence of their team, unblocking their team for maximum delivery, and communicating the team’s needs and progress to the rest of the organization.  As an engineering manager you are expected to be able to write and optimize code, as well as ensure that your developers can do the same. You'll work closely with a variety of people in the business to arrive at the best solution, immediately see the impact of your work, and get feedback directly from users.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We are looking for experienced managers who are interested in running (and building) technical teams and holding them accountable to an incredibly high standard.  You should be comfortable working across multiple languages, be excited to learn new technologies, and experienced providing technical mentorship to your teams.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;You will:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage a team of software engineers, including task planning and code reviews&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technically own (and typically build) large areas of our product and service ecosystem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with Product Owners to flesh out business requirements and ensure that the team is solving the right problems to help the business&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure that the team adheres to high standards and practices sustainable engineering&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help your team grow from both a technical and career perspective.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow an agile methodology for rapid, nimble delivery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;You might be a fit if you:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have at least 5 years of professional development experience, and have at least 2 years of management experience &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy mentoring other team members, including code reviews and tech talks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can balance deep work with cross team collaboration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoy writing code in a variety of languages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Constantly learn from and mentor other engineers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Don't worry if your experience or background doesn't match all of these areas, we believe a &lt;a href="https://engineering.alphasights.com/#team"&gt;broad spectrum of experience&lt;/a&gt; provides great perspective on solving problems in new and innovative ways and we’d love to hear from you. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;You might lead teams that:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build tools to schedule multi-party communication with heavy constraints&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Automate the detection and mitigation of risk in real-time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tackle the challenges associated with Information Retrieval including building recommendation engines, auto-completion, and data categorization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve our internal and client facing user interfaces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve and evolve our core infrastructure to continue to reduce developer friction for deployment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimize and scaling our overall platform architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who you would work with:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You would join a dynamic, multinational, and diverse team who enjoy solving interesting problems in a collaborative environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We have self-taught engineers as well as graduates from top Computer Science and Engineering schools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your co-workers will include motivated recent graduates as well as experienced industry leaders from companies such as Google and Amazon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Find out more: http://engineering.alphasights.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/alphasights-engineering-manager-remote-us"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/alphasights-engineering-manager-remote-us&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 16:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 16:27:39 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/alphasights-engineering-manager-remote-us</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/alphasights-engineering-manager-remote-us</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0064/4778/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Test Double: Engineering Manager</title>
      <region>Americas Only</region>
      <category>Management and Finance</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0064/4778/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Columbus OH
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://testdouble.com"&gt;https://testdouble.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Why We Started Test Double&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Software is broken, and &lt;a href="https://link.testdouble.com/about-test-double-agency"&gt;we're working hard to fix it&lt;/a&gt;. At Test Double, our mission is to improve the way the world builds software. While the goal may seem audacious, it’s what drives us. We believe that the current state of software development is not good enough and we’re looking for others to join our cause.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our Consultants&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Developers at Test Double focus on writing high quality software to solve our customer’s problems. We  implement solutions that are well-tested, easily maintained, and built with empathy for users. Many of our engagements allow us to work alongside our clients as embedded members of the team. We take on a &lt;a href="https://link.testdouble.com/types-of-services"&gt;variety of projects and clients&lt;/a&gt;, which provides a kind of experience accelerator.&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;About the role &lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The primary role of an Engineering Manager is to grow, facilitate, and guide the professional growth of our consultants. You will provide direct 1:1 support to software development consultants, as well as develop and execute strategic initiatives benefiting the Test Double consultant experience—from qualification and orientation to the connectedness and career development of our technical consultants. Your efforts will have a direct impact on the success and career growth of our consultants, enabling us to create more opportunities for our people and impact our mission—to improve the way the world builds software.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Core Values&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Knowledge sharing and continuous improvement are among our &lt;a href="https://link.testdouble.com/culture-at-td"&gt;core values&lt;/a&gt;. We're proud to support our Double Agents when they speak at conferences, blog, contribute to open source, and organize in their local software community. Another core value is that we’re owners. We own problems and solutions. And we’re all actual owners, because Test Double is 100% employee-owned through an ESOP.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Providing support and guidance to consultants on the development of their growth plans, including developing milestones and a system of accountability and support for the consultants as they progress along with these growth plans&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing tight feedback loops, coaching agents on how to give,  receive, and utilize feedback to improve&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fostering career growth for all consultants through regular 1:1s, career retros (feedback), goal setting, progression, and promotion discussions&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aligning agents to &lt;a href="https://testdouble.com/culture"&gt;TD’s mission, vision, and values&lt;/a&gt; by cascading company communications&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advocating for the interests of agents in balance with the needs of our clients and company&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building, supporting, executing, and continuously improving internal systems and processes to help Test Double scale sustainably&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fostering connectedness within the TD community and to our People Success ecosystem&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating clarity in and continuously improving our People Success ecosystem’s tools, processes, job/role descriptions, and documentation supporting agent’s continuous growth&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consistently contributing to Test Double’s internal initiatives and progression, as well as expanding technological capabilities&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience mentoring, coaching, and leading software engineers while guiding them towards continuous growth and success&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well-versed in supporting engineers in their ability to balance meeting stakeholder expectations with delivering quality software and practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consulting experience improving client software systems, practices, and teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to listen and communicate effectively across different levels of the organization, including addressing conflict&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adept at handling a healthy amount of ambiguity with a focus on iterative progress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in creating and delivering curriculums - (topical workshops, small group learning sessions, technical skills training programs) to increase the breadth and depth of employee knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Low ego, high emotional intelligence (EQ)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A mindset of continuous improvement, feedback, and inclusion &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Compensation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;$155k - $175k USD I $196k - $221k CAD&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Dependent on experience and interview process&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 weeks flexible time off (vacation and sick time)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10 paid holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10% Growth Time each week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up to 14 weeks parental leave (8 weeks at 100% of salary)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 week of conference attendance (and up to $3,000 of expense)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ESOP Employee stock ownership program - Test Double is 100% employee owned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New computer hardware purchase every 3 years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Co-working space reimbursement (1/2 rent up to $500 monthly)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 week Sabbatical leave after 5th year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 company-wide retreat experiences each year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health, Dental &amp;amp; Vision Insurance (we pay 100% of premiums for agents and their families)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;EAP benefits through CompPsych and mental health offerings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Short Term and Long Term Disability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Retirement contribution match of 3% of salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Life Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AD&amp;amp;D (Canadian-based Agents only)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/test-double-engineering-manager"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/test-double-engineering-manager&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 16:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 16:20:29 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/test-double-engineering-manager</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/test-double-engineering-manager</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rivo Commerce: Operations Specialist</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Management and Finance</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; United States
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.rivo.io"&gt;https://www.rivo.io&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Interested in helping build and scale a rapidly growing Saas Company in the ecommerce space?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;👋 Howdy! Stuart here, founder and CEO at &lt;a href="https://www.rivo.io/"&gt;Rivo&lt;/a&gt; :)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are you a scrappy operator, looking to dive into a fast growing Saas Company with hundreds of thousands of users?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are you looking for an opportunity to join a company where you will have a seat at the leadership team and have a direct impact on moving the needle for the business?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;If so - awesome! Keep reading. If not - no worries, perhaps we'll cross paths in the future.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;What is Rivo?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;We're here to empower ecommerce stores to create their own revenue streams through connecting with their customers. We want to help the decline of reliance on paid advertising :-)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We're a powerful marketing platform that allows stores to connect with their customers through loyalty, review and omni-channel marketing campaigns.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;About the job&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;We have a problem...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;but it's a good problem...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We have a wealth of opportunities that are in front of us - and not enough time in the day.. (Eg: Inbound Partnerships, Marketing opportunities)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We're looking for an energetic, Get 💩 done type of operator who can come in, implement key projects and move onto the next in lightning speed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is a remote, full-time role (40+ hours/week).&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Who you are&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can operate in a high-octane environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You utilize the Pareto principle (80/20)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prefer 5 minute daily standups &amp;gt; long drawn out meetings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drama-free&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience in a similar role.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable jumping on calls to build relationships with key partners, accounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Shopify or Ecommerce (not required, but nice to have)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Things we love ❤️&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Living by our GAINS core values of &lt;strong&gt;G&lt;/strong&gt;rowth Mindset, &lt;strong&gt;A&lt;/strong&gt;nalyze Before Assuming, &lt;strong&gt;I&lt;/strong&gt;terate &amp;amp; Improve, &lt;strong&gt;N&lt;/strong&gt;urture Relationships, and being &lt;strong&gt;S&lt;/strong&gt;crappy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping our fellow team members and having a stress-free work environment!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Things we avoid 🤮&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Micro-managing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Egos &amp;amp; Drama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wasting time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Salary&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;Salary is negotiable and based upon experience. Everyone should earn what they feel is fair.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;How to apply&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;Do you want to join our team as our new Operations specialist? Then we'd love to hear about you!&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/rivo-commerce-operations-specialist"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/rivo-commerce-operations-specialist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 00:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 00:03:30 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/rivo-commerce-operations-specialist</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/rivo-commerce-operations-specialist</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nagarro Digital Ventures: Senior Digital Project Manager</title>
      <region>North America Only</region>
      <category>Management and Finance</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; 
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.nagarro.com"&gt;https://www.nagarro.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;👋🏼 &lt;a href="https://www.nagarro.com/en/services/digital-ventures"&gt;We're Nagarro Digital Ventures&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We are a Digital Product Engineering consultancy who build products, services, and experiences— across all devices and digital mediums that inspire, excite, and delight. Our staff are located all around the world (9600+ experts across 26 countries, to be exact). We're looking for full-time, experienced Project Managers to help us organize and execute our client’s projects. &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do we mean by Project Manager?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Anyone who spent time in the industry knows the definitions of this kind of role can be pretty fluid from company to company. Our definition of the role is relatively expansive and successful &lt;strong&gt;Project Manager &lt;/strong&gt;at Nagarro Digital Ventures would have the following characteristics and qualities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Good with clients&lt;/em&gt;: you’ll have supporting roles to help you manage the broader client relationship, but you are the day to day point person that maintains client confidence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Self-directed&lt;/em&gt;: remote work requires self-direction, of course, but you are also the CEO of the project, you work with the client and your team to find and define the best way to execute the project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Collaborative&lt;/em&gt;: while you may be the “CEO” of the project, that doesn’t mean you are a dictator. We hire competent people, value their areas of focus and expertise, and work together to accomplish the task at hand.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Competent with Technology&lt;/em&gt;: you don’t need to be a software engineer/designer, but you need to be able to talk with software engineers/designers and understand the broad strokes of what they are doing on a given project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Desire to learn&lt;/em&gt;: we often help clients develop new products in a wide variety of spaces with varying levels of expertise. No one person can be expected to be an expert in every field, so you need to be flexible and willing to learn to meet client’s needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Ability to ask for help&lt;/em&gt;: even the most competent people occasionally find themselves over their head, either lacking the expertise or enough time to juggle the work. Transparency with both the client and internal executive stakeholders is valued; elevate problems you can’t solve yourself early to the right people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What does the day-to-day work look like?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Much of you day-to-day is defined by the clients and the projects you have. Often you are empowered to use the tools you prefer because no one tool is right for every job, though sometimes clients require specific tools that better integrate with their systems. This means skill requirements and responsibilities are a little fuzzy, but would include at least the following:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organize projects with tools like Jira, Trello, and Slack.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organize and run client and internal project meetings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Estimate new potential projects and define Scopes of Work with help from biz dev, engineering, and design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive on-time, on-budget delivery of Scope of Work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resolve issues and conflicts and assess dependencies and risks of the SOW.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage forecasting, time sheets, and billing efforts (with our accounting team) on your projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide internal and external project updates for clients and internal executive management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Occasional travel for in-person client meetings (0-10% of your time), once we are comfortably past the pandemic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What are the requirements to be considered for this position?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our requirements are as flexible as our projects can be, there is no bullet proof plan or perfect list of credentials or skills, but the following would put you in strong contention for the position:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the technology industry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Agile Software Development processes: running scrums and creating sprint plans. Project Management credentials are a bonus, but not required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience interacting with clients and finding ways to meet their needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience leading teams and launching products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience assessing risk, conflicts, and dependencies on a project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Availability during normal North American business hours. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the benefits Nagarro Digital Ventures Provides?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Our benefits include:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary, commensurate with experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open Paid Time Off&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parental Leave, family-friendly flexibility, and good work life balance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive healthcare benefits including health, dental, and vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work from home&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Equal Opportunity&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Nagarro Digital Ventures is an equal opportunity employer. We are an international team that celebrates diversity and are committed to creating an inclusive environment for all employees.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/nagarro-digital-ventures-senior-digital-project-manager"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/nagarro-digital-ventures-senior-digital-project-manager&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 17:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 17:32:31 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/nagarro-digital-ventures-senior-digital-project-manager</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/nagarro-digital-ventures-senior-digital-project-manager</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0074/5595/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Vaan: Project Manager for Design &amp; Technology Agency (eCommerce)</title>
      <region>Americas Only</region>
      <category>Management and Finance</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0074/5595/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; NYC
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.vaangroup.com/"&gt;https://www.vaangroup.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Hi there! Let's make this personal. My name is Xavier Armand and I am the co-founder and CEO of The Vaan Group (www.vaangroup.com): a remote UX design and technology agency with headquarters in NY.  We’re looking to hire a mid-level project manager to join our team.  Agency experience required.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our clients range from large e-commerce enterprises (&amp;gt;$100M per year) to successful mid-stage ($1M - $80 per year) direct to consumer e-commerce brands (these are the brands you’d be working with). You can see the full range client work/portfolio at our website.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re a realistic group, not looking for rockstar ninja wizards. Our team resides (or is working from) New York City, Warsaw, Berlin, Bergen, Seville, London, Punta Cana, Sao Paolo, Algiers, Dubai and Rotterdam. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The perfect candidate has well-formed opinions, great discipline, naturally established work habits, and takes delight in their work.   Personal accountability is critical.  They’re problem solvers that know every detail of any given project and serve as the ‘go-to’ for both clients and the Vaan team. They know what to expect, what to do next, and where they need to be at all times. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typically we hire completely remote but given the requirements for this job we are looking for someone located in the Americas.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- 2+ years of experience at an agency&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Direct experience managing E-commerce website projects, working directly with designers, developers and clients (strong preference for Shopify experience)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Problem solver&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Detail oriented&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Comfortable and happy to speak to clients and team members regularly&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Strong sense of accountability &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Previous remote experience&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Example responsibilities include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Setting weekly check-ins with clients to update them on progress&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Providing external stakeholders and internal team with weekly project reports/summaries&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Tracking and reporting project progress, milestones, budgets, and team member utilization&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Research and determine solutions (custom or off the shelf app) for client needs.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Coordinate the design process from wireframes to mockups to development hand off&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Track, assess and prioritize tasks for the dev team in Basecamp&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- QA, review and approve tasks by dev team&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Proactively determine next steps for the project overall&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Manage various data through the Shopify CMS including publishing themes, managing products, apps, etc.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Create tutorial videos&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Stay up to date on the latest features and offerings from our app partners&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Communicate with and manage projects for up to 3 developers&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Problem solve using design or feature solutions to UX and dev team&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Field incoming inquiries, assess project size and delegate for small projects&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- When necessary, interacting and finalizing tasks for clients&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where the job will grow&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re a 40-person remote-first agency. You’ll likely work with everyone on the team when executing projects but you’ll be working most closely with our Head of Client Services and founding team. You'll be learning, broadly, solutions architecture through what's possible with APIs, how we think through complex custom solutions for clients, and see how and where the future of online commerce is going. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are a mostly remote team so we value good writers who feel comfortable writing detailed explanations of feature requirements, internal requests and external detailed explanations.  We rely on Slack and Basecamp for project management. Must be fluent in English. Remote work is ok, but candidates based in the U.S. or Canada preferred.  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/vaan-project-manager-for-design-technology-agency-ecommerce"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/vaan-project-manager-for-design-technology-agency-ecommerce&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 22:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 22:02:40 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/vaan-project-manager-for-design-technology-agency-ecommerce</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/vaan-project-manager-for-design-technology-agency-ecommerce</link>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
