<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss">
  <channel>
    <title>We Work Remotely: Product Jobs</title>
    <link>https://weworkremotely.com/categories/remote-product-jobs.rss</link>
    <description>We Work Remotely: Product Jobs</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0001/5597/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Aha!: Product Success Manager (Product management experience required)</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0001/5597/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; United States
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.aha.io"&gt;http://www.aha.io&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Aha! is a very different type of high-growth SaaS company. We are self-funded, highly profitable, and 100 percent remote. We provide the world's #1 product development software so teams can build products that customers love. More than 600,000 product builders use our suite of tools which includes &lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/roadmaps/overview"&gt;Aha! Roadmaps,&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/ideas/overview"&gt;Aha! Ideas&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/create/overview"&gt;Aha! Create&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/develop/overview"&gt;Aha! Develop&lt;/a&gt;. And they rely on our training programs via &lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/academy"&gt;Aha! Academy&lt;/a&gt; to become product development experts. We are recognized as one of the best fully remote companies to work for, champion the &lt;a href="http://www.bootstrap.company/"&gt;Bootstrap Movement&lt;/a&gt;, and have given over $1M to people in need through &lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/company/cares"&gt;Aha! Cares&lt;/a&gt;. Learn more at &lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/"&gt;www.aha.io&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our team&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Our Customer Success team is an all-remote group spread across multiple time zones so we can work closely with customers when they need us.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;We serve: &lt;/strong&gt;We work with the world's best known and most innovative companies and they trust us to guide them to build products that their customers love.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;We are experts:&lt;/strong&gt; Our Customer Success team is comprised of product development experts who have experience delivering meaningful value to customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;We act with urgency:&lt;/strong&gt; We respond to customers' requests as quickly as we can. Because when we do, we have the best chance of creating the most value for customers and ourselves.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;We exchange value&lt;/strong&gt;: We do not have any salespeople and we focus on what is best for the customer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;We collaborate&lt;/strong&gt;: We have no tolerance for drama. We celebrate clear communication, effort, and teamwork. We use Slack for internal team communication and Zoom for team and customer video calls. (Email? Rarely.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;We guide product:&lt;/strong&gt; We bring our customers' requirements to our product team and define our own efficient processes and systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;We enjoy: &lt;/strong&gt;We like what we do and we want you to love your job too. Learn more about&lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/company/the-responsive-method"&gt; The Responsive Method&lt;/a&gt;, our company &lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/company/culture"&gt;values&lt;/a&gt;, and the generous&lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/company/careers/benefits"&gt; benefits&lt;/a&gt; we offer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our customers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We serve the world's most innovative companies. They are building revolutionary new experiences for their customers and move fast. They expect us to do the same and to help them develop best practices for product development. Our software is methodology agnostic, which means we need to be experts in the agile, scrum, kanban, SAFe®, and hybrid approaches that our customers depend on.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Our collective experience gives us the skills to meet customers where they are, internalize how they work (because we have been there, done that), and confidently guide them to achieve their best. And because we are always curious, we love learning from our customers along our journey together.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your experience&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;You work hard and have a history of making a positive customer impact. You thrive in a fast-paced and high-growth technology company. You are happiest when you are working directly with customers together with a team of high achievers like yourself. You definitely have worked as a product or technical project manager, but realized that you prefer helping people to writing requirements. Showcasing advanced technology to sophisticated customers energizes you. You also have:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years experience defining, managing, or launching new functionality at a growing software or technology company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Used a detailed go-to-market process to achieve product and business goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learned complex software applications and workflow methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Written clear instructions to answer questions and explain best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Independently resolved hard challenges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your work at Aha!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;This role is for product managers who prefer to work with customers more than working with developers. The Product Success team provides consultative support for the world's best known and most innovative companies. If you want to answer support requests, conduct demos, and share best practices this role is for you. Your responsibilities will include:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Guiding the world's largest and most sophisticated organizations as they improve how they innovate and build software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Delivering responsive customer service using our proven frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Guiding customers from initial demo to active subscription, through procurement, legal, and security processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning and sharing best practices for setting strategy, capturing ideas, prioritizing work, and creating visual roadmaps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping customers integrate Aha! software with their existing tools (e.g. development systems)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sharing customer feedback internally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Testing new product functionality as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Setting an example for newer team members who are learning to lead demos, share best practices, and help customers with integrations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;If this sounds appealing, we would love to hear from you. (A real human reviews every application.)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grow with us&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Everyone deserves to reach their fullest potential. We know that when we do work that matters with people we care about in a high-growth environment, we feel engaged and alive. And our goal is to help you do just that. We offer all the benefits you would expect and more, including profit sharing. The specific benefits listed below are reflective of what we offer U.S.-based hires. We also do our best to extend identical benefits to international teammates.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generous salary with annual profit sharing for all&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, dental, and vision plans — for many teammates, we cover 100 percent of the premiums&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up to 200 hours of paid time off a year to spend however you want&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;30 to 90 days of paid parental leave and five to 10 days of paid care and bereavement leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up to $1,000 annually for third-party education, along with paid time off to immerse yourself in learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aha! contributes a percentage of your total compensation each year towards your retirement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are building a &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/company/team"&gt;&lt;em&gt;distributed team&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, and you can work from anywhere in North America, the United Kingdom, Ireland, or Australia for this role. We offer generous salary, equity, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/company/careers/benefits"&gt;&lt;em&gt;benefits&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, and a profit-sharing program. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/company/careers/current-openings"&gt;&lt;em&gt;See other openings at Aha!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diversity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We are committed to hiring, promoting, and compensating employees based on their qualifications and demonstrated ability to perform job responsibilities. As an equal opportunity employer, Aha! welcomes all employees and applicants, without regard to age, race, color, national origin, physical or mental disability, gender, religion, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital or veteran status, condition of pregnancy, or any other legally protected characteristic. &lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/company/diversity"&gt;Learn more&lt;/a&gt; about diversity and inclusion at Aha!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aha-product-success-manager-product-management-experience-required"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aha-product-success-manager-product-management-experience-required&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 13:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 13:27:04 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aha-product-success-manager-product-management-experience-required</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aha-product-success-manager-product-management-experience-required</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/9239/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Overleaf: Senior Analyst</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/9239/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; London
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://overleaf.com"&gt;https://overleaf.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;The Role&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;As we grow, we’re collecting more and more data about how people use our service. We’re running split tests and monitoring how the changes we make impact user behaviour and our revenue. We are looking for a Senior Analyst with commercial/business experience to help us get the most out of our data, to inform decision making and guide our strategic thinking.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Day to day, you will:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Investigate and report on the commercial impact of activities such as:&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Seasonal promotions and other marketing campaigns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Split tests which impact purchases or user retention&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New feature releases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead investigations to support the wider business:&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finding opportunities for growth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Influencing user flows in the product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translating business questions into precise SQL queries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clearly communicate and visualise findings from our commercial data:&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trend analysis of business KPIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Forecasting and reviewing actual performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sharing insights, knowledge and best practice with the wider business&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Benefits&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote and flexible working.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Salary £40k–£60k per year depending on experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You would join a small, dedicated and growing team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We're substantially (around 80%) open source, so your work will often be on open source.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We're backed by Bethnal Green Ventures (https://bethnalgreenventures.com/) and Digital Science (https://www.digital-science.com/), through which we're part of a wider community of startups in science, health and ed-tech.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our London office is shared with several other Digital Science companies, so there's lots of interesting people to meet, and clubs and sports activities outside of work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We'll supply a Mac, Linux or Windows laptop (your choice) plus a stipend to set up your workspace.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We provide a training budget; many of our staff choose to attend relevant industry conferences or buy training materials.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;We require that you:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a minimum of 3–5 years of relevant experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Will work for us full time (or nearly full time).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Will usually be available in our core hours, 2pm–5pm UK time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are based in the UK, EU, US or Canada.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;How We Hire&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We ask you to submit a CV and a cover letter stating why you would like to work for Overleaf.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We will aim to update you on the status of your application within two weeks from when we receive it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We'll follow up by email (or sometimes schedule a phone call) with any questions we have about your application, usually around logistics, your ambitions and your expectations about the role.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We'll schedule a more in-depth interview, which is typically followed or combined with a practical assignment. For the practical, you'll have the option of either completing a homework assignment, which requires about one hour of your time before the interview, or doing an exercise during the interview, if you prefer. The exercises are practical in nature, and you can use Google, etc., and ask us questions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We may ask you to attend a second, shorter, interview.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We'll make an offer. We usually interview in batches, so there may be a short delay while we interview other candidates, but we will try to keep you informed throughout the process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Please tell us in your application about your experience with these key skills:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SQL — we expect that you’ll spend a lot of your time working with SQL (in particular, BigQuery SQL) in this role.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicating your findings — visualising and sharing analyses with teams across the business is an important part of the role.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with financial data — we're not looking for an accountant, but most of our analyses have a financial component, so it will be helpful to have a grasp of financial concepts such as revenue recognition, present values and compounding.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;Other experience that it would be helpful to highlight (but is not required) includes:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with at least one other programming language for statistical analysis, such as R or Python, because we also use these for some ad hoc analyses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BigQuery for queries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MixPanel or similar product analytics tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A/B testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working in a B2B and/or B2C SaaS context&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of the scholarly market and/or some knowledge of LaTeX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;How We Work&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;Overleaf is remote-first (and was before the pandemic too) — all founders and staff work remotely and this is &lt;a href="https://www.overleaf.com/about/values"&gt;part of our values&lt;/a&gt;. We also have an office in Farringdon for those in the London area, and we aim to get the whole team together twice a year for valuable face-to-face time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We encourage flexible working. Our core hours are 2pm–5pm UK time, during which our development and product teams have 10–15 minute daily standup calls.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We collect data and user feedback to inform our work. We have UX professionals on our team, and we run surveys and user interviews on a weekly basis. We use these, alongside quantitative data to inform our Product Discovery process. Our roadmap also includes initiatives driven by staff and quarterly hackathons to keep our learning fresh.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/overleaf-senior-analyst"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/overleaf-senior-analyst&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 17:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 17:17:38 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/overleaf-senior-analyst</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/overleaf-senior-analyst</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aha!: Sr. Product Success Manager (Product management experience required)</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; United States
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.aha.io"&gt;http://www.aha.io&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Aha! is a very different type of high-growth SaaS company. We are self-funded, highly profitable, and 100 percent remote. We provide the world's #1 product development software so teams can build products that customers love. More than 600,000 product builders use our suite of tools which includes &lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/roadmaps/overview"&gt;Aha! Roadmaps,&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/ideas/overview"&gt;Aha! Ideas&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/create/overview"&gt;Aha! Create&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/develop/overview"&gt;Aha! Develop&lt;/a&gt;. And they rely on our training programs via &lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/academy"&gt;Aha! Academy&lt;/a&gt; to become product development experts. We are recognized as one of the best fully remote companies to work for, champion the &lt;a href="http://www.bootstrap.company/"&gt;Bootstrap Movement&lt;/a&gt;, and have given over $1M to people in need through &lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/company/cares"&gt;Aha! Cares&lt;/a&gt;. Learn more at &lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/"&gt;www.aha.io&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our team&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Our Customer Success team is an all-remote group spread across multiple time zones so we can work closely with customers when they need us.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;We serve: &lt;/strong&gt;We work with the world's best known and most innovative companies and they trust us to guide them to build products that their customers love.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;We are experts:&lt;/strong&gt; Our Customer Success team is comprised of product development experts who have experience delivering meaningful value to customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;We act with urgency:&lt;/strong&gt; We respond to customers' requests as quickly as we can. Because when we do, we have the best chance of creating the most value for customers and ourselves.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;We exchange value&lt;/strong&gt;: We do not have any salespeople and we focus on what is best for the customer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;We collaborate&lt;/strong&gt;: We have no tolerance for drama. We celebrate clear communication, effort, and teamwork. We use Slack for internal team communication and Zoom for team and customer video calls. (Email? Rarely.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;We guide product:&lt;/strong&gt; We bring our customers' requirements to our product team and define our own efficient processes and systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;We enjoy: &lt;/strong&gt;We like what we do and we want you to love your job too. Learn more about&lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/company/the-responsive-method"&gt; The Responsive Method&lt;/a&gt;, our company &lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/company/culture"&gt;values&lt;/a&gt;, and the generous&lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/company/careers/benefits"&gt; benefits&lt;/a&gt; we offer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our customers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We serve the world's most innovative companies. They are building revolutionary new experiences for their customers and move fast. They expect us to do the same and to help them develop best practices for product development. Our software is methodology agnostic, which means we need to be experts in the agile, scrum, kanban, SAFe®, and hybrid approaches that our customers depend on.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Our collective experience gives us the skills to meet customers where they are, internalize how they work (because we've been there, done that), and confidently guide them to achieve their best. And because we are always curious, we love learning from our customers along our journey together.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your experience&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;You work hard and have a history of making a positive customer impact. You thrive in a fast-paced and high-growth technology company. You are happiest when you are working directly with customers together with a team of high achievers like yourself. You definitely have worked as a product or technical project manager, but realized that you prefer helping people to writing requirements. Showcasing advanced technology to sophisticated customers energizes you. You also have:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6+ years experience defining, managing, or launching new functionality at a growing software or technology company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Influenced or defined the detailed go-to-market process used to achieve product and business goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learned complex software applications and workflow methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Written clear instructions to answer questions and explain best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Independently resolved hard challenges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your work at Aha!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;This role is for product managers who prefer to work with customers more than working with developers. The Product Success team provides consultative support for the world's best known and most innovative companies. If you want to answer support requests, conduct demos, and share best practices this role is for you. Your responsibilities will include:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Guiding the world's largest and most sophisticated organizations as they improve how they innovate and build software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Delivering responsive customer service using our proven frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Guiding customers from initial demo to active subscription, through procurement, legal, and security processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning and sharing best practices for setting strategy, capturing ideas, prioritizing work, and creating visual roadmaps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping customers integrate Aha! software with their existing tools (e.g. development systems)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sharing customer feedback internally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Testing new product functionality as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentoring newer team members as they lead demos, share best practices, and help customers with integrations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;If this sounds appealing, we would love to hear from you. (A real human reviews every application.)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grow with us&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Everyone deserves to reach their fullest potential. We know that when we do work that matters with people we care about in a high-growth environment, we feel engaged and alive. And our goal is to help you do just that. We offer all the benefits you would expect and more, including profit sharing. The specific benefits listed below are reflective of what we offer U.S.-based hires. We also do our best to extend identical benefits to international teammates.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generous salary with annual profit sharing for all&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical, dental, and vision plans — for many teammates, we cover 100 percent of the premiums&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up to 200 hours of paid time off a year to spend however you want&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;30 to 90 days of paid parental leave and five to 10 days of paid care and bereavement leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up to $1,000 annually for third-party education, along with paid time off to immerse yourself in learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aha! contributes a percentage of your total compensation each year towards your retirement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are building a &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/company/team"&gt;&lt;em&gt;distributed team&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, and you can work from anywhere in North America, the United Kingdom, Ireland, or Australia for this role. We offer generous salary, equity, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/company/careers/benefits"&gt;&lt;em&gt;benefits&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, and a profit-sharing program. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/company/careers/current-openings"&gt;&lt;em&gt;See other openings at Aha!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diversity&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We are committed to hiring, promoting, and compensating employees based on their qualifications and demonstrated ability to perform job responsibilities. As an equal opportunity employer, Aha! welcomes all employees and applicants, without regard to age, race, color, national origin, physical or mental disability, gender, religion, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital or veteran status, condition of pregnancy, or any other legally protected characteristic. &lt;a href="https://www.aha.io/company/diversity"&gt;Learn more&lt;/a&gt; about diversity and inclusion at Aha!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aha-sr-product-success-manager-product-management-experience-required"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aha-sr-product-success-manager-product-management-experience-required&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 13:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 13:31:55 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aha-sr-product-success-manager-product-management-experience-required</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/aha-sr-product-success-manager-product-management-experience-required</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0001/6377/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>SystemOne, LLC: Product Manager</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0001/6377/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Northampton, Massachusetts, USA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://systemone.id/"&gt;https://systemone.id/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Product Manager&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;SystemOne is looking for a product manager who will be responsible for the overall success of our product line. You will be responsible for managing the product's lifecycle from development to product launch and bringing our company's vision and strategy to life. This position reports directly to the Chief Executive Officer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required Qualifications &lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     A bachelor’s degree in business, computer science, or a related field;  MBA preferred&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     A minimum of 5 years experience in product management or a related field&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     Exceptional analytical and conceptual thinking skills&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     Ability to influence stakeholders and work closely with them to determine acceptable solutions&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     High level of comfort with technology and its development&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     Excellent planning, organizational, problem-solving, time management, and communication skills&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     Excellent documentation skills along with in-depth knowledge of product strategy &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     Experience creating detailed reports and presentations to senior executives and key stakeholders&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     A track record of successfully making and keeping commitments&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     Be sensitive to cultural nuances and diversity in interacting and dealing with colleagues and customers             spanning multiple countries across Africa, Asia, Europe and the Americas.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     Be flexible to operate remotely and across different time zones.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     Experience in the healthcare field or SaaS products would be preferred. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Product Manager Responsibilities   &lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;●     Obtain and understand customer feedback, and translate marketback into product requirements&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     Research and suggest new product development and refinements for existing products&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     Lead the development team in creating the product road map&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     Contribute to product pricing strategies&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     Contribute to the marketing and PR strategies for company products and services&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     Support the sales team by providing product information and demos&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     Research and suggest new product development and refinements for existing products&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     Making tradeoffs between features, schedule, and costs based on their relationship to business goals,                 company policies, software architecture constraints, and software development team capacity&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     Remain abreast of the latest industry trends and technology&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt;About the Organization:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;SystemOne is a global IoT company that has built software and secure communication networks that power infectious disease monitoring and treatment programs in over 45 countries.  Our solutions specialize in moving Point of Care diagnostic data and instrument performance data in real time.  Health systems use our products to reduce the duration between diagnosis and patient treatment, to track critical inventory in remote clinics, and maintain the operational integrity of their diagnostic fleets. Our Management and Engineering teams are currently distributed across Europe, Africa, Asia &amp;amp; the Americas engaging across multiple cultures and time zones.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Candidates must embrace SystemOne's Core values:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;●     Do good and create lasting value;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     Make the journey matter;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     Be worthy of respect;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;●     Be pragmatic and keep it simple.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/systemone-llc-product-manager"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/systemone-llc-product-manager&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 14:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 14:43:39 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/systemone-llc-product-manager</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/systemone-llc-product-manager</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SugarCRM: Release Manager</title>
      <region>Europe Only</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Cupertino
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://sugarcrm.com"&gt;https://sugarcrm.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;SugarCRM &lt;/strong&gt;is looking for a Release Manager to help us ship next generation of CRM solutions. This role is responsible for delivery of cloud-based product releases. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You will ensure success of our program in running current day-to-day release activities for cloud products.  You will be part of the team responsible for planning, building, maintaining and operating release delivery that supports all product releases.  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;**Only candidates local to, and authorized to work in &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Romania&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; are being considered at this time**&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive discussions to define and communicate release milestones, scope, scale and cross team dependencies. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with team to manage scope, risks and dependencies, and quality of the releases.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform issue tracking and facilitate resolution.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create required release artifacts in Confluence for each release.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and coordinate release deployment and provide status. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage release versions, stories, and bug tracking in JIRA &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Act as a gatekeeper for delivery into production by adherence to milestone, monitoring and tracking progress of scope and changes targeted for each release. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with engineering and QA team to support setting up test environment &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with Support and Operation teams to ensure operational readiness &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of software release management experience  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communications and presentation skills. Able to communicate technical issues effectively to the team &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Agile Scrum methodology &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands on experience in tools like JIRA and Confluence &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PMI or equivalent certification is strongly desired (but not mandatory) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;We understand that no candidate is perfectly qualified for any job. Experience comes in different forms; many skills are transferable; and passion goes a long way. Even more important than your resume is a clear demonstration of dedication, impact, and the ability to thrive in a fluid and collaborative environment. We want you to learn new things in this role, and we encourage you to apply if your experience is close to what we’re looking for. We also know that diversity of background and thought makes for better problem solving and more creative thinking, which is why we're dedicated to adding new perspectives to the team.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits and Perks:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Beyond a stellar work environment, friendly people, and inspiring work, we have some sweet benefits and perks:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Private medical and vision benefit coverage&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Health &amp;amp;Wellness Reimbursement Program&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Educational Resources - Career &amp;amp; Personal Development Program&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Attractive salary package&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Flexible work hours&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Meal tickets&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;-Football Team&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;-We are a merit-based company with many opportunities to learn, excel and grow your career!&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/sugarcrm-release-manager"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/sugarcrm-release-manager&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 20:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 20:54:26 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/sugarcrm-release-manager</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/sugarcrm-release-manager</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/9021/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Overleaf: Product Manager (Technical)</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/9021/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; London, England, United Kingdom
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.overleaf.com"&gt;https://www.overleaf.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We Do&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overleaf builds modern collaborative authoring tools for scientists — like Google Docs for Science. We make an online, real-time collaborative editor for papers, theses and other documents written in the LaTeX markup language.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have over ten million registered users from around the world and over 400,000 people use our platform each day. Our company is scaling up and we are looking for a Product Manager (Technical) who can take the lead on one of our core product areas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We were recently recognised as one of the&lt;a href="https://www.overleaf.com/blog/overleaf-recognized-as-one-of-the-uks-top-100-fastest-growing-businesses" class="external"&gt; UK's top 100 fastest growing businesses&lt;/a&gt; and as the&lt;a href="https://www.overleaf.com/blog/overleaf-named-2020-saas-awards-winner" class="external"&gt; Best SaaS for Nonprofits or Education&lt;/a&gt; in the 2020 SaaS Awards Program. We're part of the&lt;a href="https://www.digital-science.com/" class="external"&gt; Digital Science&lt;/a&gt; family of science, health and ed-tech companies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Product Team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are an interdisciplinary team made of product managers, UX designers and data analysts. We are a relatively new team, with most people joining in 2021, and small enough that everyone has a few hats to wear, but large enough that we have experts who can guide the rest of the team in their area, such as User Research, User Experience or Analytics. Some of us come from a teaching background, marketing, engineering, QA and more disciplines, which gives the team its unique flavour. Our mission is to explore the future of Overleaf through data, design and research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your New Role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we expand, we are growing the product team to let us have owners for each of our core areas, namely Editor, B2C growth, Institutions and Enterprise. For this reason, we are now looking to hire an experienced Product Manager who can lead our discovery and development initiatives across one of these areas. You will take ownership of researching, understanding and delivering value to our users, enhancing their workflows for both our hosted SaaS and on-premises solutions. As part of a Product Trio (Product, UX, Engineering - plus others), you will map opportunities using product discovery methods and shape your own roadmap and KPIs. You will lead on projects related to your area of expertise from start to finish. This will usually involve: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Understanding user needs:&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Carry out primary research to understand users and their pain points, identifying opportunities to address them.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Nurture and grow our rich database of user insights, mining data as needed and present it to stakeholders in various contexts.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Based on research insights, formulate hypotheses to be tested with a variety of qualitative and quantitative methods.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Shaping and developing solutions:&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Shape a vision, define the problem and align the team with clear goals, objectives and user stories.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Map and test assumptions with a variety of qualitative and quantitative methods.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Distil existing user research data to support the team in making the right decisions.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Work closely with UX designers, data analysts and engineers throughout the release process, from shaping to building, testing and releasing.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Clearly define measures of success for A/B testing, balancing the need for accuracy with shipping value to users quickly.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Recognise and celebrate success regularly when things go well, while fostering a growth mindset when things don't go so well.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Lead and facilitate planning sessions with your team to prioritise work, often applying decision-making frameworks (e.g. RICE).&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Keep other stakeholders informed as progress is made, through regular demos, Show &amp;amp; Tells and presentations.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Understanding the Business. You will specifically own the relationship with a core department (e.g. Sales and Account Management teams for the Institutional/Enterprise core area, or Marketing for our B2C Growth area):&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Develop and manage a solid product roadmap for your core area.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Map opportunities and manage input from your stakeholders to enhance our offering on an ongoing basis.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Clearly communicate our roadmap and product changes in advance of their launch and help them manage communications to customers.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Take part in customer onboarding sessions, webinars and/or sales negotiations and use these opportunities to conduct user research.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Work closely with other departments to:&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Help them access and understand product information (e.g. releases for our On-Premises product, key features, product roadmap). &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Explain technical dependencies and how they may affect our roadmap.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Help them access product data/metrics that can provide useful insights for their departments.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Bring the user perspective in meetings and engage stakeholders with our continuous user research efforts and insights.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Strategy and planning: &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;You will input and contribute to the main product roadmap and take part in planning meetings on an ongoing basis. &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;You will develop a set of strategic goals and KPIs for your core area on an annual basis, updating stakeholders on progress throughout the year.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year, we are excited about:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Having launched our most popular feature yet, a way to &lt;a href="https://www.overleaf.com/blog/new-feature-ready-set-detach" class="external"&gt;detach the PDF view&lt;/a&gt; in another window, which allows users to work on multiple monitors.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Relaunching our core editor in CodeMirror 6 for improved functionality and accessibility.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Enhancing the collaboration experience on our product to make it even more compelling for individual users and Enterprise teams. We are currently testing assumptions around shared spaces.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Collaborating with more partners to enhance the editing experience through new technologies.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also got excited when our UX team won a prestigious award for delivering a seamless integration between Overleaf and ShareLaTeX:  &lt;a href="https://www.overleaf.com/blog/congratulations-to-paulo-john-and-sven-best-case-study-at-acm-chi2021" class="external"&gt;https://www.overleaf.com/blog/congratulations-to-p...&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How We Work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overleaf is remote-first — all staff work remotely and this is&lt;a href="https://www.overleaf.com/about/values" class="external"&gt; part of our values&lt;/a&gt;. We also have an office space in London for those that want to use it, and when the pandemic settles down we'll again get the whole team together in London a few times a year for face-to-face time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our core hours for meetings are 2pm-5pm UK time; we try to schedule all team meetings during this time, including daily 10-15 minute standup calls and biweekly company update calls.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We always collect user feedback to inform our work. We have UX professionals on our team, and we run surveys and user interviews on a weekly basis to inform our Product Discovery process. You can read more about how we introduced these methods in this &lt;a href="https://www.overleaf.com/blog/how-we-introduced-product-discovery-methods-at-overleaf-in-3-steps" class="external"&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have a flexible roadmap that we review quarterly, which includes regular user-facing releases. Our Product team works closely with everyone in the company, often as part of a Product Trio (Product, UX, Engineering, with other departments as needed) to understand every aspect of how we can best deliver value to our users. Our roadmap also includes initiatives driven by staff and quarterly hackathons to keep our learning fresh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How We Hire&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;The stages in our hiring process are typically:&lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;We ask you to submit a CV and a cover letter stating why you would like to work for Overleaf.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;We will aim to update you on the status of your application within two weeks from when we receive it.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;We'll follow up by email (or sometimes schedule a phone call) with any questions we have about your application, usually around logistics, your ambitions and your expectations about the role.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;We'll schedule a more in-depth interview, which is typically followed or combined with a practical assignment. For the practical, you'll have the option of either completing a homework assignment, which requires about one hour of your time before the interview, or doing an exercise during the interview, if you prefer. The exercises are practical in nature, and you can use Google, etc., and ask us questions.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;We may ask you to attend a second, shorter, interview with our Founders.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;We'll make an offer. We usually interview in batches, so there may be a short delay while we interview other candidates, but we will try to keep you informed throughout the process.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a deadline, please let us know in your application, and we will try to be accommodating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who You Are&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Experienced in Product Management as a discipline. You can switch from managing demanding stakeholders to resolving technical trade-offs with the Engineering team, always bringing the focus back on our long-term vision and delivering user value.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Technical. You are familiar with LaTeX or willing to learn about LaTeX and its use within academia and industry. You also understand the difference between a SaaS product and its on-premises counterpart, including their underpinning technologies, e.g. Docker.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Commercially minded. You have commercial experience within a B2C SaaS product and/or Enterprise. For example, you are able to read user research insights through a commercial lens, with a view to grow the business while shipping value to users.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Empathetic. You are curious about people and their stories. You are able to understand user and stakeholder needs, while still being able to push back or negotiate as necessary.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Data-driven. You enjoy finding ways to measure success and dig into data to make decisions. Whether it's from a survey, a database or a user interview, you are comfortable drawing insights and presenting them to your stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;Self-motivated. You are a natural at making plans, keeping people aligned along the way and thrive when you see a vision come to life.&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We require that you:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Have a minimum of 3-4 years of relevant experience.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Will work for us full time.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Will usually be available in our core hours, 2pm-5pm UK time.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Are based in the UK, EU, US or Canada.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Remote and flexible working.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Salary £50k-£75k per year depending on experience.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;You would join a small, dedicated and growing team.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;We're substantially (around 80%) open-source, so your work will often be on open source code.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;We organise company and team meetups several times a year for valuable face-to-face time.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;We'll provide a new Mac, PC or Linux laptop, along with a stipend for other equipment.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;We provide a training budget and allocate time for training; many of our developers choose to attend relevant industry conferences or buy training materials.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;We run regular&lt;a href="https://www.overleaf.com/blog/overleafs-remote-hackathon-revisited-one-year" class="external"&gt; remote hackathons&lt;/a&gt; to keep learning and experimenting.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;We run a weekly internal seminar series with short talks from staff about their work or personal projects, new technologies and techniques.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Additional benefits package varies by country. Please ask us.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're an equal opportunity employer. All applicants will be considered for employment without attention to race, colour, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, veteran or disability status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/overleaf-product-manager-technical-1"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/overleaf-product-manager-technical-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 12:35:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 12:35:08 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/listings/overleaf-product-manager-technical-1</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/listings/overleaf-product-manager-technical-1</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/8982/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Remote IT World: Product Manager AI SaaS </title>
      <region>Europe Only</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/8982/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Bulgaria
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://remoteit.world"&gt;https://remoteit.world&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Product Manager AI SaaS&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Product Manager is a full time, permanent, remote job anywhere in Europe. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remote IT World helps Tech and Blockchain Professionals to get hired for 100% remote jobs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We are a first-choice staffing partner of high-growth startups and scale-ups worldwide.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ready to embrace freedom and flexibility?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read on.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We’re hiring the first&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Product Manager AI SaaS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;to join Swiss AI SaaS innovators. The company was founded by leading AI researchers from ETH Zurich with the mission to empower organizations to &lt;strong&gt;build and deploy trustworthy AI&lt;/strong&gt;. They are building the &lt;strong&gt;world’s first AI SaaS platform&lt;/strong&gt; that enables companies to deliver robust AI models.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;After successful validation of the platform across key industries, we are now &lt;strong&gt;hiring&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;the First Product Manager AI SaaS &lt;/strong&gt;to help us ensure our clients have an amazing experience using our product. In this challenging and critical role, you will be responsible for &lt;strong&gt;driving our product roadmap&lt;/strong&gt;. To do this effectively, you will &lt;strong&gt;work closely with our customers&lt;/strong&gt;, to understand their pain points, current workflow, and how they are using our product, as well as &lt;strong&gt;with our product team &lt;/strong&gt;to &lt;strong&gt;execute the roadmap that will take our product to the next level.&lt;/strong&gt; We are a small but dedicated team and expect everyone to be self-driven, comfortable working in our dynamic and fast-paced environment and embrace the challenges we face.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Scope&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;As Product Manager you will have the opportunity to:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with an experienced C-level and executive team: we have previously built two successful deeptech ETH spin-offs acquired by PwC and the cybersecurity unicorn Snyk;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a massive impact on a product used by the best AI teams in the world and impact how AI teams work in the future.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Play a key role in solving the critical pain points in delivering robust AI models to production to accelerate the widespread adoption of AI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiment with your own ideas and implement them in the product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Main Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Help us translate our vision into deliverable product&lt;/strong&gt; – drive product vision and strategy,  prioritize features based on market feedback and customers’ needs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Communicate&lt;/strong&gt; the product roadmap internally to diverse teams – product, sales, marketing – to ensure everyone is aligned and understands the current/future product state;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Understand workflows used by ML teams&lt;/strong&gt; – from data preparation and labeling to model building, testing, deployment, and serving across diverse customer deployments – who are all the stakeholders, how do they interact, what tools they use, what are the pain points and bottlenecks, and what do different stakeholders care about. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of product management experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with B2B SaaS products and market&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with and leading engineering and design teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills, providing the ability to translate complex technical discussions to diverse stakeholders (clients, engineers, management)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated with the ability to work in a dynamic, fast-changing environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge or experience in AI is a huge plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Company Offer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully remote job with flexible working hours &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunity for professional development &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generous annual salary + equity package&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A market-invested pension plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;25 days of paid vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discounts at sports facilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accident insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regular company retreats &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interview Process&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Introductory call &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conversation about product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conversation about strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Final Round &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Offer &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apply Now by sending your CV to hr@remoteit.world or by using the link &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;For Product Manager AI SaaS, only shortlisted candidates will be contacted. Your job search is strictly confidential.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/remote-it-world-product-manager-ai-saas"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/remote-it-world-product-manager-ai-saas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 10:49:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 10:49:09 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/remote-it-world-product-manager-ai-saas</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/remote-it-world-product-manager-ai-saas</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/8801/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>GRAX, INC: Product Manager</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/8801/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Boston, MA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.grax.com"&gt;https://www.grax.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Product Manager at GRAX Inc.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.golangprojects.com/golang-remote-jobs.html"&gt;Remote&lt;/a&gt; › 🇺🇸 100% remote position (in the US) &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;$120,000 – $200,000 USD&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The GRAX product is a CRM backup, archive and restore system for the Salesforce platform. It is used by Fortune 500, government, financial and health care companies so security and trust is the name of the game. The product is designed to run anywhere from Amazon, Azure to on-prem.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The GRAX product team works closely with customers to understand their Salesforce and CRM data processing needs, then works closely with the GRAX engineering team that builds the web application and data processing systems that takes the data from Salesforce and routes it to cloud storage systems. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The product and engineering organization is led by veterans in cloud platform development, including some of the key architects behind Heroku. We value collaboration, communication and accountability.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You will:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Own the long-term product vision, roadmap, and business metrics for key product areas including Backup, Archive, and Restore&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Discover opportunities and solutions by gathering feedback from customers and prospects, and writing technical project plans&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Work with the product and engineering team to improve the existing product and define and prioritize new features&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Oversee product delivery from design, to iterative development, to internal testing, to validation in customer environments&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Engage with our largest customers, other product managers, and  cross-functional teams to design, deliver, and support solutions that make our customers successful&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You have experience with some of the following:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Talking with customers to discover product gaps and future needs&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Working with customers to validate, train and support new features&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Designing and overseeing incremental delivery of web applications and APIs&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Salesforce or other CRM platforms and tooling&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Data processing platforms and tooling&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Supporting products that run in customers own Heroku, AWS, Azure environments&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;GRAX benefits include:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Fully Remote&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Flexible PTO&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Healthcare for you and your family&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- 401K match&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;- Awesome teammates&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Inclusion Promise&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;GRAX embraces diversity and equal opportunity. We are committed to building a team that represents a variety of backgrounds, perspectives, and skills. We believe the more inclusive we are, the better our company will be.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instructions how to apply&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Email engjobs@grax.com and include your resume and a note on the best product you helped build, as well as your biggest growth opportunities.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/grax-inc-product-manager"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/grax-inc-product-manager&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:41:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 16:41:07 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/grax-inc-product-manager</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/grax-inc-product-manager</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0017/2036/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Instinct Science:  Release Manager</title>
      <region>North America Only</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0017/2036/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Greater Philadelphia, PA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.instinct.vet/"&gt;https://www.instinct.vet/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Meet Instinct &lt;/strong&gt;👋&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Instinct Science is a growing Philadelphia-based animal health company working on unique technology solutions for state-of-the-art veterinary hospitals across the globe. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;​&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re seeking an experienced &lt;strong&gt;Release Manager&lt;/strong&gt; to be the next member of our growing team. The ideal candidate is efficient, organized, detail-oriented, and motivated by working on challenging yet meaningful work that has the potential to shape the entire profession. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;​&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The Instinct team is fully distributed, so your geographic location doesn’t matter as long as you can overlap with our regular business hours (Mon-Fri 8 am - 5 pm ET). Work hours are flexible. However, this position is an on-call position and should be available for any issues and emergencies that arise outside of normal working hours.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;​&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Position Summary &lt;/strong&gt;😺 &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You will be instrumental in delivering and maintaining high-quality software. Your contributions and leadership will greatly influence the usability and reliability of the product. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Day-to-day work will consist of scheduling, managing, coordinating, and communicating releases across multiple teams and projects. Additionally, you will work closely with engineers to understand code merges and identify potential branching ramifications. You will also manage and mitigate risks and resolve issues regarding release quality and schedule. You will be part of a close-knit team that is working hard every day to create a better product.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;​&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities May Include (but aren't limited to) 💪 &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create, update, and maintain the release process between the development, QA, and support teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead and maintain an internal release checklist for deployment execution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide company-wide weekly release updates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review tickets approved in queue, batch releases, and notify the QA team for regression.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review releases in progress and organize timing of each release—taking dependencies into account.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Schedule, manage, and coordinate releases across multiple teams and projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with engineers to understand code merges and identify potential branching ramifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and mitigate risks and resolve issues regarding release quality and schedule.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organize releases in our software development tool, Jira and tag tickets appropriately to releases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Notify QA team members of the release plan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Notify QA team members of testing deadlines based on release schedule.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review release notes and identify any tickets that are missing from release notes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain release notes documentation page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate release notes with the support team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate and set expectations with the company on deployment timing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate deployment timing with the development team, demo team, and/or sales team, as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Smoke test releases manually and/or using an automated smoke test suite, once release is deployed to production.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor internal logs following production deployments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate and assist with deployments for all hotfixes/fires to production.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuously improve the release lifecycle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be available and on-call for any issues and emergencies that arise outside of normal working hours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;​&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;We’re Looking for Someone With &lt;/strong&gt;⚡&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3+ years of experience managing and deploying releases, preferably with sophisticated software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience writing release notes and communicating deployment timelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Jira or a similar software development tool&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience executing automated test suites with Webdriver IO or a similar automation framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Github or other modern code repositories&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of modern devops practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Google Sheets and Excel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of software development and testing processes and methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working closely with cross-functional teams, including development, QA, and support teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent skills communicating with technical and non-technical teammates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional attention to detail and excellent time-management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Problem-solving and critical thinking skills, with the ability to make sound decisions under pressure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience managing multiple tasks and projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;​&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Bonus Experience &lt;/strong&gt;💡​&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with CircleCI and Papertrail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience writing automated tests using JavaScript or similar language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Elixir&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Notion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zephyr test case management or other testing repositories&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working efficiently as part of a distributed team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Veterinary or healthcare industry experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;​&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;A Sneak Peek at Team Instinct &lt;/strong&gt;🔭&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The Instinct team consists of a unique mix of veterinary and technology experts who offer years of experience developing and commercializing point-of-care software for the veterinary industry. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Instinct fosters a diverse, inclusive, transparent, and fun work environment. As a fully distributed team, we value teammates with strong communication and organizational skills. We’re building a company that reflects our care for every individual, treating each team member well by going out of our way to help one another in the short-term and pushing for growth in the long-term. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;​&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re guided by one thing: helping veterinary hospital teams excel. To that end, your work contributions will greatly shape the workflows, staff happiness, and patient care for some of the most advanced veterinary centers on the planet.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary and Benefits Highlights 🌞&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We offer a supportive, innovative, caring work environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We pay our team well (flexible based on experience).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We give our team owner-like flexibility over work and time off.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We offer health, vision, dental insurance, and 401K.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We offer a generous home office and professional development stipend.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We provide all-expense-paid travel to veterinary hospitals and our retreats.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;​&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn More About Us 👓&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.instinct.vet/"&gt;https://www.instinct.vet&lt;/a&gt; - Corporate website&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="https://pickthebrain.instinct.vet/"&gt;https://pickthebrain.instinct.vet&lt;/a&gt; - Our blog called Pick the Brain that has articles that will help you understand a little more about how we engage and help our customers—besides writing awesome software.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/instinct-science-release-manager"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/instinct-science-release-manager&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 15:35:20 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/instinct-science-release-manager</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/instinct-science-release-manager</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0064/4621/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Punchbowl: Software QA Lead</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0064/4621/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Framingham, MA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.punchbowl.com"&gt;https://www.punchbowl.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Punchbowl is looking for a Software QA Lead to join our growing team. The ideal candidate has 3-5+ years of experience in software quality assurance. As a hands-on QA manager for Punchbowl.com, Memento.com, and our mobile apps, you will take on the role of player/coach. You’ll build a deep knowledge of our platform and products, execute test plans, and ensure all new code is tested with minimal risk of causing site downtime. Ultimately, you’ll build and lead a team who will manage all QA responsibilities. This is a fantastic opportunity for a skilled QA leader who is looking for autonomy in their next role.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You are: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passionate and opinionated about delivering flawless products (web and app)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced with software quality assurance (3-5+ years) and different testing techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An exceptional communicator who knows how to write clear, precise feedback for developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledgeable about how to build processes and evangelize them within an organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Confident in your ability to manage other team members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A problem-solving savant with impeccable attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You will: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with stakeholders to run and perfect the release process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage all processes for testing &amp;amp; communicating feedback to the dev team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead and grow a team of QA specialists&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee the development and maintenance of test plans for all active products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop test cases for planned features and ensure full test coverage of the product spec&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with the customer support team to identify user-facing and user-reported issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish new processes earlier in the development lifecycle to help our QA process “shift left”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evangelize and implement end-to-end regression testing with a framework like Cypress or Playwright to improve our testing automation suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prioritize and escalate live issues appropriately&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Punchbowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Do you want to work in a growing company that invests in its employees more than the average company? Punchbowl is the company behind the critically-acclaimed technology platform for celebrations, holidays, and meaningful life memories. The Company runs its platform on Punchbowl.com, Memento.com, and best-in-class iOS and Android apps. We provide a fun, casual, and innovative environment where hard work is recognized and rewarded.  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Some Punchbowl Perks:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% healthcare coverage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexibility to work from wherever you will be most effective&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A collaborative, start-up environment where you’ll learn a lot, get your hands dirty, and see your work directly impact our customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fantastic, smart coworkers who are passionate about what they do&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Virtual team coffee chats, Friday team trivia challenges, and anything else we can think of to have fun as a team from a distance&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;TO APPLY: &lt;/strong&gt;Please send a resume to jobs@punchbowl.com&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/punchbowl-software-qa-lead"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/punchbowl-software-qa-lead&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 16:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 16:23:22 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/punchbowl-software-qa-lead</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/punchbowl-software-qa-lead</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0018/8581/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Filestage: Product Manager (SaaS)</title>
      <region>Europe Only</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0018/8581/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Stuttgart
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://filestage.io"&gt;https://filestage.io&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Filestage&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Filestage frees people from chaotic approval processes, making work more joyful and productive. From large enterprises to independent agencies, our review and approval platform helps teams share, discuss, and approve all their files, all in one place – including documents, designs, images, videos, and audio files.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We're a fully remote team with people working in home offices, co-working spaces, and coffee shops all over the world. Together, we're on a mission to create a seamless approval process that helps people deliver their best work.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We've raised our Series A and have over half a million users across 500+ companies, including AB InBev, LG, Havas, GroupM, and Emirates. So if you're looking for a fast-growing start-up in a booming market, you've found it!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be working on as our Product Manager&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re looking for a Product Manager to help achieve product leadership in our market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;In your first year at Filestage, you will&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Play a key role in defining the future of our category-leading SaaS product. &lt;/strong&gt;This is an opportunity to shape how we simplify the daily work-life of thousands of people.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Develop compelling product strategies and define roadmap priorities.&lt;/strong&gt; You’ll be transforming user needs and market opportunities into excellent product solutions that drive business results.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Ship outstanding product improvements in your product squads&lt;/strong&gt;, collaborating closely with your design and engineering teammates – as well as our partners and customers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Run product experiments&lt;/strong&gt; in cross-functional growth squads to achieve our business and user goals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Build strong relationships &lt;/strong&gt;with our community of passionate customers, talking to our users and taking a deep dive into their pain points, needs, and use cases.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Life at Filestage&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We believe people are more productive when they can choose their own schedule. So we’re proud to offer fully-remote roles that give you the perfect balance between work and life.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Here are some of the benefits you can look forward to at Filestage:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Work from where you’re happiest and enjoy a flexible schedule. &lt;/strong&gt;We’ve been fully remote from the start, giving you the opportunity to meet people all over the world and broaden your horizons.&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;For this role, we’re looking for someone &lt;strong&gt;based in Europe&lt;/strong&gt; to make sure there’s a high time overlap with our team members, customers, and partners.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Meet up in real life. &lt;/strong&gt;We all travel together at least once a year (in normal times) at our team retreat to have fun and get to know each other.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Enjoy a strong team culture&lt;/strong&gt;. We’re a group of knowledge seekers, reflective thinkers, clear communicators, goal owners, problem solvers, and team players. These are the values we strive for to help us achieve our mission.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Join a happy team.&lt;/strong&gt; We’ve been rated five stars on Glassdoor by our lovely team. &lt;a href="https://www.glassdoor.co.uk/Reviews/Filestage-Reviews-E2536549.htm"&gt;You can take a look at our reviews here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Create a workspace that suits you. &lt;/strong&gt;You’ll get a €1,500 budget for hardware, as well €500 for home office to buy whatever you need to do your best work – including a computer, webcam, or standing desk.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Get 36 days of holiday.&lt;/strong&gt; Plenty of time for city breaks, summer escapes, and everything in between. You’ll also get a half day on your birthday to give you a chance to celebrate!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Continue to grow and develop your career. &lt;/strong&gt;We care about your development and want you to be able to learn new things! After six months in the company, you’ll get a budget to be able to use for personal development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Make your voice heard.&lt;/strong&gt; We trust our team members to make the best decisions to achieve their goals, so you won’t have to put up with micromanagers here.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Say goodbye to pointless meetings.&lt;/strong&gt; We practice what we preach when it comes to productivity, so you can expect flat hierarchies, fast iterations, and no bullshit meetings.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll bring to the role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You have three years of experience working as a product manager in SaaS. Now you’re looking for a new and exciting challenge that has a huge (and positive) impact on the way people work.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Here are some of the things we’d like to see from you:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;You have a holistic understanding of product management for SaaS. &lt;/strong&gt;You know what’s needed to build great digital products and you have more than three years of professional experience in SaaS product management.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;You put a superior user experience at the heart of the product. &lt;/strong&gt;You enjoy collaborating with designers to craft solutions with an outstanding user experience. You understand that the details matter.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;You’re passionate about user onboarding&lt;/strong&gt; and you’ve already proven success in activating users.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;You work well with lots of questions and few answers. &lt;/strong&gt;No problem is too big or too hard. You are most productive when ambitious goals are clearly set and you can choose your own path to reach them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;You have an entrepreneurial mindset and you’re hungry to learn.&lt;/strong&gt; You roll your sleeves up to get things done. You strive to continuously improve, iterate, and integrate what you learn.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;You’re a strong communicator &lt;/strong&gt;and have experience collaborating with a distributed team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/filestage-product-manager-saas-1"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/filestage-product-manager-saas-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 17:32:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 17:32:49 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/filestage-product-manager-saas-1</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/filestage-product-manager-saas-1</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0071/3543/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>ArborXR: Product Manager for AR/VR Company</title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0071/3543/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Fully Remote
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://arborxr.com"&gt;https://arborxr.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Hello,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;How are you?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;I’m sure you’ve read hundreds of these job descriptions by now.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;I hope reading this one will be less painful.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;In short: We are growing our product team and looking to add our 3rd&lt;strong&gt; Product Manager&lt;/strong&gt; to our team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;What might that look like?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You'll lead a cross functional Product team developing software and working closely with our customers. You'll collaborate with our leadership and other product leads on your vision for the product. Perform user surveys and interviews, digging deep into how our customers use our software.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Does that sound interesting? Would you enjoy that role?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If so, please apply. We’d love to talk.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;A bit about us?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re a team of ~50&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are fully remote.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We don’t micro manage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We don’t do the startup grind thing (and we don’t work weekends).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You'd be working with a product team (not solo).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re building some cool stuff. Our product is growing like crazy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Want to read a bit about our team culture and story? See this: &lt;a href="https://arborxr.com/about-us/"&gt;https://arborxr.com/about-us/&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If that all sounds interesting and you'd like to apply.... please include in your cover letter your favorite flavor of ice cream. (Spam filter!)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Cover letters are very important to us -- we read them all thoroughly! We want to hear about you and what gets you excited.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of Product Management in SaaS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Product led Product Management experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience coordinating the development of and adherence to product roadmaps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Combination of short term execution and long term product vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to Have&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with a fully remote team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working at a high growth startup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical experience in software development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with AOSP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with OEMs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full-time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote, but based in the U.S. or Canada&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visa sponsorship is not available&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Salary between $104,000 USD and $124,800 USD&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equity Stock Option Plan - 1 year cliff / 4 year vest&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full Healthcare benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited time off&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Annual team retreats&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Want to read a bit about our team culture and story? See this: &lt;a href="https://arborxr.com/about-us/"&gt;https://arborxr.com/about-us/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/arborxr-product-manager-for-ar-vr-company"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/arborxr-product-manager-for-ar-vr-company&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 21:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 21:50:11 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/arborxr-product-manager-for-ar-vr-company</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/arborxr-product-manager-for-ar-vr-company</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TestGorilla: International Expansion Manager</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Amsterdam
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/"&gt;https://www.testgorilla.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Hi,&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;I’m Claudia, the Head of Product at TestGorilla. We’re a fast-growing HR tech startup that helps teams make better hiring decisions, faster and bias-free.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Over the past year, we’ve experienced tremendous growth. More than 7,500 companies have replaced CVs with our assessments to screen candidates in an unbiased and data-driven way.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As we scale our efforts in 2022 and beyond, we’re looking for a &lt;strong&gt;International Expansion Manager  &lt;/strong&gt;who’s passionate about languages, localization and helping people land dream jobs.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s in it for you?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping shape a fast-growing HR tech startup as an early employee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully remote position with bright, motivated, and friendly colleagues around the world &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary + share appreciation rights (SARs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible hours and vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid parental leave &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote working budget: €1,000 per year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning and development budget: 3.5% of salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The job in a nutshell&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;Localization at TestGorilla (or, as we like to call it, international expansion) is centered around linguistic excellence, a great team environment, and cutting-edge technology. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are responsible for the translation and cultural adaptation of everything TestGorilla creates, from our scientifically designed skills tests (ranging from coding to personality and cognitive ability tests) to beautiful user interfaces and marketing campaigns that attract customers worldwide. &lt;br&gt;Our work is not just about translation, it’s about providing our customers and candidates with an experience that feels local.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As the &lt;strong&gt;International Expansion Manager&lt;/strong&gt;, you will work directly with the Head of Product, train, grow and drive the International Expansion team and develop key relationships with our third-party linguists. You will be directly involved in all International Expansion initiatives and responsible for all elements of the localization workflow of our content, from request creation to job completion. You will become a localization champion. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This is an amazing opportunity for an International Expansion Manager that is looking to embark on an entrepreneurial journey and is ready to put a dent in the universe! &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’ll spend time on the following:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating, managing and growing the International Expansion team &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implementing and optimizing end-to-end localization workflows using our translation management tools and systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing localization projects and requirements across stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Driving high-quality output from localization vendors and freelancers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing independent projects within the program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working cross-functionally with TestGorilla stakeholders to identify critical business blockers and collaborate to solve and optimize these&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifying and managing project risk through prioritization, bug management, and any other means necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing the localization budget for your projects by gathering data on the cost, timeliness, and quality of your projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leading project kick-offs and meetings with cross-functional groups for planning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Promoting international expansion to stakeholders&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here’s what we are looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are inspired by our mission to put &lt;em&gt;1 billion of people in dream jobs&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are fully aligned with &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/careers/"&gt;our values&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience leading a team of project managers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a strong ability to balance hands-on execution and strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a strong knowledge of industry-standard localization tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have excellent written and verbal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have strong analytical problem-solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are proactive and innovative by nature&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have strong attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are comfortable with the ambiguity and pace of iteration of an early-stage startup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;We typically expect candidates with at least 5  y. of experience in &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/test-library/role-specific-skills-tests/project-management-test/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;project management&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, preferably working on Localization projects that involve language launches, software, and/or creative content localization, into have the skills mentioned above.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus points if…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience working in a SaaS company and a fast-growing startup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are multilingual (for example, English, Spanish, French, German, Portuguese, Dutch)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interested?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;We don’t offer rainbow glitter unicorns or dog-friendly offices (we literally don’t have an office), but we do offer real people, solid core values, and a product meant to give everyone a fair, unbiased chance at their dream jobs.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Here at TestGorilla, we eat our own dog food. We use our assessment platform to make sure we make the best hiring decisions, faster and bias-free.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;So if this role sounds like a good fit for you, I’d like you to take an assessment so we can get a better idea of whether you would be the perfect fit for this role. It’s also a great opportunity for you to get to know our product!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;If you’re hired, I’ll do everything I can to help you succeed at TestGorilla and throughout the rest of your career.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-international-expansion-manager"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-international-expansion-manager&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 03:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 03:19:42 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-international-expansion-manager</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-international-expansion-manager</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0077/5904/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>TestGorilla: Senior Product Manager</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0077/5904/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Amsterdam
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/"&gt;https://www.testgorilla.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Hi,&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;I’m Claudia, the Head of Product at TestGorilla. We’re a fast-growing &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/"&gt;HR tech startup&lt;/a&gt; that helps teams make better hiring decisions faster and bias-free.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Over the past year, we’ve experienced tremendous growth. More than 7,500 companies have replaced CVs with our assessments to screen candidates in an unbiased and data-driven way. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As we scale our efforts in 2022 and beyond, we’re looking for a &lt;strong&gt;Senior Product Manager &lt;/strong&gt;who’s passionate about building amazing product experiences and helping people land dream jobs. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s in it for you?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping shape a fast-growing HR tech startup as an early employee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully remote position with bright, motivated, and friendly colleagues around the world &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary + Share appreciation rights (SARs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible hours and vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid parental leave &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote working budget: €1,000 per year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning and development budget: 3.5% of salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;The job in a nutshell&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a&lt;strong&gt; Senior Product Manager,&lt;/strong&gt; you’ll be responsible for creating and shipping products that help hundreds of thousands of users around the world land their dream job. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Together with a cross-functional team, you’ll take ownership of translating our product vision and strategy into a roadmap, ensure seamless product delivery and drive feedback loops on what has been shipped. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Your goal is to give our customers and their candidates the best experience possible out there! This is an amazing opportunity for a product manager that is looking to embark on an entrepreneurial journey and is ready to put a dent in the universe! &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’ll spend time on the following:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define a vision, strategy and roadmap that drives maximum impact for your area of the customer and candidate experience. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/test-library/role-specific-skills-tests/product-owner-test/"&gt;Drive product execution&lt;/a&gt;: gather requirements, define functionality, set goals, deliver with your team against these goals, resolve quality issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with cross-functional stakeholders (Customer Success, Sales, Marketing, etc.). to factor their requirements into product decisions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Talk to users on a regular basis: our customers that create assessments as well as candidates taking the assessment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leverage data and user insights to create solutions that satisfy and solve user needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create clear and thoughtful documentation that can easily be understood and used by both technical and non-technical stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure UX and product-led growth is at the heart of what we build.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gain a broader understanding of trends in the HR and HR-tech vertical that impact product development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in a collaborative, talented distributed team across the globe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here's what we are looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are inspired by our mission to put &lt;em&gt;one billion people in dream jobs&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are fully aligned with our &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/careers/"&gt;values &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a track record of shipping and scaling high quality products that effectively service the needs of both customers and the business.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have creative and innovative problem solving skills and feel comfortable engaging in detailed conversations about strategy and product design with both non-technical and technical audiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are data driven and use that skill to drive strategic decisions for the product you are working on. Making sure we tackle the biggest opportunities in the most effective way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re able to think big, but start small. You can establish a north star for your product while maintaining an agile mindset towards getting there.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a user-first mindset. You’re passionate about understanding their needs and continuously improving their experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have strong collaboration and relationship building skills that allow you to build cross-functional relationships.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have excellent communication skills (both written and verbal) and attention to detail. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are comfortable with ambiguity and thrive in the fast paced environment of an early-stage startup that is operating remotely around the globe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;We typically expect candidates with at least &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;5 years of Senior Product Management experience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to have the skills mentioned above.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus points if…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience working in a high growth product-led startup.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have domain experience working in HR-tech and/or SaaS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have led detailed short-term product roadmaps while keeping the longer term vision intact.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have strong experience with UI/UX design, and you are passionate about design and creating beautiful products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interested?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We don’t offer rainbow glitter unicorns or dog-friendly offices (we literally don’t have an office), but we do offer real people, solid core values, and a product meant to give everyone a fair, unbiased chance at their dream jobs.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Here at TestGorilla, we eat our own dog food. We use our assessment platform to make sure we make the best hiring decisions, faster and bias-free. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;So if this role sounds like a good fit for you, I’d like you to take an assessment so we can get a better idea about whether you would fit the role. It’s also a great opportunity for you to get to know our product!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;If you’re hired, I’ll do everything I can to help you succeed at TestGorilla and throughout the rest of your career.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-product-manager-2"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-product-manager-2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 03:13:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 03:13:36 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-product-manager-2</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-product-manager-2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0077/5101/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>TestGorilla: Senior Data Analyst</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0077/5101/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Amsterdam, The Netherlands
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/"&gt;https://www.testgorilla.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Hi,&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;I’m Claudia, the Head of Product at TestGorilla. We’re a fast-growing &lt;a href="https://testgorilla.com/"&gt;HR tech startup&lt;/a&gt; that helps teams make better hiring decisions faster and bias-free.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Over the past year, we’ve experienced tremendous growth. More than 7,500 companies have replaced CVs with our assessments to screen candidates in an unbiased and data-driven way. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As we scale our efforts in 2022 and beyond, we’re looking for a &lt;strong&gt;Senior&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Data Analyst &lt;/strong&gt;who’s passionate about building amazing product experiences and helping people land dream jobs. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s in it for you?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping shape a fast-growing HR tech startup as an early employee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully remote position with bright, motivated, and friendly colleagues around the world &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary and stock options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible hours and vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid parental leave &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;€1000 remote working budget per year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning &amp;amp; development budget of 3,5% of salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;The job in a nutshell&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a&lt;strong&gt; Senior Data Analyst&lt;/strong&gt;, you’ll be responsible for supporting the data needs of a large number of teams in our organization and help them become more data-driven. As the first Data Analyst on the ground, you’ll have the opportunity to lay the foundations for how we run and grow our Data team. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You’ll work closely with different (cross-functional) teams to uncover insights about our business, develop hypotheses and embed an iterative mindset of testing and learning. One day you might be helping the Sales team to improve their lead scoring system by assessing leading upsell indicators, the next day you are analyzing verbatim feedback from users to identify and prioritize improvement opportunities. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is an amazing opportunity for a data analyst that is looking to embark on an entrepreneurial journey and is ready to put a dent in the universe! &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’ll spend time on the following:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leverage data to uncover valuable insights about our customers and our candidates and develop hypotheses for further analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Investigate usage patterns to uncover points of friction in our product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Study A/B test results and make suggestions for new experiments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze uptake of new released features across our different user cohorts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide the various teams with dashboards, reports and visualizations that help them understand performance in the most efficient way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the various teams and departments to determine and measure the right metrics for their respective domains.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Empower others in the organization to be more self-reliant for their data needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create the foundation for our data model and reporting framework.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in a collaborative, talented distributed team across the globe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here's what we are looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are inspired by our mission to put &lt;em&gt;1 billion people in dream jobs.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are fully aligned with our &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/careers/"&gt;values. &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have 5+ years of experience in data, reporting and analytical problem solving.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have strong &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/test-library/programming-skills-tests/sql-coding-test-complex-queries/"&gt;SQL skills&lt;/a&gt; and worked with a modern data warehouse like Redshift, BigQuery or Snowflake.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have technical knowledge of relational databases, data modeling and data visualization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience building reports in BI tools like Tableau or Looker.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience with product analytic tools like Google Analytics, Mixpanel, Amplitude, or similar.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have excellent communication skills (both written and verbal) and attention to detail. Your analysis and actionable insights are always high quality, accurate and easy to understand.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have strong collaboration and relationship building skills that allow you to build cross-functional relationships.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are comfortable with ambiguity and thrive in the fast paced environment of an early-stage startup that is operating remotely around the globe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus points if…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience working in a high growth product-led startup.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have prior experience in  HR-tech and/or SaaS with a background in hypothesis-driven A/B Testing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interested?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;We don’t offer rainbow glitter unicorns or dog-friendly offices (we literally don’t have an office), but we do offer real people, solid core values, and a product meant to give everyone a fair, unbiased chance at their dream jobs.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Here at TestGorilla, we eat our own dog food. We use our assessment platform to make sure we make the best hiring decisions faster and bias-free. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;So if this role sounds like a good fit for you, I’d like you to apply by taking this assessment. This will take about an hour and will focus on your soft and hard skills required to succeed in this role. It’s also a great opportunity for you to get to know our product!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;If you’re hired, I’ll do everything I can to help you succeed at TestGorilla and throughout the rest of your career!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-data-analyst-1"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-data-analyst-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 03:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 03:10:22 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-data-analyst-1</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-data-analyst-1</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/5898/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>TestGorilla: Senior Product Designer</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/5898/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Amsterdam
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/"&gt;https://www.testgorilla.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Hi,&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;I’m Claudia, the Head of Product at TestGorilla. We’re a fast-growing &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/"&gt;HR tech startup&lt;/a&gt; that helps teams make better hiring decisions faster and bias-free.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Over the past year, we’ve experienced tremendous growth. More than 7,500 companies have replaced CVs with our assessments to screen candidates in an unbiased and data-driven way. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As we scale our efforts in 2022 and beyond, we’re looking for a &lt;strong&gt;Senior Product Designer &lt;/strong&gt;who’s passionate about creating amazing product experiences and helping people land dream jobs. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s in it for you?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping shape a fast-growing HR tech startup as an early employee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully remote position with bright, motivated, and friendly colleagues around the world &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary + Share appreciation rights (SARs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible hours and vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid parental leave &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote working budget: €1,000 per year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning and development budget: 3.5% of salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;The job in a nutshell&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a &lt;strong&gt;Senior Product Designer&lt;/strong&gt;, you’ll be responsible for creating products that help hundreds of thousands of users around the world land their dream job. You’ll work on identifying and solving complex design problems, work together with your cross-functional team to shape them to the best experience possible out there and make sure that what gets shipped matches our design standards. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is an amazing opportunity for a product designer that is looking to embark on an entrepreneurial journey and is ready to put a dent in the universe! &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’ll spend time on the following:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work through design problems from beginning to end: unpacking the problem, ideating new products and features, prototyping, user validation and finally creating detailed interactions to handover to engineering&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sketch and prototype ideas to assess viability of a solution early on in the design process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Validate design solutions with our different target audiences, using both qualitative and quantitative methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Iterate on feedback from your cross-functional team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with engineers as they build and ship&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take an active role in growing our design team, improving processes and collaborating with other designers to make their work and the whole team better&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here's what we are looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are inspired by our mission of people in dream jobs &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are aligned with our &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/careers/"&gt;values&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have 5+ years of experience as a Product Designer or similar role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a Product Design or &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/test-library/role-specific-skills-tests/ux-ui-design-test/"&gt;UI/UX design&lt;/a&gt; portfolio with multiple case studies of products you worked on&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can think through complex interaction problems with a systematic approach and attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience creating complex interaction design, user experiences, flows and prototypes with high-fidelity visuals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are able to discuss and explain your design decisions and back them up by applying customer insights and business metrics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are comfortable giving and taking feedback, and apply feedback to final designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; You can handle multiple projects at the same time and are able to adjust priorities as our business needs change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are comfortable with ambiguity and thrive in the fast paced environment of an early-stage startup that is operating remotely around the globe&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have strong collaboration and relationship building skills that allow you to build cross-functional relationships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;We typically expect candidates with &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;at least 5 y. of experience in a Product Designer role&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to have the skills mentioned above.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus points if…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience working in a high growth product-led startup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have domain experience working in HR-tech and/or SaaS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interested?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;We don’t offer rainbow glitter unicorns or dog-friendly offices (we literally don’t have an office), but we do offer real people, solid core values, and a product meant to give everyone a fair, unbiased chance at their dream jobs.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Here at TestGorilla, we eat our own dog food. We use our assessment platform to make sure we make the best hiring decisions faster and bias-free. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;So if this role sounds like a good fit for you, I’d like you to apply by &lt;a href="https://assessment.testgorilla.com/testtaker/publicinvitation/2852ffd8-1727-4274-8247-b225f95edd62"&gt;taking this assessment&lt;/a&gt;. This will take about an hour and will focus on your soft and hard skills required to succeed in this role. It’s also a great opportunity for you to get to know our product!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;If you’re hired, I’ll do everything I can to help you succeed at TestGorilla and throughout the rest of your career!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-product-designer-2"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-product-designer-2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 03:07:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 03:07:31 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-product-designer-2</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-senior-product-designer-2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/8339/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>TestGorilla: Product Manager</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/8339/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Amsterdam
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/"&gt;https://www.testgorilla.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Hi,&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;I’m Claudia, the Head of Product at TestGorilla. We’re a fast-growing HR tech startup that helps teams make better hiring decisions faster and bias-free.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Over the past year, we’ve experienced tremendous growth. More than 7,500 companies have replaced CVs with our assessments to screen candidates in an unbiased and data-driven way. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As we scale our efforts in 2022 and beyond, we’re looking for a &lt;strong&gt;Product Manager &lt;/strong&gt;who’s passionate about building amazing product experiences and helping people land dream jobs. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s in it for you?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping shape a fast-growing HR tech startup as an early employee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully remote position with bright, motivated, and friendly colleagues around the world &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary + Share appreciation rights (SARs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible hours and vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid parental leave &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote working budget: €1,000 per year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning and development budget: 3.5% of salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;The job in a nutshell&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a &lt;strong&gt;Product Manager&lt;/strong&gt;, you’ll be responsible for creating and shipping products that help hundreds of thousands of users around the world land their dream job. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Together with a cross-functional team, you’ll take ownership of translating our product vision and strategy into a roadmap, ensure seamless product delivery and drive feedback loops on what has been shipped. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Your goal is to give our customers and their candidates the best experience possible out there! This is an amazing opportunity for a product manager that is looking to embark on an entrepreneurial journey and is ready to put a dent in the universe! &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’ll spend time on the following:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define a vision, strategy and roadmap that drives maximum impact for your area of the customer and candidate experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/test-library/role-specific-skills-tests/product-owner-test/"&gt;Drive product execution&lt;/a&gt;: gather requirements, define functionality, set goals, deliver with your team against these goals, resolve quality issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with cross-functional stakeholders (Customer Success, Sales, Marketing, etc.). to factor their requirements into product decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Talk to users on a regular basis: our customers that create assessments as well as candidates taking the assessment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leverage data and user insights to create solutions that satisfy and solve user needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create clear and thoughtful documentation that can easily be understood and used by both technical and non-technical stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure UX and product-led growth is at the heart of what we build&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gain a broader understanding of trends in the HR and HR-tech vertical that impact product development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in a collaborative, talented distributed team across the globe&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here's what we are looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are inspired by our mission to put &lt;em&gt;one billion people in dream jobs&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are fully aligned with our &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/careers/"&gt;values &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a track record of shipping and scaling high quality products that effectively service the needs of both customers and the business&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have creative and innovative problem solving skills and feel comfortable engaging in detailed conversations about strategy and product design with both non-technical and technical audiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are data driven and use that skill to drive strategic decisions for the product you are working on. Making sure we tackle the biggest opportunities in the most effective way&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re able to think big, but start small. You can establish a north star for your product while maintaining an agile mindset towards getting there.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a user-first mindset. You’re passionate about understanding their needs and continuously improving their experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have strong collaboration and relationship building skills that allow you to build cross-functional relationships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have excellent communication skills (both written and verbal) and attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are comfortable with ambiguity and thrive in the fast paced environment of an early-stage startup that is operating remotely around the globe&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;We typically expect candidates with at least 2  y. of experience in a Product Management position to have the skills mentioned above.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus points if…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience working in a high growth product-led startup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have domain experience working in HR-tech and/or SaaS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have led detailed short-term product roadmaps while keeping the longer term vision intact&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have strong experience with UI/UX design, and you are passionate about design and creating beautiful products&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interested?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We don’t offer rainbow glitter unicorns or dog-friendly offices (we literally don’t have an office), but we do offer solid core values and a product meant to give everyone a fair, unbiased chance at their dream jobs.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Here at TestGorilla, we eat our own dog food. We use our assessment platform to make sure we make the best hiring decisions, faster and bias-free. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;So if this role sounds like a good fit for you, I’d like you to take an assessment so we can get a better idea about whether you would fit the role. It’s also a great opportunity for you to get to know our product!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;If you’re hired, I’ll do everything I can to help you succeed at TestGorilla and throughout the rest of your career.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-product-manager-1"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-product-manager-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 02:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 02:40:40 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-product-manager-1</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-product-manager-1</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TestGorilla: Growth Product Manager</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Amsterdam, The Netherlands
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/"&gt;https://www.testgorilla.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Hi there,&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;I’m Claudia, the Head of Product at TestGorilla. We’re a fast-growing HR tech startup that helps teams make better hiring decisions faster and bias-free.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Over the last year, we’ve experienced tremendous growth. More than 7,500 companies have replaced CVs with our assessments to screen candidates in an unbiased and data-driven way. That growth is in part thanks to our extensive inbound marketing program. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As we look to scale our efforts in 2022 and beyond, we’re looking for a &lt;strong&gt; Growth Product Manager&lt;/strong&gt; who’s passionate about joining our quest to help people land dream jobs. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s in it for you?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping shape a fast-growing HR tech startup as an early employee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully remote position with bright, motivated, and friendly colleagues around the world &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chance to be at the forefront of a growing trend of Agile Marketing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary + share appreciation rights (SARs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible hours and vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid parental leave &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote working budget: €1,000 per year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning and development budget: 3,5% of salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The job in a nutshell&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;Reporting into our Head of Product, we are looking for a creative and highly collaborative &lt;strong&gt;Growth Product Manager&lt;/strong&gt; with a solid experimentation background and an obsession over the user's needs to lead one of our new Marketing Squads. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a Growth Product Manager in our Marketing Department, you'll collaborate with stakeholders and teams from multiple departments to help attract new users to TestGorilla, and convert them into valued customers. You will do this by developing in-depth product, customer, and market insight, translating that insight into a healthy portfolio of marketing experiments that can help us provide a better experience to our users, and validating &amp;amp; informing our brand positioning and product strategy. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This is an amazing opportunity for a Growth Product Manager who is looking to embark on an entrepreneurial journey and is ready to put a dent in the universe! &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’ll spend time on the following:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with Test Gorilla's Product and Marketing leadership teams to help plan and execute an acquisition strategy to drive sustainable user growth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prioritize a healthy portfolio of marketing experiments and marketing campaigns that can move the needle for user visits, conversion, and engagement &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop a deep understanding of our users and our content through qualitative research, data analytics and experimentation &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Form part of the Product and Engineering team by collaborating with Product Designers and Engineers - from discovery to delivery, on to monitoring after release&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work cross-functionally across the company to understand how Marketing can leverage our product, content, articles, creatives, and landing pages to grow our user base&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's what we are looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are inspired by our mission of &lt;em&gt;putting people in their dream jobs&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are fully aligned with our &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/careers/"&gt;values &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are natively proficient in written English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are passionate about Product Management and &lt;a href="https://www.testgorilla.com/test-library/role-specific-skills-tests/growth-marketing-b2c-test/"&gt;Marketing&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience in a marketing role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience running experiments with lean thinking and quick iterations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data-driven approach to product management and prioritization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent stakeholder management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mindset that always thinks MVP first&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User psychology and marketing know-how &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are comfortable with the ambiguity and pace of iteration of a hyper-growth startup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;We typically expect candidates with at least &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;3 years of experience in agile cross-functional product&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; and/or marketing team to have the skills mentioned above.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus points if…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience working in a SaaS company and a fast-growing startup &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience working in a Product-led growth environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience with Agile Marketing &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interested?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;We don’t offer rainbow glitter unicorns or dog-friendly offices (we literally don’t have an office), but we do offer real people, solid core values, and a product meant to give everyone a fair, unbiased chance at their dream jobs.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Here at TestGorilla, we eat our own dog food. We use our assessment platform to make sure we make the best hiring decisions faster and bias-free. I took one too and I enjoyed it!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;So if this role sounds like a good fit for you, I’d like you to &lt;a href="https://assessment.testgorilla.com/testtaker/publicinvitation/cc74819f-dbe4-4978-b112-8d75fc0923b2"&gt;take an assessment&lt;/a&gt; so we can get a better idea about whether you would fit the role. It’s also a great opportunity for you to get to know our product!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;If you’re hired, I’ll do everything I can to help you succeed at TestGorilla and throughout the rest of your career.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-growth-product-manager-1"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-growth-product-manager-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 02:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 02:30:42 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-growth-product-manager-1</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/testgorilla-growth-product-manager-1</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/9462/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>EnBW Energie Baden-Württemberg AG: Projektmanager Einkauf Offshore Wind (m/w/d)</title>
      <region>Europe Only</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/9462/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Karlsruhe
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://vonq.io/3T433pF"&gt;https://vonq.io/3T433pF&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Über das Unternehmen&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gemeinsam packen wir Dinge an, die uns auch morgen begleiten. Wir entwickeln intelligente Energieprodukte, machen unsere Städte nachhaltiger und treiben den Ausbau erneuerbarer Energien voran. Hier bei EnBW gibt es Raum für Gestaltung und Entfaltung.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Über den Bereich&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wir sind Teil eines sich verändernden, zunehmend agiler werdenden Konzerns, der gerade den größten Windpark in der deutschen Nordsee baut. In Brandenburg realisieren wir die größten Solarparks der Republik und unsere Fuel Switch Projekte zeigen die neuen Wege konventioneller Energien auf.&lt;br&gt;Als Projektmanager*in Einkauf Offshore Wind unterstützen Sie die Entwicklung und Umsetzung deutscher Offshore Wind Projekte einkaufseitig. Dabei managen Sie alle relevanten Beschaffungsaktivitäten und sind Hauptansprechpartner*in für die Projektleitung zu allen Einkaufsthemen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vielfältige Aufgaben&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Als Projektmanager*in Einkauf sind Sie verantwortlich für die Einkaufsstrategie des jeweiligen Projekts. Dabei fördern Sie explizit die cross-funktionale Zusammenarbeit der verschiedenen Fachbereiche innerhalb des Projekts und agieren selbst als Beschaffungsexpert*in in diesem Bereich&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sie analysieren relevante Markttrends und leiten gemeinsam mit den relevanten Category Manager*innen die strategischen Entscheidungen für das Projekt ab&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Die Entwicklung von unseren zukünftigen Offshore Wind Projekten in der deutschen See unterstützen Sie durch Ihre Kenntnis der Lieferkette und aktuellen Marktpreisen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Im weiteren Projektverlauf leiten Sie das Einkaufsprojektteam und planen, koordinieren und kontrollieren alle relevanten Beschaffungsaktivitäten&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Überzeugendes Profil&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sie sind Einkäufer*in aus Leidenschaft, Technik-affin, kommunikationsstark und haben Ihr Organisationstalent während Ihrer mehrjährigen Einkaufserfahrung stark entwickelt. Neben Ihrer Berufserfahrung bringen Sie ein erfolgreich abgeschlossenes technisches oder kaufmännisches Studium mit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sie haben zudem bereits Erfahrung in der Offshore Wind Industrie sammeln können und kennen die wichtigsten Lieferanten. Auch EU-Vergabeverfahren sind Ihnen vertraut&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ihre Fachkompetenz in Einkaufsprozessen und -methoden sowie Verhandlungs- und Überzeugungsstärke runden Ihr Profil ab&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sie überzeugen durch Ihren Willen, sich weiterzuentwickeln und haben bereits in cross-funktionalen Teams gearbeitet&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sie sprechen sowohl Deutsch als auch Englisch verhandlungssicher und bringen interkulturelle Sensibilität mit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unser Angebot&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spannende Aufgaben eröffnen vielfältige Perspektiven zur persönlichen Entwicklung &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kollegiale Zusammenarbeit im Team und moderne Arbeitsplätze zeichnen uns aus &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible Arbeitszeitmodelle ermöglichen die Vereinbarkeit von Beruf und Privatleben &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attraktive Mitarbeiterangebote zählen zu unseren Stärken&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.enbw.com/unternehmen/karriere/was-wir-ihnen-bieten/"&gt;Mehr &lt;/a&gt; zu unseren vielfältigen Arbeitgeberleistungen im Überblick.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kontakt&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interessiert? Jetzt online bewerben! Ein Anschreiben ist dafür nicht erforderlich, gegebenenfalls stellen wir ein paar jobspezifische Fragen in unserem Bewerbungsformular.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bei Fragen steht Ethra Ilousis, &lt;a href="mailto:a.ilousis@enbw.com"&gt;a.ilousis@enbw.com&lt;/a&gt;, aus dem Personalbereich gerne zur Verfügung.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alle Menschen sind bei uns willkommen, egal welchen Geschlechts, Alters, sexueller Identität, Herkunft, Religion, Weltanschauung, mit oder ohne Behinderung. Hauptsache Sie passen zu uns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.enbw.com/datenschutz/bewerber"&gt;Unsere Informationen zum Datenschutz für Bewerber (w/m/d)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/enbw-energie-baden-wurttemberg-ag-projektmanager-einkauf-offshore-wind-m-w-d"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/enbw-energie-baden-wurttemberg-ag-projektmanager-einkauf-offshore-wind-m-w-d&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 08:52:42 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/listings/enbw-energie-baden-wurttemberg-ag-projektmanager-einkauf-offshore-wind-m-w-d</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/listings/enbw-energie-baden-wurttemberg-ag-projektmanager-einkauf-offshore-wind-m-w-d</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fleetio: Product Quality Analyst, Mobile</title>
      <region>North America Only</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Birmingham, Alabama
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://fleetio.com"&gt;https://fleetio.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;As a Product Quality Analyst at Fleetio, your job is to participate in building remarkable solutions for complex problems. You’ll achieve this by assessing our products' business functionality, design, usability, and overall quality. You’ll be the voice of the customer and champion the user experience in everything you do. You’ll own the Fleetio standard for quality and play a major role in helping us create value for our customers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;In this role, your focus will be on our native iOS and Android applications. You’ll help facilitate the mobile release cycle and have a deep understanding of how Fleetio’s platforms integrate as a whole. In addition, you’ll collaborate with several other Fleetio teams to help identify, troubleshoot, recreate, and resolve issues and escalations on all platforms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We’re looking for a highly organized, observant, and persistent team member. This person notices the little things and sweats the small stuff. They excel at understanding complex business problems, can pinpoint the root cause of issues, can identify inconsistencies in design and functionality, and can articulate trade-offs and communicate difficult feedback. Remember to mention coffee in your application so we know you read this.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;About Fleetio&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Fleetio is a modern software platform that helps thousands of organizations worldwide manage their fleet operations. Transportation technology is a hot market and we’re leading the charge, with raving fans and new customers signing up daily.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More about our team and company:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Watch our culture videos: &lt;a href="https://fleet.io/culture"&gt;https://fleet.io/culture&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fleetio overview video: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IlvIbwZT3oU"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IlvIbwZT3oU&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More about the Fleetio platform: &lt;a href="https://www.fleetio.com/features"&gt;https://www.fleetio.com/features&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our careers page: &lt;a href="https://www.fleetio.com/careers"&gt;https://www.fleetio.com/careers&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead and champion product quality and user experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure timely and high-quality release of our features to our customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build customer trust by contributing to the improvement of the software quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage multiple testing initiatives for both new features and iterative enhancements primarily in our mobile apps with opportunities to assist in testing web applications and APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with Software Engineers and help build a comprehensive automated test suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specialize in QA testing for our native iOS and Android applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Play a part in the mobile release cycle on iOS and Android&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with the Product Management, Product Marketing, Design, and Engineering teams to validate product specifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with the Engineering teams to identify and resolve escalated issues within the product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Suggest opportunities for process improvements across the team, especially as it relates to mobile-specific release processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s in it for you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a part of an incredible team of “A” players who go above and beyond to make Fleetio a successful company. We’re a customer-centric team with a great product, excellent support, and countless happy customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work remotely (within the United States) or at our Birmingham, AL HQ. About half of our product, engineering, and design teams work remotely, and as a company, we strive to promote a strong remote working culture and have done so since the beginning (2012).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate in a transparent environment where you are provided the necessary tools, processes, and encouragement to excel daily.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You get to be heard by colleagues who are eager to apply the best practices and ideas you bring to the table and who will share theirs as well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years of manual QA testing experience on iOS and Android mobile platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of mobile release cycles and App Store/Play Store release processes for iOS/Android&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with project management and issue-tracking software systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to multitask and context-switch within a fast-paced, dynamic, and evolving environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re a team player, and you enjoy collaborating with multiple project owners across multiple departments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can understand and solve complex problems, and you enjoy doing so&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You communicate succinctly and effectively both written and verbally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;Considered a plus:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You know a thing or two about the Fleet industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have worked with Asana and Jira&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience with automated testing frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have experience using cloud app testing infrastructure such as Firebase, Kobiton&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% health/dental coverage (50% coverage for family)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vision insurance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Incentive stock options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401(k) match of 4%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PTO - 4 weeks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8 company holidays + 2 floating holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parental and bonding leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dependent care and medical FSA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Short and long term disability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Community service funds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional development funds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health and wellness initiatives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mac laptop + new hire equipment stipend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monthly catered lunches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully stocked kitchen with tons of drinks &amp;amp; snacks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote working friendly since 2012 &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/fleetio-product-quality-analyst-mobile"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/fleetio-product-quality-analyst-mobile&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 17:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 17:11:09 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/fleetio-product-quality-analyst-mobile</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/fleetio-product-quality-analyst-mobile</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0066/9892/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Payoneer Germany GmbH: Merchant Services, Senior Product Strategy Lead</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0066/9892/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Munich, Germany
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.payoneer.com/enterprise/solutions/payment-orchestration/"&gt;https://www.payoneer.com/enterprise/solutions/payment-orchestration/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Product Offering Lead/ Manager&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Build Your Career | Love your Work | Make a Difference&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Payoneer’s mission is to empower businesses to &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;go beyond &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;– beyond borders, limits and expectations. In today’s digital world, Payoneer enables any business of any size from anywhere to access new economic opportunities by making it possible to transact as easily globally as they do locally.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Payoneer’s digital platform streamlines global commerce for millions of small businesses, marketplaces and enterprises from 200 countries and territories. Leveraging its robust technology, compliance, operations and banking infrastructure, Payoneer delivers a suite of services that includes cross-border payments, working capital, tax solutions, merchant services and risk management. Powering growth for customers ranging from aspiring entrepreneurs in emerging markets to the world’s leading digital brands like Airbnb, Amazon, Google and Upwork, Payoneer makes global commerce easy and secure.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;With over 150 employees from 32 countries, our team is truly international in every sense of the word. We are a FinTech team passionate about helping SMB’s across the world grow by bringing equalilty &amp;amp; opportunities wherever they are in the world.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt;What we have&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We have a hybrid collocated in multiple worldwide offices / distributed group of business stakeholders, product owners, software and delivery engineers working closely with the product offering team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We provide a range of payment-related services &amp;amp; products to our customer with Product Offering team involved in the introduction and development of the new products. Product Offering is primarily responsible for the Vision, Mission, Value Proposition &amp;amp; Roadmap of Payoneer Checkout. It is responsible for truly understanding customer needs, translating these into the above &amp;amp; inspiring Payoneer as we go along the rocket ship journey&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;We talk via Slack, Zoom, MS Teams and use Jira, Confluence, ProductBoard, Figma &amp;amp; Miro a lot.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we require from you&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years in product roles with a key understanding of product management methods, applied concepts and tools in modern product management and product design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know SMBs, preferably in ecommerce. Be able to relate to them, talk to them and understand what they need from us&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ideally know payments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Entrepreneurial mindset with a uncompromisable value generation and problem-solving attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A great team player, communication professional etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Product Owners, Developers, Commercial, Strategy &amp;amp; GTM stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Commercially astute in the financial aspects of a FinTech&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relentless focus on data. From gathering, analyzing with colleagues to making decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With a customer base in the millions &amp;amp; spread across the world, speaking multiple languages is a great bonus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Things you’ll do&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be part of  our Product Offering for our Checkout product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report to the Head of Product Offering – Checkout. Own a critical part of the Checkout product offering vision, mission, value proposition &amp;amp; roadmap&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand our customers, truly understanding their needs and the reasons their needs exist&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Be an inspirational character within the business gaining support and bringing the company on the journey product offering charts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand our customers alternatives to us and why customers use them. Bringing this knowledge to our value proposition and roadmap.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collect market insights, constantly thrive to understand the needs and drive innovation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive the value proposition and perfect the understanding what makes it a great product offer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and document the vision of features you own and support the product domains to understand, plan and execute&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with our local GTM teams to ensure success with customer acquisition targets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No people management duties.                                                                                                                                     &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Who we are:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt; Payoneer (NASDAQ: PAYO) is the world’s go-to partner for digital commerce, everywhere.  From borderless payments to boundless growth, Payoneer promises any business, in any market, the technology, connections and confidence to participate and flourish in the new global economy. Powering growth for customers ranging from aspiring entrepreneurs in emerging markets to the world’s leading brands, Payoneer offers a universe of opportunities, open to you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/payoneer-germany-gmbh-merchant-services-senior-product-strategy-lead"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/payoneer-germany-gmbh-merchant-services-senior-product-strategy-lead&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 12:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 12:04:32 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/payoneer-germany-gmbh-merchant-services-senior-product-strategy-lead</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/payoneer-germany-gmbh-merchant-services-senior-product-strategy-lead</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/8134/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Semaphore : Product Marketing Manager Remote </title>
      <region>Latin America Only</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/8134/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Novi Sad, Serbia 
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://semaphoreci.com"&gt;https://semaphoreci.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="https://semaphoreci.com/"&gt;Semaphore&lt;/a&gt;, a leading continuous delivery service with a global customer base, is looking for a Product Marketing Manager to join our Marketing team. Our product is used by the World's best engineering teams, such as Confluent, Better Up, and Tigera. With your help, we will ensure that our customers are always on top of what new features the product has and how to leverage them for their CI/CD success.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are looking for someone passionate about technology and software development, who possesses 'people skills, and who can be a bridge between the Product team, the Marketing team, the Sales team, and the Semaphore’s customers.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This is a full-time and remote position with at least 4 hrs of overlap with us (HQ) CET time.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The best candidate will have that curiosity that leads to eagerness to learn new things, grasp complex technical concepts quickly, and explain them to the world, in the most effective manner.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a critical contributor to Semaphore’s product success, your role will be to:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strategically plan and lead new product launch and release marketing activities while working closely with the Product, Customer Success, and Marketing teams. You will report to the Head of Marketing. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and promote educational content about the product’s new features in the form of blog posts, videos, website updates, email campaigns, customer success stories, and product slide decks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist the Sales team by creating the sales enablement materials they need to sell the product successfully.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor and optimize product marketing campaigns and materials for maximum effectiveness.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Requirements:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 years of experience working as a Product Marketing Manager at a SaaS company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in creating technical content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communication skills, with the capacity to explain and translate complex technical concepts into simple and intuitive communications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be highly organized and self-managed, have an excellent work ethic, and attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be able to work effectively remotely with an international team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Benefits:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The impact of working on a product that is competing in a global market.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Join a small team of around 30 full-time employees who love what they do.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A healthy 40-hour work week, friendly and supportive work environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company retreats.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Space to learn continuously and choose the tools and equipment for your job.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid trips to conferences and books of your choice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interact with developers that use Semaphore and talk about the latest and greatest way to develop and ship software.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid membership at a fitness club of your choice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Semaphore is an equal-opportunity employer. Consistent with our mission of serving a diverse and global audience, we value a diverse workforce and inclusive culture, which reflects that. We encourage applications from all qualified individuals without regard to race, color, religion, gender, sexual orientation, gender identity or expression, age, national origin, marital status, disability, and veteran status.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/semaphore-product-marketing-manager-remote"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/semaphore-product-marketing-manager-remote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 09:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 09:37:09 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/semaphore-product-marketing-manager-remote</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/semaphore-product-marketing-manager-remote</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0016/4419/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Credit Glory: Data Analyst</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0016/4419/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Henderson, NV
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.creditglory.com"&gt;http://www.creditglory.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;About Us&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are a fully remote team looking for a proactive and experienced Data Analyst to join our team.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Your responsibilities will include working closely with our CTO &amp;amp; COO to make sense of our marketing efforts, and to produce accurate and relevant data that helps improve our customers' financial futures. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;If you enjoy diving into data, uncovering insights, creating actionable reports, then this is a great position for you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We’re Looking For:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience as a data analyst and/or data scientist&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid SQL skills to create and evaluate complex queries with numerous tables and relationships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Python (and related libraries such as Pandas and Numpy) or proficiency in Ruby&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong verbal and written communication skills to explain insights and results to the stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience working remotely&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analytical, proactive &amp;amp; problem-solving skills (along with attention to detail)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to receive &amp;amp; administer constructive feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-hour overlap with CET timezone required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You’ll Do:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build, maintain and own a suite of internal reports that guide our day to day decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with the rest of the company and engineering team to provide necessary insights and to find a common truth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish best practices for data analysis, A/B experiments etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Pay&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Starting salary is between $80,000 - $100,000 USD depending on your skills and experience.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/credit-glory-data-analyst"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/credit-glory-data-analyst&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 14:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 14:45:20 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/credit-glory-data-analyst</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/credit-glory-data-analyst</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/7656/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Meilisearch: Product Marketing Manager</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/7656/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Paris, France
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://meilisearch.com"&gt;https://meilisearch.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;We are a team of 26 passionate people with a majority of tech profiles and our project is growing fast (+10K GitHub stars in 12 months). We are looking for a Product Marketing Manager to own the buyer's journey for all our users with a focus on the bottom-up approach.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🧠 About the role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We have made it our mission to make it easy to find anything anywhere, by providing a go-to search solution for every developer. For 4 years we have developed a fully open-source search solution thanks to the precious feedback of our users.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Beginning of 2022 we started developing a Cloud hosted feature, by demand of our community. We are working with our first clients and are starting to monetize.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a Product Marketing Manager, your role will be to capitalize on our existing brand and product-led growth, by creating and implementing marketing methods to accelerate our development and maximize adoption and user retention. You will work closely with the founders as well as the Product and Developer Relations teams, on topics such as the definition of our positioning, the creation of our marketing campaigns and the improvement of our pricing model.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🧑‍💻 What you’ll be doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a Product Marketing Manager, your role will include:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Defining &amp;amp; executing our marketing strategy:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clarifying and formalizing the characteristics of our clients and personas: customer journey, motivations, pain points…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Crafting our value proposition with the Product team: how is Meilisearch addressing these characteristics?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborating closely with the Developer Relations and Product teams to ensure alignment with company objectives,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participating in the definition of our pricing strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Managing marketing campaigns, from creation to ROI analysis:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Based on the strategy, creating campaign content that conveys our competitive advantage,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifying the relevant channels for the promotion of our marketing content,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Testing and iterating over the combination of audience, channel, and content,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Setting performance expectations, analyzing the data and providing actionable patterns to drive improvements,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Defining and executing a strategy for SEM (SEO + SEA),&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating media and content to support customer journey: landing pages, blog posts, technical content, infographics…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Supporting data driven decisions for our Cloud offer:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conducting market research to provide market insights to the founders and relevant teams: analyst views, market landscapes, competitor intelligence,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gathering the best customer knowledge by interviewing clients and prospects, running workshops and focus groups in partnership with the Product team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🫀 Our ideal profile - Soft skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Empathy, judgment, and tact: You feel comfortable targeting anyone in organizations (executives to developers), understanding their problems, and answering accordingly;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong organizational skills: You can plan, manage your time and communicate to deliver projects;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A dual-minded approach: you’re highly creative but also process-driven; you think scale, and rely on data to make decisions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimistic mindset and not afraid of starting from scratch;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Humility &amp;amp; will to continuously learn: you take experimentation seriously;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to coordinate across many teams, collect the correct information and provide efficient communication.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🔨 Our ideal profile - Hard skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Must-have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years of overall experience, 3+ years of experience in marketing or business development of B2B SaaS/cloud services;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Former experience in a fast-moving professional environment;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong tech culture: technical background or experience working with developers/on developer tool products;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding communications skills to translate complex technical concepts into simple and intuitive communications and create perfect marketing copies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated results in achieving annual growth targets;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deeply passionate about open-source and convinced of its long-lasting impact;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track record in launching new products and optimizing existing product offerings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;⏳ Recruitment process&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please send us your resume and a quick note of why you might be a good fit for this job. Don't hesitate to look at our &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/meilisearch"&gt;LinkedIn page&lt;/a&gt; and to our &lt;a href="https://www.notion.so/Meilisearch-Team-b7f24733f4944fa9b09fd518d6fc3eff"&gt;Meet the Team&lt;/a&gt; page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Screening call (30min) : if your profile fits, you will be contacted for a screening call to briefly chat about your background and motivations, and confirm your availability and salary expectations. &lt;em&gt;If it doesn't fit, you will get an email from us.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HR &amp;amp; culture fit interview (1h): you will meet you will meet &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/morgane-neff-8b1334102/"&gt;Morgane&lt;/a&gt;, our HR Manager and &lt;a href="https://www.notion.so/b049ebf78edb4138b43cf84e031542cd"&gt;Dave&lt;/a&gt;, our Cloud Product Manager, to ask questions about the role and assess your fit with our culture.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical interview (1h): you will meet &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/ferdinandboas?miniProfileUrn=urn%3Ali%3Afs_miniProfile%3AACoAAAJHvmkBGvGdfIi76z_Ul3s12Qn8QTkDJls&amp;amp;lipi=urn%3Ali%3Apage%3Ad_flagship3_search_srp_all%3B1zSn914wQU6iht2YnhHxtg%3D%3D"&gt;Ferdinand&lt;/a&gt;, our Head of Developer Relations and &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/tpayet?miniProfileUrn=urn%3Ali%3Afs_miniProfile%3AACoAABIB-KsBtoHebkiXi3YUPJva25tXBMzj6c8&amp;amp;lipi=urn%3Ali%3Apage%3Ad_flagship3_search_srp_all%3B%2FdawrVQUTki4B0gDSWgsqg%3D%3D"&gt;Thomas&lt;/a&gt;, our COO. They will go more into detail about your background and skill set.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical test (2 weeks) + debrief: we will ask you to create a go-to-market strategy for a specific use case: creation of a value matrix, defining channels, creating campaign messages. You will have two weeks to send us your assignment copy (if needed, the timeline can be extended). A 1h debrief will be organized to discuss the test.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team fit interview (1h): You will meet &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/quentin-de-quelen-4241a865/"&gt;Quentin&lt;/a&gt;, our CEO and &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/charline-moncoucut?miniProfileUrn=urn%3Ali%3Afs_miniProfile%3AACoAACCBgAYB83WGg3aa6lAyEdxSog3sFL0oVWM&amp;amp;lipi=urn%3Ali%3Apage%3Ad_flagship3_search_srp_all%3BHn3%2FSp2ESOCWn4k7hZ2WLA%3D%3D"&gt;Charline&lt;/a&gt;, one of our Product Managers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our HR manager will conduct a reference check - don't hesitate to give her 2 or 3 contacts in advance (preferably a former manager).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;❤️ Why you'll enjoy working with us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🤝 Permanent full-time contract,&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;📈 Stock options,&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🌎 We are open to fully remote applications, as long as you are between GMT-4 and GMT+5 time zones,&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;⏰ &lt;a href="https://blog.meilisearch.com/how-we-implemented-the-4-day-work-week/"&gt;4 day work week&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; flexible working hours,&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🏠 If you’re working from home, we will provide either a stipend for you to equip yourself, or an access to &lt;a href="https://fleex.com/?gclid=CjwKCAjwgr6TBhAGEiwA3aVuIZpF5FkDXQAnR9_jXz9bbftTiRMdOvgGNV6V2CzpBgDnQHtZtugcTxoCF_cQAvD_BwE"&gt;Fleex&lt;/a&gt; (Europe). We also reimburse up to 500 EUR / month for your co working expenses,&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🧘 Access to a mental health platform (&lt;a href="https://www.moka.care/"&gt;moka.care&lt;/a&gt;) + 4 sessions with a coach/trained therapist,&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;👶 3 months paid parental leave,&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🌴 6 weeks paid time off,&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;💪 Management training to freshly hired and newly appointed managers,&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🥳 We all get together &lt;em&gt;at least&lt;/em&gt; once a year for a company offsite.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meilisearch is an equal opportunity employer. We strive to develop an inclusive work environment that reflects the diversity of our open-source community.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/meilisearch-product-marketing-manager"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/meilisearch-product-marketing-manager&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 15:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 15:59:28 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/meilisearch-product-marketing-manager</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/meilisearch-product-marketing-manager</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0074/7299/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Data Virtuality GmbH: Product Manager for Customer UX. Full-time. Unlimited. Contractor.</title>
      <region>Europe Only</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0074/7299/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Leipzig, Germany
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://datavirtuality.com/en/careers/"&gt;https://datavirtuality.com/en/careers/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;We would love to be your new team!&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Working at Data Virtuality means being part of an international team and thriving. What we offer is remote work from your home, wherever it is. Further, you can expect an unlimited long-term freelance contract with full-time work, benefits, and genuine team spirit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;At Data Virtuality, you will experience respectful interactions, harmonious teamwork,&lt;br&gt;without a dog-eat-dog mentality!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT OUR FANTASTIC TEAM WORLDWIDE LOVES ABOUT WORKING WITH DATA VIRTUALITY:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• A stable and reliable job with the freedom and flexibility of a freelancer&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Flexible working hours + fix salary + paid holidays&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Fast and dependable monthly payment – in EUR, USD, or Crypto, as you prefer&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Contributing to the success of a growing company&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Developing a groundbreaking data technology and working with cutting-edge technologies&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Knowledgeable and approachable C-Level&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Continuity and growth potential&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Friendly and international colleagues&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Full integration into our teams and invitation for our team events worldwide&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THE POSITION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Full-time. Freelance. Remote. m/f/d&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a Product Manager for Customer UX, your overall goal should be: to increase the satisfaction of our customers, improve conversion rates, and identify and eliminate potential user experience issues before they become a customer problem. What do we think about how you achieve your goal (There might be some more ways to get to Rome. Your responsibilities are just limited by your drive, ideas, and know-how):&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a Customer Experience Specialist, you will work together with our CEO on our SaaS products. You plan and manage the web front-end roadmap and its backlog, especially Customer UX. Due to your broad experience, you can estimate the time required and plan implementations on this information with our developers. You will plan and deliver UX designs while working closely with cross-functional teams to create optimal and intuitive frontend usability and user experiences for our SaaS Platforms. Therefore it‘s needed to work with customers, partners, and other Data Virtuality stakeholders to identify and clarify functional and non-functional requirements for the product. Based on this, you will write high-quality specifications and communicate specific and actionable requirements to QA and development teams. So we expect that you will influence the product management and development teams to achieve solutions that are right for our customers.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You will be our internal champion for ensuring that our product makes&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;an excellent qualitative impression and radiates high-class value.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU SHOULD BRING TO THE TABLE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• You are obsessed with establishing a perfect customer experience, and at the same time, you can easily talk with developers and understand the technical context.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• 5+ years of Product Management experience in an independent software vendor, working on SaaS applications, ideally in a Data Management related environment.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Strong technical background with the ability to quickly develop deep product knowledge.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Demonstrated skills in analysis, design, product development, and planning.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Strong project management skills and proven ability to generate end-to-end designs - from concept through production detailing.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Ideally, experience with Google Analytics, Mixpanel, Fullstory or similar.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Ideally, proficiency with wireframing and prototyping tools, such as Axure, Sketch, Illustrator, Photoshop, Balsamiq, etc.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Ideally leadership experience&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NICE-TO-HAVE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Experience with data management, product information management, data governance, data warehousing, business intelligence, or data visualization is a plus&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Experience with Cloud (SaaS) software or Big Data technologies is a plus&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Experience in working in agile teams&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WE WOULD LIKE TO SEE FROM YOUR PERSONAL SIDE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Excellent interpersonal skills, with a proven track record of building strong relationships and establishing credibility with customers, prospects, sales and development teams, and the management team&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Highly self-motivated and team-oriented&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Able to work both autonomously and effectively as part of a fully distributed team&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Strong communication and presentation skills, with fluency in English&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;• Technological vision&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/data-virtuality-gmbh-product-manager-for-customer-ux-full-time-unlimited-contractor-1"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/data-virtuality-gmbh-product-manager-for-customer-ux-full-time-unlimited-contractor-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 07:51:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 07:51:32 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/data-virtuality-gmbh-product-manager-for-customer-ux-full-time-unlimited-contractor-1</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/data-virtuality-gmbh-product-manager-for-customer-ux-full-time-unlimited-contractor-1</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0076/4357/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Climate Connect Digital: Product Marketer</title>
      <region>UK Only</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0076/4357/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; London
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://climateconnect.digital/"&gt;https://climateconnect.digital/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;Our team is inspired to change the world by making energy greener and more affordable. Established in 2011 in London, UK, and now headquartered in Gurgaon, India. We have become a leading energy-AI software player from unassuming beginnings, at the vanguard of accelerating the global energy transition.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;In 2020, ReNew Power, India’s largest renewables developer, acquired Climate Connect Digital. Following ReNew’s NASDAQ listing in the summer of 2021, Climate Connect Digital has been newly formed as a fully independent subsidiary. With backing from ReNew for an ambitious and visionary new strategy for rapid organic and inorganic growth.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our mission has technology at its core and involves unlocking value by leveraging information technology and AI/ML  across the energy ecosystem. However, the world is still at the nascent stages of using such technologies in the energy sector to create massive value for all stakeholders.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do you fit in&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are looking for a &lt;strong&gt;Product Marketer&lt;/strong&gt; to help maximize the success of our products and gain an edge in the market. You’ll work hand-in-hand with the product management team to ensure readiness for new offerings, optimize pricing and packaging, coordinate the launch of new offerings, and ensure customer-facing employees can sell and support our products. In addition, you’ll be an expert not just on our products but on our target audiences, understanding how and why they buy and what it takes to achieve product-market fit.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Product Messaging and Positioning&lt;/strong&gt; – Hit the right notes to connect with our target audience and ensure the product is optimally positioned within the market&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Market and Competitive Analysis &lt;/strong&gt;– Be the expert on what the competition is doing and how we can keep our offering highly desirable and attractive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Customer Discovery&lt;/strong&gt; - Combine a variety of primary and secondary research techniques to discover and add clarity to underlying customer needs, behaviours, and motivations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Content Development&lt;/strong&gt; – Develop creative and engaging product collateral across various media types and platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sales Enablement&lt;/strong&gt; – Equip the sales and marketing teams with the insight and material that they need to convince and win customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Brand Development&lt;/strong&gt; - Support the branding team in their attempts to position the Climate Connect Digital brand at the intersection of the technology sector and the fight against climate change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-5 years of experience in B2B SaaS organisations which follow a sales model of customer acquisition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with product teams to understand underlying customer motivations and needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with enabling sales teams on developing collateral and pitching playbooks &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent visual, written, and verbal communication skills, with the ability to tell compelling stories&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong working knowledge of content development and product branding strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well-versed in working with CRM systems and marketing automation stacks to enable workflow integrations and reporting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in collaborating with cross-functional teams across geographies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the energy, climate, or sustainability spaces is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s in it for you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We offer competitive salaries based on prevailing market rates. In addition to your introductory package, you can expect to receive the following benefits:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible working hours and leave policy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning and development opportunities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medical insurance/Term insurance, gratuity benefits over and above the salaries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access to industry and domain thought leaders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;At Climate Connect Digital, you get a rare opportunity to join an established company at the early stages of a significant and well-backed global growth push.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are building a remote-first organization ingrained in the team ethos. We understand its importance for the success of any next-generation technology company. The team includes passionate and self-driven people with unconventional backgrounds, and we’re seeking a similar spirit with the right potential.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What it’s like to work with us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;When you join us, you become part of a strong network and an accomplished legacy from leading technology and business schools worldwide. Such as the Indian Institute of Technology, Oxford University, University of Cambridge, University College London, and many more.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We don’t believe in constrained traditional hierarchies and instead work in flexible teams with the freedom to achieve successful business outcomes. We want more people who can thrive in a fast-paced, collaborative environment. Our comprehensive support system comprises a global network of advisors and experts, providing unparalleled opportunities for learning and growth.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/climate-connect-digital-product-marketer"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/climate-connect-digital-product-marketer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 11:18:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 11:18:28 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/climate-connect-digital-product-marketer</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/climate-connect-digital-product-marketer</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maharishi Foundation International: Product Analyst</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; London (Remote)
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.maharishi.foundation/"&gt;https://www.maharishi.foundation/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.maharishi.foundation/"&gt;Maharishi Foundation International&lt;/a&gt; (MFI) is a US-registered non-profit that supports the development of new technologies and outreach opportunities for the worldwide Transcendental Meditation® (TM®) organisations. Over the past 60 years, more than 10 million people worldwide have learned the TM technique through personal instruction by tens of thousands of certified teachers. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;MFI is a growing, fully remote team of around 50 people, located around the globe but mainly in North America and Europe. As an organisation we are committed to leveraging modern technology and progressive management practices to make the TM technique and its related programmes more available to people everywhere. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We favour a healthy and balanced work environment with opportunities for personal development.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Summary&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are seeking a curious and motivated Product Analyst to join our team to be responsible for using data to help the product and engineering teams understand the performance of our current products as well as generating actionable insights to shape our product strategy going forward. You will be the expert in our organisation in turning data into insights – both in scalable, repeatable ways and in novel exploratory ways too. This remote role is part of our product team, and reports to the Director of Product based in Czechia.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About You&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You love to work with data as much as you enjoy communicating your findings to an interested audience. You are excited about finding ways to help our product and engineering teams to provide more value to our customers using insights derived from data. You are comfortable working at the interface between business, analytics and engineering. You are a strong team player and know that results come from great people working together around meaningful ideas. You are excited by our mission and want to help us achieve it.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using data to identify, prioritize and answer questions essential to the product discovery and development process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generating actionable insights to shape our product strategy via exploratory data analyses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and maintain reports and dashboards for the wider team and external stakeholders to measure business performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enabling data-informed decision making by defining, implementing and monitoring key metrics in dashboards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supporting the planning process by forecasting impact of potential new features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aligning tracking requirements with product and engineering teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Informing the work of the product team by communicating relevant insights effectively&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skills and Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-6 years of experience in product or data analytics role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of work experience in a digital product company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very strong proficiency in SQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience with at least one statistical programming language (R or Python are a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical thinking and product management knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with A/B testing and its statistical foundations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of descriptive statistics, intermediate knowledge of inferential statistics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and prioritization skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to translate business requirements into actionable metrics and analyses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motivated for self-improvement and a healthy lifestyle, and open to / interested in meditation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, presentation, and interpersonal skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English (written and verbal)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work autonomously and remotely&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you are passionate about this work but do not have all of the skills listed we are still interested in speaking with you and encourage you to apply!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pay and Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our pay levels are set according to a formula that combines above-median market rate data for the role (we pay 55th percentile of market rate for this role, based on &lt;a href="https://www.payscale.com/"&gt;Payscale&lt;/a&gt; data) adjusted for your local cost of living based on &lt;a href="https://www.numbeo.com/cost-of-living/rankings_current.jsp"&gt;Numbeo&lt;/a&gt; data.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We take the issue of equitable pay very seriously, and we apply our pay formula to all workers who work 80% or more of full time hours with us.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diversity and inclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We care about diversity - we strive to ensure all of our team feel included and can bring their whole selves to work but we also know that this work is never ‘done’ or complete, and that we can always improve.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our team is fully remote, living and working across 20 countries across the world, and we’d love to hear how you can add to our special culture at MFI.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/maharishi-foundation-international-product-analyst-1"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/maharishi-foundation-international-product-analyst-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 14:49:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 14:49:39 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/maharishi-foundation-international-product-analyst-1</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/maharishi-foundation-international-product-analyst-1</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0081/5727/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>HiveMQ: Senior Technical Product Manager</title>
      <region>Europe Only</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0081/5727/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Landshut, Germany
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://hivemq.com"&gt;https://hivemq.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;HiveMQ’s Vision for this role&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;At HiveMQ, our customers come first. Thus, as a Technical Product Manager, being an integral part of the HiveMQ broker team and working closely with other disciplines, you will discover and deliver new HiveMQ product capabilities that delight our customers. In this role you will work cross-functionally to determine how our users interact with our products and run discovery to nail down user problems, needs and desires. You will strategize product initiatives, break down complex problems and enable your team to deliver new product capabilities. We work with agile principles and believe reliant data enables us to move fast while continuously meriting the trust that our customers store in us every day.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;You will...&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn everything about MQTT, distributed systems, IoT (theory, applications, best practices) and work with your team to understand and deliver outstanding value to our users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facilitate strategy formation to deliver on outcomes through new product initiatives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discover users' needs and opportunities utilizing both quantitative and qualitative methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enable your product team to iteratively discover and deliver new product capabilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enable marketing, customer success and professional services teams and facilitate influx of product insights from the field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;You have...&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound background in software development, ideally related to MQTT or similar distributed streaming technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A passion for distributed technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven strategy formation/alignment skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A learning Mindset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven customer/stakeholder management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant experience as a Technical Product Manager&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acquired problem identification skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding interpersonal skills and a deep empathy with your users &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why Us?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are a remote first company, offering you a very high level of freedom, versatility and autonomy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We also offer you regular training courses to further develop your career&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frequent team events and big annual company outings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our unique HiveMQ culture with great colleagues, outstanding team spirit and innovative technologies &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We offer you a versatile job with high personal responsibility and global challenging tasks &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can work in a professional, international working environment with flat hierarchies and short decision-making paths &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With us, you can grow personally in an exciting industry of the future, helping people and companies reach their full potential &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We live a co-operative and respectful corporate culture with fun at work and room for own ideas &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have the chance to learn, develop and grow with the support of our whole international team &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A very high level of freedom, variability and autonomy &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A MacBook and iPhone of the latest generation &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/hivemq-senior-technical-product-manager"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/hivemq-senior-technical-product-manager&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 10:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 10:14:49 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/hivemq-senior-technical-product-manager</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/hivemq-senior-technical-product-manager</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0076/3612/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>discoverygarden: Solution Architect </title>
      <region>USA Only</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0076/3612/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Canada 
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://discoverygarden.ca"&gt;https://discoverygarden.ca&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;discoverygarden&lt;/em&gt; is a market leading provider of Digital Preservation and Asset Management Systems. Our mission is to help our clients preserve and share their prized digital assets. We believe that by preserving knowledge, history and information, we will better understand our culture - now and in the future. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our solutions are built upon Open Source technologies including Islandora (Drupal) and have been adopted by clients around the world. From scans of telegrams sent by Babe Ruth held at the Baseball Hall of Fame Archives to construction photos of the Golden Gate Bridge housed at the San Francisco Public Library, we give our clients confidence that their prized information, artifacts and stories can be safely protected and shared.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The team at discoverygarden is growing and is looking for a &lt;strong&gt;Solution Architect &lt;/strong&gt;to join the team. As a Solution Architect&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; you will design, describe and manage solution engineering to match it with specific client needs. You are a visionary who designs a blueprint for the solution based on customer requirements and evolving technologies.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If helping organizations and institutions preserve important digital assets of scientific, cultural, or historical significance sounds interesting to you, we would love for you to apply!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a &lt;strong&gt;Solution Architect,&lt;/strong&gt; your day-day may involve:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Working with our clients on articulating their requirements to map out a comprehensive solution and plan;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Liaising closely with our internal Sales, Product and Delivery teams on creating a common understanding of client needs and how they triangulate between the product roadmap and technical stack;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Assist in estimations of project scope and size, arriving at a solution that both our team and the client are comfortable with;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Brainstorm creatively and problem solve to find novel solutions to address complex client requirements and/or technical limitations;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Describe the structure, characteristics, behaviour and other aspects of the software to all project stakeholders, ensuring a seamless project kickoff where expectations are aligned;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Provide specifications according to which the solution is defined, managed and delivered; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Maintain a high-level structure of the software system (architecture), it’s main components, their interfaces, and unique elements depending on the client (i.e. integration paths with external systems);&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;A general architectural vision that guides the organization and serves as a basis for mutual understanding between all parties involved in ongoing product development &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Experience and Skill Set &lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relative experience in a similar capacity and/or familiarity with Islandora and Drupal, ideally as a primary user of the Islandora framework in a past role &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extremely strong English written and oral communication skills; ability to communicate complex technical information to non-technical decision makers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is a fast learner who is extremely comfortable learning new technologies and working in a fast-paced, deadline-driven environment where change is the norm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is comfortable tracking details across many projects and maintaining multiple projects simultaneously&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable attention to detail and the ability to simplify complex, intertwined needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable ability to triangulate needs across a variety of stakeholders, working collaboratively to arrive at a mutually agreed upon solution, and can proactively raise issues that are likely to impact a project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A self-starter and ability operate independently and remotely &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Nice To Haves&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in leadership roles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in technical / software product development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Islandora Digital Asset Management Framework and other digital repository systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Drupal9 and cloud computing (AWS, GCP, Azure)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of JIRA would be an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Employee Benefits&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An exciting position in an agile and entrepreneurial organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote-first work environment with stipend for home office expenses (We prefer if candidates can work at least 50% of their day in Atlantic/Eastern time zone to maximize collaboration) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possibility to make a real impact on a fast-growing tech company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunities to contribute to the open-source Islandora project and community &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resources and support for certifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generous time-off policy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personal fitness stipend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company-paid health, dental and vision benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/discoverygarden-solution-architect"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/discoverygarden-solution-architect&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 18:59:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 18:59:26 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/discoverygarden-solution-architect</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/discoverygarden-solution-architect</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0076/3605/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>AgencyAnalytics: Product Manager</title>
      <region>Canada Only</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0076/3605/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Toronto, Canada
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://agencyanalytics.com"&gt;https://agencyanalytics.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;This is a great opportunity for you as a Product Manager to dive right into a successful SAAS app and begin contributing to product improvements immediately. We have a small product team so you must be the type of person that likes to own a project from start to finish. The work you will do will have an immediate impact on the product and user experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You will own the process in managing a new feature or improvement and getting it released. This includes researching the use cases, collecting and analyzing customer feedback and working with our designers and engineers to get the project completed. You will be responsible for managing our product roadmap and organizing all those involved to make sure projects are moving along.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;🇨🇦 This position is 100% remote and only eligible for those who are authorized to work in Canada. We are hiring for multiple positions with varying responsibilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with the product team on product strategy and vision for your specific projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with the project team for refinement, technical approach and delivery targets of projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage the process and release of bringing new product features and improvements to market&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage the backlog and creation/prioritization of user stories&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform regular audits on the platform to spot opportunities for UI / UX improvements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate the product roadmap across multiple departments including marketing and engineering&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review customer feedback to determine where to prioritize focus within the product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze usage data to discover strengths and weaknesses of the product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work effectively in a distributed, cross functional team model spanning multiple time zones&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job requirements&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years as a product manager&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a product manager role at a SAAS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Digital Marketing Knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;College/ University degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profit-sharing, distributed quarterly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frequent promotions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 weeks vacation and paid sick days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Happy Hour every Friday&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extended health benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continued education allowance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Annual fitness allowance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work from anywhere in the world&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Join a bootstrapped, product-focused, &amp;amp; customer-oriented team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/agencyanalytics-product-manager-2"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/agencyanalytics-product-manager-2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 14:44:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 14:44:09 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/agencyanalytics-product-manager-2</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/agencyanalytics-product-manager-2</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0076/3098/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>SOCi: Director of Product Management</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0076/3098/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; San Diego, CA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://meetsoci.com"&gt;http://meetsoci.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Us:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;SOCi is one of the fastest growing technology companies in the country, ranking in the top tier of Inc 5000’s Fastest Growing Companies in America list for the last 4 years in a row.  The builder of an award-winning enterprise SaaS marketing platform, and one of Forbes’ Best Startup Employers, SOCi boasts hundreds of the world’s largest brands as its customers. The SOCi platform specifically solves complicated marketing and workflow problems for national and global multi-location brands that want to scale and optimize their presence across search, social, reviews, listening, ads, bots, and more. As the largest localized marketing platform in the world, SOCi makes the impossible possible by enabling top brands and their locations to strengthen and scale their digital presence across limitless locations.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our accolades include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recently closed a Series D investment round of $80 million, led by JMI Equity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4x honoree on Inc. 5000 Fastest Growing Companies in America&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2x honoree on Financial Times’ Fastest Growing Companies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3x CEO Finalist for Ernst &amp;amp; Young’s Entrepreneur of the Year award&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Winner of the MarTech Breakthrough Award for Best Overall Social Media Management Platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;#1 Rank by Entrepreneur magazine’s Top Marketing Providers for Franchises, three years in a row&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Front Runner for Gartner award in Reputation Management &amp;amp; Brand Management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2021 Honoree on Forbes America’s Best Startup Employers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Director of Product Management&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our product team drives the product vision and is responsible for the value and viability of our solutions. Through deep discovery and collaboration with our customers, we identify the right problems to solve and leverage design and engineering to deliver differentiated solutions that delight our customers. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As the Director of Product Management, you will collaborate with the VP of Product to identify the problems that we must address from a product perspective in order to deliver on the product strategy set by the VP of Product and executive leadership. You will own the day to day execution of product initiatives and are responsible for the success of our products and will lead 6-9 product team members each owning one of the SOCi products (Social, Reputation, Listings, Local Pages, Bots, Ads, Boost, Surveys, Listening). You will work with your counterparts in Product Operations, Design and Engineering to ensure the delivery of  valuable and viable product improvements on an ongoing, iterative basis. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You have a deep understanding of modern product management practices from Marty Cagan and Dan Olsen school of thought, with a proven track record of practical application. You are well versed in establishing career development and skills growth plans for your product managers. You serve your team, you obsess over your customers, and you execute with precision and impact. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About You… &lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Process&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have product sense, are a leader and get things done&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a proven track record of delivering valuable products, consistently, rapidly and effectively from early stage (finding product-market fit) to mature products  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will guide teams to deliver on product outcomes that align with the company’s strategy and are well versed in executing against OKRs &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will coach and mentor product managers to be creative, strategic, execution focused and with a growth mindset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will coach product managers on product discovery techniques that help them focus on outcome and risk and to leverage the power of written narratives, JTBD, Kano models, customer benefit ladders, interviews, surveys, and other applicable frameworks to define and iterate on features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will instill a culture of rapid hypothesis testing, measurement, and the importance of consistently delivering differentiated and innovative products that solve customer and prospect biggest pain points&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will create a repeatable process for hiring and developing product managers that can deliver on our strategic intent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define and analyze key metrics that inform decision making and measure success of product initiatives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will obsess over product health metrics and work with product operations to provide the business with visibility into how the product is performing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate product strategy into roadmaps that are informed by the product managers discovery of customer problems, market and competitive research, cross-functional stakeholders and most importantly focus on a product outcome &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will pivot as necessary and understand that it's better to deliver value than to stick to a failing plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;People &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deliver and communicate measurable business impact to the VP of Product, CTO and cross-functional leadership and teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate cross functionally with customer success, sales and marketing to ensure our product is being positioned and sold accurately and is well supported&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build a business case for investment by articulating initiative recommendations and trade-offs to leadership and cross-functional stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will work with cross-functional leaders to communicate the product roadmap and deliver on GTM activities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are a high agency leader who knows how to hire and foster this growth mindset within a team &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a proven track record of inspiring, leading, and rallying cross-functional teams behind a product vision &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You understand the importance of a strong collaborative relationship with design and engineering&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You understand the importance of learning and will create safety for exploration and innovation to foster a learning organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Product&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will obsess over the MarTech industry &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will learn and leverage knowledge across the organization to stay abreast the latest industry trends in social media, marketing, seo, and customer experience &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will learn and stay abreast of competitor changes but understand the most differentiated products keep an eye on the competitive landscape but obsess over their customers &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will learn and obsess over our customers, from its buyers to its day to day users you understand that without knowing them deeply our products will fail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will learn and obsess over delivering solutions that solve customer problems in ways that work for the business (understanding cross-functional teams constraints and motivations)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will develop a deep understanding of our customers' &amp;amp; prospects' problems to be best equipped to guide our product team and deliver solutions that drive growth and customer retention &amp;amp; delight&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are not afraid to roll up your sleeves and join your product teams on customer discovery calls, testing, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of experience as Product Manager in SaaS / MarTech platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of experience managing product managers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding modern Product Management techniques (“Inspired” &amp;amp; “Empowered” [Cagan], “Lean Product Playbook” [Olsen], JTBD frameworks)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of outcome-based measurements and the difference between feature factories and impactful true product teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skilled in giving feedback, creating accountability and building trust (“Crucial Accountability” [Patterson], “Radical Candor” [Scott], “Speed of Trust” [Covey], etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of creating and facilitating learning organizations (“Fifth Discipline” [Senge])&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated track record of partnership with design and engineering&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What's SOCi's culture like?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Led by a team of industry experts, SOCi is leading the pack in Localized Marketing for Multi-Location brands. Our passionate team of SOCialites work from home or in our office locations in both San Diego, CA and Austin, TX. We offer flexible PTO, comprehensive health &amp;amp; benefits packages, 401k and matching  (amongst many other perks). Every new team member is equipped with a MacBook laptop, tech accessories &amp;amp; SOCi swag. We are a fast-paced, agile environment where thought leadership and input is encouraged. If you are looking for a place where you can come and make a difference in the way enterprise organizations utilize social technology, then SOCi is for you. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOCi is an Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex including sexual orientation and gender identity, national origin, disability, protected Veteran Status, or any other characteristic protected by applicable federal, state, or local law.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/soci-director-of-product-management"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/soci-director-of-product-management&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 20:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 20:16:25 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/soci-director-of-product-management</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/soci-director-of-product-management</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0075/9827/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Silo Technologies: Data Analyst</title>
      <region>North America Only</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0075/9827/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; San Francisco, CA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.usesilo.com"&gt;http://www.usesilo.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;The Role:&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As our founding Data Analyst, you will work closely with all functions at Silo to ensure we have access to accurate data, digestible and flexible reports, and informative dashboards. You’ll be responsible for developing, maintaining, and improving reports and dashboards in our BI Tool, Mode, as well as finding opportunities for improvements. Our Data Scientist, Director of Operations, and Head of Finance will support your work and collaborate with you on making Silo’s data analytics function successful for years to come. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work cross-functionally to support organization with internal analytics (e.g. product, marketing, sales, customer support, ops, finance etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support teams with defining and tracking key metrics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain dashboards in BI Tool, Mode, in order to monitor metric progress, as well as understand and interpret key drivers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform deep-dive analyses and support business decisions with actionable data-driven insights&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help develop data models and pipelines to preprocess data for analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help building dashboards for external analytics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the development of self-service analytics to enhance data access across organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively recommend improvements that ensure data hygiene and our ability to receive accurate insights used to make strategic decisions&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;An ideal candidate would have:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical skills: Strong SQL skills. High proficiency using one of the dash-boarding/BI tools (preferably Mode). Google spreadsheet/Excel. Minimum level 3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data Visualization: Can effectively convey the key message with a visualization. Uses a variety of visual aids, uses appropriate visualization for data (e.g. line or bar for time-series). Minimum level 3.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication: Strong data storytelling skills with the ability to communicate effectively with non-technical stakeholders. Highly collaborative with experience working cross-functionally. Minimum level 3.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critical Thinking: Understands what question is being asked beyond what words are being used. Can break down the problem and find answers with data. Comfortable to develop and suggest metrics  in line with company's objectives. Goes beyond the numbers and thinks critically about the "why". Minimum level 3.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;gt; 2 years of relevant experience in data, business, product analytics. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands-on mindset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-starter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a startup environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Python knowledge is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with descriptive and inferential statistics is a plus &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/silo-technologies-data-analyst"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/silo-technologies-data-analyst&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 20:23:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 20:23:11 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/silo-technologies-data-analyst</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/silo-technologies-data-analyst</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0075/9557/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>Pixellu: Lead Product Designer</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0075/9557/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; Seattle, USA
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.pixellu.com/"&gt;https://www.pixellu.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;⭐ SUMMARY&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;We are Pixellu, a software company on a mission to take the work out of running a photography business so photographers can do what they love. We are seeking a world-class Lead Product Designer to head our product design. You’ll be working with the Head of Product, CEO, and CTO to develop a product design vision and execute on that vision with the help of fellow designers, product managers, and engineering. In this role, you will be both a designer on a major product and a leader of other product designers.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is not a “sit in the office and plan” role. This is a role where you will be with the exec team one day, and in the trenches the next. Expect to roll up your sleeves and be in the weeds, doing the work.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;😎 YOUR ROLE&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;Pixellu currently has three main products - SmartAlbums, SmartSlides, and Galleries. You would be the designer responsible for one of these products, while leading the other two designers. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Your job will be to:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Conduct user research and testing. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Plan: &lt;/strong&gt;Help shape the product vision, strategy, and prioritization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Prototype:&lt;/strong&gt; Define the user experience, interactions, and user interface through user flows, information architecture, sketches and wireframes, and visual design. Build functional prototypes to validate and test your designs. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Interaction design:&lt;/strong&gt; Design simple, streamlined, data-driven, user-centric experiences that delight users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Lead: &lt;/strong&gt;Lead our small team of product designers. Set standards, inspire, motivate, manage, and execute.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;📗 &lt;strong&gt;REQUIREMENTS&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;Aside from the standard job description, here is what we most value in a candidate:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Obsession with simplicity and intuitive interactions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mastery and appreciation of color, space, typography, iconography, illustration, and UX laws&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough knowledge of the latest trends in UX/UI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;People &amp;amp; communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data-driven decision making&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4+ years of experience in designing, shipping, and maintaining products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;🏖️ BENEFITS&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🌎 Work from anywhere with a good internet connection — our team is 100% remote and distributed all over the world, across 15 countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;​​🕙 Freedom to choose your own working hours — We have three "required online ​​hours" which are 8-11 am Pacific Time. Outside of those hours, you are free to work at whatever time of day suits you best. Structure your work around your kids, family, hobbies, and around the time of day that you know you are most productive. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;💰 Competitive salary based on experience level and your local cost of living considerations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📈 You get rewarded as we grow. As a Pixellu employee, you’ll become part of our Quarterly Profit-Sharing program where you’ll receive bonuses based on seniority and ​​role as Pixellu continues to grow.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid parental leave.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🏝 22 paid days off annually, with the ability to make up missed days on weekends. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;🚀 ABOUT PIXELLU&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div&gt;At Pixellu, we know professional photographers are frustrated with all of the tedious work required to run a successful photography business. Many get so overwhelmed, they end up quitting on their dream of having a photography career. That is why we create easy-to-use, time-saving software that takes the work out of running a photography business so photographers can get back to doing what they love, creating art.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Pixellu was co-founded in 2010 by two wedding photographers. Faced with the challenges of long hours and endless tasks, we began asking ourselves, “How can we save valuable time, make more money, and get our lives back?” Our answer was technology. We started Pixellu with the idea that we could make money by providing an honest service that helped photographers save time and live more fulfilling lives. We believed that, by focusing on a great product and great service, we could build a business that not only does good, but also does well. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Today, we are a team of 35 team members spread across 15 countries, serving tens of thousands of photographers in over 100 countries. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our vision is for Pixellu to become the foundation of more than 1 million successful photography businesses, so that photographers can focus on doing what they love while we automate the rest of their work. We are becoming the bridge between their camera and clients — all they would need to do is upload their photos to Pixellu. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We embrace the spirit of autonomous teams that are empowered to change the photography world while having a healthy work-life balance. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="https://vimeo.com/405889874"&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to learn more about us and why you’ll love working at Pixellu.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/pixellu-lead-product-designer-1"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/pixellu-lead-product-designer-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 16:20:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 16:20:02 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/pixellu-lead-product-designer-1</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/pixellu-lead-product-designer-1</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <media:content url="https://wwr-pro.s3.amazonaws.com/logos/0071/4151/logo.gif" type="image/png"/>
      <title>A.Team: Senior Independent Product Manager/Product Designer ($110-$190/hr)</title>
      <region>Anywhere in the World</region>
      <category>Product</category>
      <type>Full-Time</type>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://we-work-remotely.imgix.net/logos/0071/4151/logo.gif?ixlib=rails-4.0.0&amp;w=50&amp;h=50&amp;dpr=2&amp;fit=fill&amp;auto=compress" /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Headquarters:&lt;/strong&gt; NYC, SF, and TLV
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://build.a.team/wwrfastrackreferral"&gt;https://build.a.team/wwrfastrackreferral&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="https://build.a.team/wwrproductmgrfasttrack"&gt;A·Team&lt;/a&gt; is a VC-backed, stealth, application-only home on the internet for Senior Product Managers &amp;amp; Product Designers (along with developers &amp;amp; UX/UI folks) to team up with the best companies on their next big thing. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After talking with hundreds of independent engineers, designers, and product folks, we heard over and over that finding vetted, high-quality, consistent clients is hard, and projects are often too small to be rewarding. A·Team matches small teams of the most talented builders in the world with companies backed by a16z, YC, Softbank, General Catalyst, etc. on a contract basis for many of their most important initiatives. We quietly launched in May 2020, and have helped A·Teamers earn $11.4+ million since.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As part of A·Team, you can expect:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;High-paying, meaningful client missions (where you'd lead Product) with the most audacious companies&lt;/strong&gt; sent your way; generally $110-$190/hr, with vetted, fascinating clients doing work that matters. We're picky about who we partner with; new clients only come in via trusted referral. We've worked with Lyft, McGraw Hill, ClearCo, irl.com, the former CEO of Waze, the leading vaccine production software, several new unicorns we can't say here, and dozens of startups backed by a16z/YC/Softbank/etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Work alongside friends old &amp;amp; new: &lt;/strong&gt;our niche is small/diverse product teams, since clients with larger budgets and higher-impact work tell us they want teams, not individuals. Of course, we keep friends together whenever we can.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Full autonomy:&lt;/strong&gt; say "no" to things that don't excite you. The most talented builders often juggle a few things at once, so there's never pressure to join an A·Team mission if you don't have the bandwidth. If we're no longer a fit, it's easy to leave or pause too. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Small, curated, off-the-record gatherings:&lt;/strong&gt; for conversations hard to have elsewhere. Long-term, we're creating micro-communities for the world's top builders to become friends around the things they care about.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Keep 100% of what you earn: &lt;/strong&gt;if you charge $130/hr, you get $130/hr. A·Team makes money by charging a small, flat, transparent platform fee on &lt;em&gt;top&lt;/em&gt; of your rate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to apply:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Go here: &lt;a href="https://build.a.team/wwrproductmgrfasttrack"&gt;https://build.a.team/wwrproductmgrfasttrack&lt;/a&gt; + mention WWR under how you heard about A·Team. No resume or cover letter needed; we respect your time so the application is short. We're also much more interested in seeing what you've made, and excited to chat more if there’s a fit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What you’ll do:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once part of A.Team, you’ll regularly be invited to be the lead Product manager/designer for impactful missions that match your interests, which you can accept or decline. Take your pick from early-stage incubations with world-class founders, to fast-growing super-funded companies, to old-school non-tech incumbents looking to build as a tech giant would.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Missions usually involve building an ambitious piece of software from 0 to 1 as part of a small 3-4 person team. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ll be paid to scope it out, give the client options, guide strategy, and execute on the selected solution. Sometimes the client has a clear vision, sometimes not; which is why A.Team builders tend to be senior folks who can work together to find the right direction. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who A&lt;/strong&gt;·&lt;strong&gt;Team is for:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Senior Product Managers/Designers who left large companies and high-growth startups to pursue their craft with autonomy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Those who prefer consistent contract work over a full-time role, who want to create a variety of new products alongside other top-tier builders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The majority of A.Teamers spend most of their time doing independent work, but a sizeable percentage are either employed full-time (but testing out client work), bootstrapping a side project, or looking for their next big thing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who A&lt;/strong&gt;·&lt;strong&gt;Team is &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; for:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;People looking for small gigs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Folks looking to build simple wordpress/wix/squarespace-style websites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Those still early in their careers and recent university/bootcamp grads (at least not yet).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our long-term vision:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://build.a.team/wwrproductmgrfasttrack"&gt;&lt;span&gt;A·Team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is a new type of company for a new kind of independent software builders. We call them "unhirables": people who traditional companies couldn’t hire full-time even if they wanted to, but who want to do their most meaningful work with their favorite people in small, autonomous, distributed expert teams. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;To help us secure amazing missions, we raised $5 million+ (not public, yet) from NFX, Village Global, and Box Group, along with the former CEO of Upwork, the founders of Fiverr and Lemonade, Apple's Global Head of Recruiting, YC Partner Aaron Harris, Wharton's Adam Grant, and Duke's Dan Ariely.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/a-team-senior-independent-product-manager-product-designer-110-190-hr"&gt;https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/a-team-senior-independent-product-manager-product-designer-110-190-hr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 23:21:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <expires_at>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 23:21:48 +0000</expires_at>
      <guid>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/a-team-senior-independent-product-manager-product-designer-110-190-hr</guid>
      <link>https://weworkremotely.com/remote-jobs/a-team-senior-independent-product-manager-product-designer-110-190-hr</link>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
